[SILENCE]
♪MY PLACE IS THE WAY♪
♪FROM OGUM AND IANSÃ♪
♪ THERE IS SAMBA ♪
♪ATÉ DE MANHÃ♪
♪A GINGA ON EVERY FLOOR♪
♪MY PLACE♪
♪IT’S SURROUNDED BY FIGHT AND SWEAT♪
♪HOPE IN A BETTER WORLD♪
♪AND BEER TO CELEBRATE♪
♪MY PLACE♪
♪IT HAS ITS MYTHS♪
♪E BEINGS OF LIGHT♪
♪IT’S VERY CLOSE TO OSVALDO CRUZ♪
♪CASCADURA, VAZ LOBO AND IRAJÁ♪
♪MY PLACE♪
♪IT’S A SMILE, IT’S PEACE AND PLEASURE♪
♪YOUR NAME IS SWEET TO SAY♪
♪É DIVINO♪
[WOMAN] WE ARE HERE IN THE DIVINO, SUBURBIAN NEIGHBORHOOD
FROM RIO DE JANEIRO, WHERE THE GUNNER
FROM THIS YEAR'S CARIOCA CHAMPIONSHIP, JORGE TUFÃO,
BORN AND RAISED. PLEASE, YOUR DIOGENES?
[DIOGENES] NOTHING, LADY.
[WOMAN] THE TYPHOON, HE HAS STAND OUT IN THE CARIOCA CHAMPIONSHIP.
[DIOGENES] YES, YES, OF COURSE. [WOMAN] TONIGHT
IS HE THE ONE WHO WILL SCORE THE VICTORY GOAL?
[DIÓGENES] OH MY DAUGHTER, TYPHOON DOES NOT DISAPPOINT,
HE DOESN'T MAKE MISTAKES, HE NEVER MAKES MISTAKES AND YOU KNOW WHAT HIS NAME WAS
HIM HERE BEFORE? MACHINE, GOAL SCORING MACHINE,
MADAM. AND TODAY IS MY BOY'S DAY,
WHO I RAISED AS IF HE WAS MY SON!
YES, HE IS A CREATE, HE IS A CREATE HERE OF OUR... OF OUR...
FROM OUR DIVINE FOOTBALL CLUB!
[MAN] I WAS THE ONE WHO THREW THE FIRST BALL
AS A GIFT FOR TYPHOON.
[TYPHOON] THAT'S A LIAR, RIGHT? LOOK AT THE SALAFRÁRIO,
THIS IS WORTH NOTHING, THIS HARD BREAD OF YOUR JUCA,
WHEN HE MOVED TO DIVINE, I WAS ALREADY AN ADULT
AND I WAS ALREADY THE HOLDER, UNDERSTAND? REMEMBER THAT BAR
WHAT DID HE HAVE? NEVER LET YOU GET A CASH ON THAT CRAP!
[LELECO] RELEASE, MY SON, RELEASE!
[MURICY] DON'T GET NERVOUS, SON, DON'T GET NERVOUS.
AND TODAY IS YOUR DAY, TODAY NOTHING CAN MAKE YOU LOSE
YOUR CONCENTRATION, TODAY IS THE DAY YOU TAKE THE FIELD,
MY SON, AND IT’S A GOAL! IT'S GOAL!
[TYPHOON] THIS IS WHAT MAKES ME NERVOUS, UNDERSTAND?
EVERYONE SAYING IT'S A GOAL, YOU HAVE TO SCORED A GOAL, GOAL,
WHAT IF YOU DON'T? HUH? WHAT IF IT DOESN'T HAPPEN?
[MURICY] NO, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, SORRY, SORRY, SON,
THE MOTHER IS NERVOUS, THE MOTHER IS NERVOUS.
[IVANA] OH, THE TELEVISION IS OUTSIDE, COME ON.
[TYPHOON] LET ME GO IN MY TIME, LET...
FATHER, SAY I'M GOING IN MY TIME.
[IVANA] LET ME PUT ON A LITTLE MAKEUP,
IT'S MALE RICE POWDER!
[TYPHOON] ALWAYS THIS FRESH, DAMN IT?
[LELECO] THE SPONSOR'S SHIRT.
[MURICY] HE PUTS OVER IT, PUTS OVER IT.
BOOT, BOOT, BOOT. WAIT I'LL GO WITH YOU!
[MAN] JUST ONE WORD, TYPHOON.
TYPHOON, WHAT ARE YOUR EXPECTATIONS TODAY?
TYPHOON, WHAT ARE YOUR EXPECTATIONS FOR TODAY?
[MURICY] WAIT, WAIT, WAIT IT'S SO SWEATY.
[TYPHOON] NO, WHAT... MOTHER? THE EXPECTATION IS CERTAINLY...
I WILL GIVE THE BEST OF MYSELF AND SHOW THE BEST FOOTBALL
THAT I CAN HAVE IN THE FIELD.
[MAN] DID THE TEACHER SAY SOMETHING SPECIAL TODAY?
[WOMAN] STRAIGHTENING IS GOING TO BE SHOW, RIGHT, MONALISA?
[MONALISA] IS CURRENTLY THE PRODUCT
THAT HAS MORE OUTLETS IN THE SALON.
[WOMAN] DO YOU SEE WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
ME, HUH? IT SEEMS LIKE IT'S IN ANOTHER WAY.
[MONALISA] OH, I'M SORRY, I'M LISTENING TO MY BOYFRIEND
TALKING ON TELEVISION.
[WOMAN] ARE YOU TYPHOON'S GIRLFRIEND?
[WOMAN] I AM, YES. [MONALISA] HOW CHIC, GIRL.
[OLENKA] OH, MONALISA, MY FRIEND, ARE YOU NOT DELUDED?
THE TYPHOON WAS TURNING AROUND WITH YOU,
THIS DOESN'T MEAN THAT HE WANTS ANYTHING SERIOUS WITH YOU.
[MONALISA] ME, HUH? THAT "A TURN" WHAT? ARE YOU CRAZY?
I'VE BEEN WITH HIM FOR TWO YEARS.
[MAN] AFTER SO MUCH SUCCESS, TYPHOON,
WHAT ARE THE PLANS FOR THE FUTURE?
[TYPHOON] I INTEND TO GET MARRIED SOON.
[MAN] OOO, GREAT NEWS THEN.
AND DOES THE WEDDING ALREADY HAVE A DATE SCHEDULED?
[TYPHOON] IT'S... NEXT MONTH, NEXT MONTH.
[MAN] AND WHERE WILL THE HONEYMOON BE?
[TYPHOON] CANCÚN, EVERYTHING IS ALREADY SCHEDULED.
[LAUGHTER]
[MONALISA] BUT WHAT WEDDING IS THIS? I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
[OLENKA] NO, THIS IS SOMETHING THAT MAKES YOU THINK, PEOPLE...
[MONALISA] NO, NO, NO, TYPHOON IS NOT GETTING MARRIED,
HE WOULD HAVE TOLD ME SOMETHING!
[WOMAN] MY DAUGHTER, I KNOW YOU'RE NOT VERY WELL,
BUT IT'S TINGLING HERE. LOOK, I THINK THIS PRODUCT
IT'S BEEN IN MY HEAD FOR TOO LONG,
OH MY GOD, GET THIS BUSINESS OUT OF HERE.
[RITA] [SIREN IMITATION] " CAN SOMEONE HELP ME?
MY HOUSE IS ON FIRE."
[SIREN IMITATION]
[RITA] "HELP, MY"... [CARMINHA] STOP SCREAMING,
PLAGUE! DON'T YOU KNOW HOW TO PLAY QUIETLY?
[RITA] "PLEASE HELP ME, PLEASE!"
[SIREN IMITATION]
[RITA] "PLEASE SOMEONE HELP ME, SOMEONE HELP ME,
PLEASE?" [IMITATION OF SIREN] "SOMEONE HELP ME,
SOMEONE HELP ME."
[CARMINHA] WHAT ARE YOU DOING, GIRL?
CAN'T YOU SEE THAT I'M BOXING EVERYTHING?
[RITA] BOXING FOR WHAT? WE'RE NOT GOING TO MOVE FROM HERE.
[CARMINHA] WE'RE GOING TO MOVE, YES, I'VE ALREADY TOLD YOU A THOUSAND TIMES,
THIS HOUSE IS BEING SOLD.
[RITA] NOBODY CAN SELL THIS HOUSE. THIS HOUSE IS MY MOTHER'S.
[CARMINHA] GO PUT ON YOUR UNIFORM, IT'S TIME FOR SCHOOL.
[RITA] I'M NOT GOING TO SCHOOL TODAY. I'M NOT GOING AND THAT'S IT.
[CARMINHA] YOU WILL OBEY ME, GIRL, YOU WILL OBEY ME!
I'M WARNING YOU! IT WILL BE BETTER FOR YOU.
[RITA] I DON'T OBEY YOU, IT'S NOT MINE AT ALL,
YOU ARE NOT MY MOTHER, YOU ARE NOTHING!
[CARMINHA] YOUR MOTHER DIED. IT'S DEAD AND BURIED.
IT'S UNDER THE EARTH AND THE WORMS HAVE ALREADY ATE IT
HER WHOLE BODY, DID YOU HEAR THAT?
ALL THE WORMS EATING MOM'S BODY?
SO, GIRL, NOW I'M HERE,
YOUR FATHER'S WIFE! AND YOU OBEY ME!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] WILL YOU CHALLENGE ME?
[CARMINHA] DID YOU DECIDE TO CHALLENGE ME?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RITA] NO, NO, NO, PLEASE NO! PLEASE DO NOT!
THE DOLL MY MOTHER GAVE ME, PLEASE NO!
[CARMINHA] SO YOU LEARN, GIRL, NOT TO MESS WITH ME!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] NOW YOU'RE GOING TO GET IT!
[RITA] MY FATHER SAID YOU CAN'T HIT ME.
[CARMINHA] HE WON'T KNOW I'M GOING TO BEAT YOU
WITH A WET TOWEL.
[RITA] I'LL TELL HIM.
[CARMINHA] YEAH, WHO DO YOU THINK HE’LL BELIEVE,
HUH, TELL ME? IN YOU OR IN ME?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] HUH?
[DOOR OPEN]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RITA] DADDY!
[GENÉSIO] WHAT WAS IT? WHAT IS HAPPENING HERE?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] HUH?
[RITA] SHE ALMOST HIT ME.
[GENÉSIO] HIT? WHAT...WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT? BA... HOW DID YOU HIT? WHAT IS THAT?
[CARMINHA] LOOK WHAT RITA DID TO ME, LOOK.
[GENÉSIO] WHAT HAPPENED? WAIT, WAIT...
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU? [RITA] DADDY!
[GENÉSIO] WAIT, LET ME TALK TO HER, WAIT.
SPEAK, SPEAK, WHAT WAS IT?
[RITA] LOOK WHAT SHE DID TO MY DOLL!
[GENÉSIO] I WANT TO KNOW WHAT HAPPENS...
[CARMINHA] RITINHA, MY LOVE! MY GOD,
IT WAS YOU YOURSELF WHO FINISHED THE DOLL.
[RITA] [STUMBLING] DAD, IT'S A LIE!
[GENÉSIO] RITA!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] LOVE,
SHE INVENTS THINGS. [GENÉSIO] CALM DOWN...
[CARMINHA] SHE WANTS TO PLAY WITH ME IN ANY WAY,
LOVE. I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO ANYMORE, MY GOD.
RITA, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, WHAT DID I DO TO YOU? I KNOW I AM NOT
YOUR MOM, LOVE, I DON'T EVEN WANT TO TAKE HER PLACE.
I WANT TO BE YOUR FRIEND, I LOVE YOU. LOVE YOU MY LOVE.
[RITA] LIAR! [CARMINHA] YES, I LOVE IT.
[RITA] [SHOUTING] LIAR! LIAR!
[WAY]
[GENÉSIO] [SHOUTING] OH RITA, COME HERE! RETURN! COME HERE! RITA!
WHAT IS THIS, PEOPLE? I'VE NEVER SEEN THIS GIRL LIKE THIS... RITE!
[CARMINHA] LEAVE IT, LEAVE IT, LEAVE IT. I UNDERSTAND HER, POOR GIRL.
I UNDERSTAND. AT THAT AGE, SHE HAS NO MOTHER.
[GENÉSIO] OH MY LOVE, DON’T TALK LIKE THAT, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD,
IT'S JUST JEALOUSY...
[CARMINHA] I LIKE HER SO MUCH, I WISH SHE LIKED IT
JUST A LITTLE LITTLE OF ME.
[GENÉSIO] GIVE IT A BREAK, DEAR, GIVE IT A BREAK.
YOU WILL SEE. YOU WILL SEE THAT NATURALLY THIS WILL HAPPEN.
I SWEAR TO YOU, LOOK AT ME, I SWEAR TO YOU! LET'S SIT DOWN,
SIT HERE FOR A WHILE, SIT. SIT. SEARCH...
TRY TO SELF... TRY TO CALM DOWN.
[CARMINHA] I'M SUFFERING A LOT...
[GENESIUS] CHRIST.
[GENÉSIO] AND... YES... SORRY, BUT... ARE YOU ALREADY...
PACKING THINGS?
[CARMINHA] I'M GETTING AHEAD, LOVE. I'M ADVANCED, YES. DO YOU SIGN
SCRIPTURE TODAY, IS IT? [GENÉSIO] HUH?
[CARMINHA] WILL YOU SIGN THE DEED TODAY?
[GENÉSIO] OH, YEAH... YEAH, IT'S... HALF AND HALF.
[OLENKA] HERE, MONA, GO HOME, GO. LEAVE IT THERE.
YOU NEED TO REST, GO.
[MONALISA] NO, IMAGINE, THAT. I DON'T HAVE THAT WITH ME, NO.
I WILL STAY UNTIL THE END OF THE WORKSHOP. YOU KNOW ME,
YOU KNOW HOW I AM. I AM NOT A WOMAN
THAT I LET MYSELF GET DOWN, NO. I CAN TAKE THE LOCK.
[HAIRDRYER]
[OLENKA] [LAUGHS] COME HERE, OK, JUST FOR A LITTLE BIT. GIVE US LICENSE, OK?
[MONALISA] [VOICE SHAKEN] SORRY!
[OLENKA] DON'T BE LIKE THIS!
[MONALISA] HOW DID HE HAVE THE COURAGE TO DO THIS TO ME?
ON TELEVISION! I KNEW ON TELEVISION!
[OLENKA] I KNOW, MONA... MONALISA, I'M ALREADY TIRED
TO TELL YOU, MAN IS ALL A BUNCH OF DOGS, SISTER.
[MONALISA] BUT HE TOLD ME A WEEK AGO THAT HE LOVED ME,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THIS?
[OLENKA] BUT LET IT BE, THAT BLONDE GIRL HE GOT
THEN, YOU'LL TAKE ALL THE MONEY FROM HIM. YOU WILL SEE IT ONLY. AH, GO!
[MONALISA] BLONDE? WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT?
[OLENKA] OH, I DON'T KNOW, YOU ALWAYS EXCHANGE IT FOR A BLONDE, RIGHT?
[MONALISA] DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING?
[OLENKA] NO... [MONALISA] NO, YOU SAID:
"THE BLONDE". WHAT BLONDE IS THIS?
[SILAS] ATTENTION, ATTENTION, ATTENTION! LADIES, GENTLEMEN,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN! IMMEDIATELY REQUESTED
THE PRESENCE OF THE ONE WHO RAISES OUR SPIRIT HERE
IN OUR NEIGHBORHOOD! WE ARE TALKING ABOUT THE Dignified,
FROM SORUMBÁTIC, FROM METAPHÓRIC, FROM PRINCIPISSIMA,
FUTURE FIRST LADY HERE AT DIVINE!
MONALISA BARBOSA DA SILVA! JHO... JHO...
JORGE TUFÃO ASKS HER TO MARRY!
[MONALISA] WHAT... WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS?
[OLENKA] NO, THIS IS A PRANK, FOR SURE.
[MONALISA] GUYS, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT,
ARE YOU STILL GOING TO MAKE A WORD ABOUT MY SUFFERING?
[SILAS] COME WITH ME, LOOK AT THIS. FOLLOW ME! FOLLOW ME!
THERE IS A SURPRISE TODAY, HUH? IT COULD BE YOU!
AND THERE SHE IS! WE WILL RECEIVE WITH GREAT JOY,
THE MESOPOTAMICA, THE STROGONOPHICA, THE MAJESTÁTICA,
MONALISA BARBOSA DA SILVA!
[OVATION]
[SILAS] SILENCE, SILENCE, SILENCE!
[MONALISA] WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS, SILAS?
[SILAS] MONALISA BARBOSA DA SILVA,
YOU ACCEPT IN MARRIAGE JOR,
JOR, JOR, JOR...
TYPHOON?
[SCREAMS OF CELEBRATION]
[OLENKA] ACCEPT!
[SILAS] SILENCE, SILENCE, SILENCE.
[MONALISA] DO YOU WANT TO HAVE FUN AT MY EXPENSE?
IT'S NO LONGER ENOUGH FOR EVERYONE TO KNOW THAT I GOT A PACK IN THE ASS,
TYPHOON SAID ON TELEVISION THAT HE WAS GOING TO MARRY SOMEONE ELSE,
HE IS THERE IN CONCENTRATION,
YOU CAME HERE TO SEE IT UP CLOSE
MY HUMILIATION, IS THAT IT?
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, DEAR!
[TOGETHER] TYPHOON! TYPHOON! TYPHOON! TYPHOON!
[MONALISA] TYPHOON, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I KNOW, YOU SAW THE MESS YOU DID, RIGHT?
AND YOU CAME TO ASK ME FOR SORRY, YOU CAME TO ASK FOR FORGIVENESS,
BECAUSE YOU BREAK UP WITH ME ON TELEVISION, RIGHT?
CAN YOU EXPLAIN ME WHAT PRESEPADA IS THIS?
WHAT DO YOU MEANT BY THAT?
ARE YOU WANTING TO MAKE ME CRAZY?
[TYPHOON] MY LOVE, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I ESCAPE FROM CONCENTRATION TO ASK YOU TO MARRY,
WHAT DID YOU NOT LIKE? OF CAR? OF THE MESSAGE? SURPRISE?
[MONALISA] WHAT DO YOU WANT? HOW DO YOU WANT
THAT I BELIEVE IN YOU?
[TYPHOON] I CAME HERE TO ASK YOU TO MARRY, GIRL!
DO YOU ACCEPT OR NOT ACCEPT?
[TOGETHER] ACCEPT! ACCEPTED! ACCEPTED! ACCEPTED!
[SILAS] SILENCE, SILENCE, LET'S HEAR THE ANSWER.
[MONALISA] WHAT ABOUT THE HONEYMOON IN CANCÚN?
[TYPHOON] BUT YOU DIDN'T WANT TO SEE MEXICO?
[MONALISA] IS CANCÚN IN MEXICO?
[TYPHOON] OH, NO IT'S NO?
[MONALISA] WHERE IS CANCÚN? I THAT...
I WANT TO KNOW ABOUT THE 20 YEAR OLD BLONDE.
[TYPHOON] NO, THERE IS NO BLOND, LOVE, THERE IS NO
NO BLONDE, IT'S ONLY YOU IN MY LIFE.
[COMMOTION]
[SILAS] SILENCE.
[MONALISA] SWEAR? SO DO YOU REALLY WANT TO MARRY ME?
[TYPHOON] WHAT DO YOU THINK I'M DOING HERE?
OH, I EVEN BROUGHT A RING.
[COMMOTION]
[SILAS] SILENCE...
[TYPHOON] I'LL START FROM THE BEGINNING...
[TYPHOON] MONALISA.
[COMMOTION]
[SILAS] SILENCE, SILENCE.
[TYPHOON] YOU ACCEPT ME...
LIKE YOUR FUTURE HUSBAND?
♪OUR LOVE♪
[MONALISA] I ACCEPT, OF COURSE I ACCEPT!
[SCREAMS OF CELEBRATION]
♪IN THIS STORY OF THE TWO OF US♪
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪IT’S NOT A WORK OF CHANCE♪
♪IT’S A DESIGNED PLAN♪
[CARMINHA] WHAT IS IT, MY LOVE? ARE YOU SAD?
[GENÉSIO] I'M SAYING GOODBYE TO THIS HOUSE,
IT'S A LOT OF MEMORIES.
[CARMINHA] I KNOW,
YOUR EX-WIFE WENT THROUGH HER ILLNESS HERE, RIGHT?
[GENÉSIO] Yeah.
[CARMINHA] DIED HERE.
THAT'S WHY IT'S GOOD TO MOVE OUT OF THIS HOUSE NOW, LOVE.
NEW LIFE, BALL FORWARD.
[GENÉSIO] [LAUGHTER] Yeah.
DID YOU KNOW THAT MARTA WAS BORN HERE?
HERE. I TOLD YOU ALREADY, RIGHT?
THAT THIS WAS HER FAMILY HOME.
AND... [MUXOXO] IT'S DIFFICULT, YOU KNOW?
BEFORE I DIE,
SHE MADE ME SWEAR I WOULD NEVER SELL THIS HOUSE.
[CARMINHA] LOVE, I'M SURE
THAT WHEREVER MARTA IS,
WHAT SHE WANTS IS FOR YOU TO BE HAPPY.
AND WE WILL BE MUCH HAPPIER IN THE TAQUARA APARTMENT,
LOVE, I'M SURE.
AND THEN, HERE IS VERY BIG,
AS YOU SAY YOURSELF, FULL OF MEMORIES.
[GENÉSIO] [LAUGHTER]
IT'S FIRE, RIGHT? PEOPLE KEEP THINKING.
YOU'RE RIGHT, SEE?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] HI, DAUGHTER.
[GENÉSIO] BYE, GO WITH GOD, SEE?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] LOOK, COME HERE.
[GENÉSIO] IT'S NOT GOING TO LEAVE LIKE THAT, RIGHT?
SAY A RIGHT SAY TO CARMINHA NOW,
GO. GO, GO AND SAY GOODBYE TO HER PROPERLY, GO.
RITA, GO AWAY, DAUGHTER. RITA.
[DOOR OPEN]
[GENÉSIO] DAUGHTER, DON’T DO IT...
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] OUR LADY. AGAIN, I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU WILL HAVE TO HAVE A LOT OF PATIENCE.
[CARMINHA] LOVE, I'LL HAVE ALL THE PATIENCE IN THE WORLD.
[GENÉSIO] AH, GIRL, I DON'T KNOW.
[CARMINHA] STAY CALM. LOVE, IT'S ALMOST TIME FOR YOU TO GO
FOR SERVICE, COME ON, I'LL GET YOUR SUIT.
FROM THERE DO YOU GO DIRECTLY TO THE BANK?
[GENÉSIO] I'M GOING, I'M GOING DIRECTLY.
[CARMINHA] WHAT ABOUT THE BUYER OF THE HOUSE, DOES HE PAY YOU IN CINCH?
[GENÉSIO] OH, YEAH, THAT'S IT,
YOU'LL PAY ME IN CINCH, YOU DON'T THINK IT'S DANGEROUS
AM I GOING OUT CARRYING ALL THIS MONEY FROM THE BANK? THERE IS?
[CARMINHA] I THINK.
[STEPS]
[CARMINHA] LOVE, YOUR SUIT IS ALREADY PREPARED. DO ONE THING...
[GENÉSIO] DID YOU PUT ON A TIE HERE AND EVERYTHING?
[DOOR CLOSE]
[CARMINHA] PUT THE MONEY IN THIS BAG.
YOU LEAVE THE BANK UNWORRIED, THERE IS NO DANGER.
[GENÉSIO] AH, UNWORRIED. [LAUGHS]
ALL RIGHT, LETS GO, RIGHT?
I LOVE YOU.
[KISSING CLAP]
[CARMINHA] NEW LIFE!
[GENESIUM] NEW LIFE.
[KISSING CLAP]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MAN] COME ON, APOLO, RODRIGO, GABRIELA. VAMBORA, CÍNTIA, RITA.
COME ON, RITA. COME ON, RITINHA.
♪MÚSICA DRAMÁTICA♪
[MAN] CLOSE THE DOOR.
[CARMINHA] ANSWER, DAMN IT. OH, DID YOU ANSWER? WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I DIDN'T TELL YOU NOT TO LEAVE, I WAS GOING TO CALL
ANY TIME? IT'S RIGHT, IT'S RIGHT. OH, LISTEN HERE.
[URBAN ENVIRONMENT]
[GATE OPEN]
[CARMINHA] THERE IS NO ERROR, GENÉSIO MUST BE LEAVING
FROM THE BANK BETWEEN 12PM AND 12:30PM. HE WILL GET THE MONEY FROM THE SALE
FROM THE HOUSE IN THE BAG I GAVE HIM.
OF COURSE. GUARANTEE, GENESIO'S FOOL
YOU'RE NOT SUSPECTING ANYTHING. COME HERE AND THAT COLLEAGUE OF YOURS WHO
YOU TAKEN OFF, YOU ARE TRUSTED, RIGHT? LOOK THERE, HUH? IT'S A LOT OF MONEY,
OUR FUTURE. AS SOON AS YOU GET YOUR HAND ON THE MONEY,
YOU CALL ME, UNDERSTAND? I'M JUST WAITING TO SIGN THE TERMS
TO GET OUT OF THIS HOUSE. NO, OF COURSE, I'LL WAIT
ABOUT TWO, THREE DAYS, UNTIL IT DISAPPEARED FOREVER SO AS TO EVER BE NOTWEEN SEEN, RIGHT?
OH, JUST THINKING THAT I WILL NEVER HAVE TO LOOK IN THE FACE AGAIN
FROM THAT OLD BABÃO DO GENÉSIO... OH, IT'S GOING TO BE AWESOME.
JUST THE TWO OF US IN FRIBURG, HUH?
IN THAT LITTLE CHALET, HUH? DELIGHT. WHAT? WHAT'S THAT, MAX?
OF COURSE THERE'S NO ONE AT HOME, DO YOU THINK I'M CRAZY?
THE PLAGUE WENT TO THE SCHOOL.
OKAY, OKAY, I'LL CHECK IT.
I COME, I LOVE YOU, YUMMY, YUMMY.
[CALL CLOSES]
[STEPS]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] [MUXOXO]
[DOOR CLOSE]
[KEY HANDLING]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[PHONE RING]
[CARMINHA] HELLO? WHAT? NO, AUNT, I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN INCREASING THE MILE PLAN, NO. I ALREADY SAID NO, ANTA,
ARE YOU DEAF? OH, IT'S GOING TO KILL YOU.
[CALL CLOSES]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[STEPS]
[MAN] HEY GIRL, DO YOU WANT TO BE PACKED, DO YOU? COME BACK HERE!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[SPEAKING]
[RITA] BOY, OPEN UP! BOY, OPEN UP! OPEN!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] I'LL TAKE A WHILE, BECAUSE I'LL GIVE
A TRIP TO THE BANK.
[MAN] IT’S CALM, GENÉSIO. GO THERE.
[GENÉSIO] SEE YOU. [MAN] SEE YOU.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RITA] SIR, IS MY FATHER THERE?
[MAN] HE JUST LEFT.
HE WENT TO GET HIS CAR FROM THE PARKING LOT.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[PLATFORM IMPACT ON THE GROUND]
[GENÉSIO] YEAH, THANK YOU.
THAT'S RIGHT. YOU CAN LEAVE IT, I'LL PULL THE THING OVER THERE.
♪MÚSICA DRAMÁTICA♪
[RITA] [SHOUTING] DADDY! FATHER!
[RITA] DADDY!
♪MÚSICA DRAMÁTICA♪
[GENÉSIO] WHAT IS THIS? DAUGHTER,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE, DAUGHTER?
[RITA] FATHER, I HAVE TO TALK TO THE LORD
ANYWAY. SO INTENDED TO STEAL THE LORD
WHEN YOU LEAVE THE BANK, THEY WILL TAKE YOUR PURSE WITH THE MONEY!
[GENÉSIO] WAIT, WAIT, CALM DOWN. SPEAK IT ALL AGAIN,
THAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND ANYTHING.
[RITA] CARMINHA, DADDY, SHE'S GETTING IT DONE
OF STEALING THE LORD.
[GENÉSIO] WHERE DID YOU GET THIS
CRAZY STORY, DAUGHTER?
[RITA] DAD, I HEARED HER ON THE PHONE.
[GENÉSIO] AH, DAUGHTER, YOU MUST HAVE BEEN CONFUSED, DAUGHTER.
SOMETIMES WE GET IT WRONG
WHEN YOU GET A HALF-HALF CONVERSATION.
[RITA] I SWEAR NOT. I HEAR IT RIGHT,
SHE WAS MATCHING WITH A GUY.
[GENÉSIO] YOU KNOW, THIS IS YOUR IMPLICATION WITH CARMINHA
IT'S BEYOND THE LIMIT.
[RITA] FATHER, DO YOU NOT WANT TO LISTEN TO ME?
THEY WILL STEAL THE LORD, THEY WILL TAKE EVERYTHING THAT IS US,
EVERYTHING THAT WAS MOM’S!
[GENÉSIO] DAUGHTER, I KNOW YOU DON’T WANT
THAT I SELL THE HOUSE,
I KNOW IT'S DIFFICULT TO ACCEPT ANOTHER WOMAN BY MY SIDE,
BUT WHAT YOU ARE DOING IS A VERY UGLY THING.
COME ON, COME ON, WAIT!
[RITA] DAD, IT'S TRUE!
[GENÉSIO] LOOK, I'M TELLING YOU SOMETHING: ARE YOU
ACCUSING THE WOMAN I LOVE OF SOMETHING VERY SERIOUS.
[RITA] DAD, IT'S TRUE!
[GENÉSIO] NO, IF... COME ON, THIS MATTER IS OVER.
GET IN THAT CAR, GET IN, I’LL LEAVE YOU AT SCHOOL,
THAT'S WHERE YOU SHOULD BE, IN SCHOOL!
GOOD, AND THERE IS NO MORE SAYING ABOUT THIS SUBJECT, DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
DON'T SAY ANY MORE ABOUT THIS SUBJECT!
[HORNS]
[GENÉSIO] HAVE YOU SEEN IT? THEN, GO WALK, GO WALK NOW.
IT'S THAT THE CHILD IS TALKING TO ME.
♪GOD PROTECT ME FROM YOUR ENVY♪
♪DEUS ME DEFENDA♪
♪FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
♪GOD HELP ME FROM YOUR ANGER♪
♪DEUS ME IMUNIZE♪
[VERÔNICA] WAKE UP, CRUCIBLE, THE BIG DAY HAS ARRIVED.
[CUCTION] DO YOU THINK I COULD SLEEP?
I DIDN'T BLINK AN EYE ALL NIGHT.
[VERÔNICA] TO SEE IF THEN THE TIME IS, YOU WON'T GET YELLOW.
[CRUCCILE] NO, NO.
[VERÔNICA] HUH, CRUCIBLE? LOOK THERE, HUH? FOR GOD'S SAKE,
YOU HAVE TO ASK FOR A LOT THROUGH THE BROKER.
CLEAN THE FLOWER, OK?
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE, 20 MILLION, OK?
THINK ABOUT THAT, 20 MILLION, OK? OUR FUTURE!
[CRUCCILE] OKAY, OKAY.
[VERÔNICA] CRUCIAL, YOU'RE NOT PAYING ATTENTION
WHAT AM I TALKING ABOUT? [CRUCCILE] OKAY, OKAY, YES.
[VERÔNICA] I'M GOING TO TURN OFF THE TV...
[CRUCILE] NO, NO, NO, DON'T DO THAT, NO, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD.
O, VERONIQUINHA, HUM!
IT'S JUST TODAY, IT'S A LONG TIME,
DID YOU UNDERSTAND? IN ADDITION TO BEING THE DAY THAT I WILL SELL MY BROKERAGE,
IT'S THE DECISION OF THE CARIOCA CHAMPIONSHIP, GUYS!
[VERÔNICA] HOW SO? WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES THIS GAME MAKE?
FOR YOU? IT'S NOT YOUR TEAM THAT'S PLAYING, CRAP.
YOU DON'T ROOT FOR THAT THING ABOUT... THE DIVINE, HUH,
WHO HASN'T WON A CHAMPIONSHIP IN OVER 40 YEARS?
[CRUCIBLE] THAT'S WHERE THE BEAUTY OF IT LIVES.
TUFÃO, WHO IS THE CARIOCA CHAMPIONSHIP'S TOP SCORES,
IT CAME FROM THE DIVINE FOOTBALL CLUB.
[VERÔNICA] DON'T DRINK COFFEE, IT'S NOT GOOD FOR YOU.
[CUCTION] I ALREADY TOLD YOU THIS STORY, BUT YOU FORGET, RIGHT?
HIS MOTHER, DONA MURICY, WAS A COOK AT HOME.
HE WAS MY BEST FRIEND
WHEN WE WERE KIDS, YEAH, AND TODAY...
[VERÔNICA] OH, EAT THIS, OMEGA THREE,
IT'S GOOD FOR YOU, EAT IT.
[CUCCILE] [THROAT CLEAR] AND TODAY... AND TODAY HE CAN...
HE COULD BE THE GOALScorer IN THE CARIOCA CHAMPIONSHIP.
[VERÔNICA] EAT, EAT, LOVE, IT’S GOOD.
[CRUCIBLE] IF HE SCORES, HE WASHES THE SOUL OF MY POOR TEAM,
DUST. TODAY IS HIS BIG DAY AND MY BIG DAY TOO!
[VERÔNICA] OH, Wow, TYPHOON, TYPHOON...
[CRUCCILE] WHAT IS IT, DAUGHTER?
[DÉBORA] I ACCIDENTALLY BROKEN THE TOY
WHAT YOU DID TO ME.
[CRUCILE] AH, DADDY FIXES IT, THERE'S NO PROBLEM, SEE?
[VERÔNICA] OH, NO, NO, NO, DADDY WILL JUST FIX IT
IF YOU EAT FRUIT AND VEGETABLES FOR LUNCH, HUH?
[DÉBORA] I DON'T WANT TO EAT FRUIT AND VEGETABLES,
I JUST WANT FRIES.
[VERÔNICA] YOU WANT TO GET FAT, RIGHT?
[CRUCILE] FRIES? THEN DADDY WILL STOP BREATHING
AND EXPLODE HERE, IN FRONT OF YOU, WANT TO SEE? [INSPIRATION]
[DÉBORA] NO, DADDY! NO, DADDY! DADDY, I'M NOT GOING TO...
DADDY, I'M GOING TO, I'M GOING TO EAT VEGETABLES FOR LUNCH, I SWEAR!
[VERÔNICA] NO, NO, HOLY SHIT, DEBINHA, IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GO
FOR SWIMMING, COME ON. MARLENE, LOVE,
TAKE HER TO ME, LOVE, TAKE IT? THANKS.
[CRUCCILE] GOOD, I'LL HAVE TO GO TOO, BECAUSE
I'LL HAVE TO GO TO SÃO PAULO BEFORE THE MEETING, OK?
[VERÔNICA] WHAT DO YOU MEAN FOR SÃO PAULO, CADINHO?
[CRUCKLE] TO SÃO PAULO, LOVE, IT'S LIKE THIS, I'VE ALREADY TOLD YOU THAT...
[VERÔNICA] CRUCIBLE, CRUCIBLE,
WHAT TO DO IN SÃO PAULO AGAIN?
YOU'VE ALREADY SPENT HALF OF THE WEEK IN SÃO PAULO FOR MONTHS.
[CRUCCILE] SEE, MY LOVE, I ALREADY EXPLAINED THIS TO YOU
MORE THAN A THOUSAND TIMES!
MY MOST IMPORTANT CUSTOMERS ARE THERE,
I NEED TO TALK TO EVERYONE, ONE BY ONE,
ABOUT THE SALE OF THE BROKERAGE, UNDERSTAND? AND THAT. [LAUGHS]
[VERÔNICA] WHAT SUIT IS THAT?
[CUCTION] DID YOU LIKE IT? I BOUGHT IT IN SÃO PAULO.
[VERÔNICA] KILL YOURSELF, RIGHT, LOVE? HORRIBLE,
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU INSIST ON BUYING CLOTHES ALONE.
[CRUCCILE] I LIKE IT.
[VERÔNICA] USED TO HATE IT.
[CRUCCILE] PEOPLE CHANGE.
[VERÔNICA] IN YOUR CASE, FOR WORSE, RIGHT, CRUCIBLE?
YOU DON'T HAVE TASTE IN DRESSING.
TAKE OFF THAT TIE, COME ON.
SINCE YOU INSIST ON GOING IN THAT LAWYER SUIT
FROM JAIL DOOR,
AT LEAST PUT THAT TIE HERE,
THAT I BOUGHT FOR YOU, O. BEAUTIFUL TO GIVE YOU LUCK.
HE COMES. [LAUGHTER] HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT WHERE WE'RE GOING TO CELEBRATE LATER?
[CRUCCILE] NOW, AT GINO AND GINA, I HAVE ALREADY RESERVED A TABLE
FOR US, SEE?
[CUCIDHO] GO HOME NUMBER TWO, BARRETO.
NO, WAIT, LET'S GO TO A FLORIST BEFORE.
[CRUCCILE] HI!
[NOÊMIA] [SCREAM] WHAT A SCALE! THERE!
[CRUCIBLE] LILIES FOR A REAL FLOWER.
[NOÊMIA] OH, HOW BEAUTIFUL, DUDU!
[CUCTION] I MISS YOU, LOVE!
[KISSING CRACKS]
[BEATS]
[NOÊMIA] YOU TOOK TOO LONG! I WAITING FOR YOU FOR LUNCH,
DUDU! I ALREADY KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO SAY.
[CRUCCILE] WHAT? [NOÊMIA] THE FLIGHT WAS DELAYED.
[CADINHO] EXACTLY, THIS AIR BRIDGE TO SÃO PAULO...
[NOÊMIA] IT'S GETTING WORSE EVERY DAY, I ALREADY KNOW.
YOU PRACTICALLY LIVE IN SÃO PAULO.
[CRUCCILE] MY LOVE, BUT...
[NOÊMIA] BUT LEAVE IT... LEAVE IT, LEAVE IT I DON'T WANT TO BANK
THAT BORING WIFE, THAT NEEDY WIFE
THAT KEEP CHARGING YOU.
[CRUCIBLE] THIS, THIS, YOU... YOU ARE NOT THAT WOMAN,
EXACTLY. THAT'S WHY YOU ARE SO SPECIAL, UNDERSTAND?
[KISSING CRACKS]
[NOÊMIA] WHAT A TERRIBLE TIE, DUDU! PRACTICALLY DESTROYS THIS
BEAUTIFUL SUIT I GAVE YOU! DID YOU GET THIS TIE FROM SOMEONE?
[CRUCKLE] I BOUGHT IT IN SÃO PAULO.
[NOÊMIA] IT SHOULDN'T BE, YOU'RE NOT GOOD FOR THAT.
I'LL DRESS YOU, DUDU.
[CRUCCILE] AH, BUT LIKE IS NOT DISCUSSABLE.
[NOÊMIA] NO, THERE IS, YES, IT CAN BE DISCUSSED!
HAVE NOT YOU LEARNED YET? AND LOOK AT ME LATELY
BATTLING... CIDA! TO GIVE A LITTLE SENSITIVITY,
OF CULTURE, OF REFINEMENT FOR THIS IGNARO CAPITALIST
WHO I MARRIED.
[CRUCCILE] LOOK, I KNOW YOU TEACH ME A LOT OF THINGS, YOU KNOW?
I KNOW, BUT ONE POINT YOU HAVE TO AGREE WITH ME,
YOUR CULTURE, YOUR REFINEMENT, IS OF NO USE WITHOUT MY MONEY.
NO, I KNOW, I KNOW, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO CALL ME?
OF ARGENTÁRIO. [NOÊMIA] ARGENTÁRIO!
[CRUCIBLE] THAT, CALLS ME AN ARGENTARY.
[NOÊMIA] THINKS THAT MONEY IS EVERYTHING, BECAUSE, FOR HER GOVERNMENT,
THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE WITHOUT MONEY AND THAT IS VERY ELEGANT!
[TOMÁS] ATTENTION, ASTRONAUTS OF INTERGALACTIC SPACE!
THE COSMIC MEGAPOWER SPACESHIP HAS JUST PENETRATED
IN YOUR CONSTELLATION. SURRENDER OR YOU WILL BE DISINTEGRATED!
[NOÊMIA] TOMÁS, SPEAK DIRECTLY TO YOUR FATHER.
[CRUCIBLE] BUT WHAT THE MEGAPODER SPACECRAFT DOESN'T KNOW IS THAT
THE SPACE GIANT ADAMASTOR LIVES IN THIS CONSTELLATION! [LAUGHS]
[TOMÁS] LET'S LAUNCH OUR RAYS AT THE GIANT ADAMASTOR
AND VAPORIZE IT!
[MOANS]
[NOÊMIA] [LAUGHTER]
[PAPER HANDLING]
[GENÉSIO] RIGHT, 54 THOUSAND REAIS. IT'S THERE.
[MAN] NOW YOU INITIAL AND SIGN THE LAST SHEET,
PLEASE.
[GENÉSIO] THIS IS THIS ONE, RIGHT?
[MAN] YES.
[GENÉSIO] YES. HERE. HERE?
[MAN] THANK YOU, CONGRATULATIONS EVERYONE, SEE?
[GENÉSIO] THAT'S IT. ALL THE BEST TO YOU AND THE LORD, SEE?
MAY YOU BE HAPPY AT THE HOUSE, THAT'S WHAT I WISH.
[MAN] YOU DON'T WANT TO DEPOSIT?
[GENÉSIO] NO, I'LL TAKE IT WITH ME.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] NO! TRAMP! TRAMP! CATCH IT, CATCH IT!
CATCH THE TRAMP.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] OH! PLEASE, HAVE YOU SEEN THE SIGN?
DIDN'T YOU SEE IT, RIGHT? PEOPLE, THERE IS NO...
[URBAN ENVIRONMENT]
♪MÚSICA DRAMÁTICA♪
LOOK, I SAW EVERYTHING FROM HERE. IT SEEMS AS LIKE THE LORD KNEW THAT
I WAS GOING TO BE ASSAULTED, I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU WANT ME TO CALL THE POLICE?
[GENÉSIO] NO, YOU CAN LEAVE IT. WHERE IS THE MONEY?
WHERE IS THE MONEY?
[PAPER HANDLING]
[MAN] YOU BE VERY CAREFUL, SEE.
[GENÉSIO] YOU CAN LEAVE IT. NOW I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MAN] GIVE THE BAG THERE QUICKLY. GIVE, GIVE, GIVE.
[MAN] WHAT A CRAZY THING IS...
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MAN] ANSWER, ANSWER, ANSWER, ANSWER. HELLO, MAX,
IT'S ME, CUMPADI. BROTHER, THERE IS NO MONEY IN THE BACKPACK.
NOTHING, NOTHING. IT'S A TRAM, TAKE CARE.
MAX, THEY SET YOU UP, BROTHER.
♪MÚSICA DRAMÁTICA♪
[CARMINHA] OH, GENÉSIO, YOU ALMOST SCARED ME TO KILL.
WHY THAT FACE? YOU LOOK LIKE A ZOMBIE.
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME ROCK WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY RHYTHM♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NOITE♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU GET TIRED♪
♪STIR AND REMOVE♪
♪SCALES THAT'S CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COMES TO MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAY STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MOVE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪SCALES THAT'S CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COMES TO MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAY STILL♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[GENÉSIO] I WAS robbed, THEY STOLE ALL OUR MONEY!
[CARMINHA] I CAN'T BELIEVE IT! OH, GENESIO, IT’S NOT POSSIBLE.
[GENÉSIO] IT IS THE PURE TRUTH.
[CARMINHA] OH MY GOD IN HEAVEN, THEY DID SOMETHING TO YOU,
MY LOVE, DID THEY HURT YOU?
[GENÉSIO] YOU HAD HURT ME BEFORE.
I WOULD RATHER HAVE LOST A HAND THAN MY DAUGHTER'S INHERITANCE.
[CARMINHA] BUT TELL ME, HOW WAS IT, MY GOD?
[GENÉSIO] A BIKER. [CARMINHA] HUH?
[GENÉSIO] HE PASSED BY AND TOOK THE BAG OUT OF MY HAND.
[CARMINHA] SOMEONE WARNED YOU WERE GOING TO LEAVE
FROM THE BANK WITH THE MONEY.
[GENÉSIO] YES, SOMEONE WARNED.
[CARMINHA] USED TO BE SOMEONE FROM THE BANK,
SOMEONE INFILTRATED THERE. OH MY GOD...
AND DID YOU CALL THE POLICE?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] IT'S NO USE.
[CARMINHA] IT’S NO USE.
OH MY GOD.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] I'M AN IDIOT, AREN'T I, CARMINHA? HE CAN TALK.
NO, SPEAK, SPEAK. AN IDIOT, A DOWNLOAD, A BEAST. A FOOL
WHO LOST EVERYTHING HE HAD IN SUCH AN IMBECIAL WAY. GO...
[CARMINHA] NO, MY LOVE. HOW COULD YOU IMAGINE
THAT SOMETHING LIKE THIS WOULD HAPPEN. MY LOVE.
[KISSING CLAP]
[CARMINHA] NO...
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] LOOK AT ME.
[CARMINHA] HUH? [GENÉSIO] LOOK.
[GENÉSIO] TELL ME HOW A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN LIKE YOU...
[GENÉSIO] BEAUTIFUL...
[GENÉSIO] HOW CAN YOU WANT SOMETHING A... A...
[GENÉSIO] WITH A MAN LIKE ME? OLD, UGLY, BLACK,
WITHOUT MONEY. NOW, THEN, WITHOUT...WITHOUT ANY MONEY.
HOW CAN YOU WANT... SOMETHING... NO.
OK, TELL ME. IT TELLS ME.
[CARMINHA] LOVE, WHAT IS THIS? YOU ARE A WONDERFUL MAN.
DON'T TALK LIKE THAT. YOU ARE A HUSBAND. I IMAGINE THAT
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU CAUSED YOU A BLOW.
BUT NOT. WE HAVE NO WHY TO WORRY.
STAY CALM, LOVE. WE DON'T NEED TO WARM THEIR HEADS.
DO YOU WORK. LOOK, I NEED IT TOO...
I NEED TO GET A JOB.
I'M GOING TO GET A JOB TOO.
THERE WILL BE NO MISSING FOOD IN OUR HOUSE, OKAY?
I GUARANTEE. I GUARANTEE, MY LOVE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[DOOR OPEN]
[DOOR CLOSE]
[GENÉSIO] GO TO THE ROOM. I WANT TO HAVE A SERIOUS CONVERSATION WITH YOU.
[CARMINHA] LEAVE HER...
[GENÉSIO] TO THE ROOM! I'LL TALK TO YOU THERE.
SHE CANNOT DO WHAT SHE DID TO YOU.
I HAVE TO GIVE HER A SERIOUS SCORE.
[CARMINHA] NO, LOVE. LEAVE IT THERE. STAY HERE.
RELAX. LET'S TALK...
[GENÉSIO] I HAVE TO DO THIS. I REALLY HAVE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] [THROAT CLEAR]
[GENÉSIO] [WHISPERING] DAUGHTER.
[RITA] I SWEAR I SAW... I SWEAR I SAW.
[GENÉSIO] I KNOW YOU SEE IT. AND WHAT YOU SAW IS ALL TRUE.
I KNOW. EVERYTHING YOU SAID IS TRUE, MY DAUGHTER.
YOU SAVED YOUR FATHER, YOU SAVED US.
[RITA] DID THEY STOLEN THE LORD, FATHER?
[GENÉSIO] NO... NO... NO. [EXTENDED] "XIU."
THEY DID NOT STOLE. THE MONEY IS WITH ME. I LIED TO CARMINHA.
SHE THINKS I WAS ROBBED, AND I WANT
MAY SHE BELIEVE THIS. IT'S IMPORTANT FOR SHE TO BELIEVE IN THIS,
DAUGHTER. NOW PAY ATTENTION. YOU... YOU'RE GOING TO STAY IN THIS ROOM.
DO NOT OPEN THE DOOR. I'M GOING TO GIVE CARMINHA A WAY, DAUGHTER.
[RITA] WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO, FATHER?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
[GENÉSIO] [WHISPERING] YOU WILL NEVER SEE THIS WOMAN AGAIN.
LEAVE IT TO ME, DAUGHTER. TODAY SHE'S LEAVING THIS HOUSE.
NOW, PAY ATTENTION TO ANOTHER THING WHICH IS THE
MOST IMPORTANTLY, THE MONEY IS WITH ME AND I LEFT IT HIDDEN
IN A BLACK PLASTIC BAG IN THE KITCHEN CABINET.
THAT CLOSET WHEN YOU ENTER THE YARD, IN THAT...
ON THE RIGHT, LIKE THIS, BEHIND SOME CANS. IT'S HIDING THERE,
ARE YOU GOOD, MY DAUGHTER? WHEN I LEAVE,
YOU WILL NOT OPEN THE DOOR TO ANYONE.
FOR NOBODY, MY DAUGHTER. OH, MY BELOVED DAUGHTER, I LOVE YOU.
YOU ARE MY GUARDIAN ANGEL, DAUGHTER. MY GUARDIAN ANGEL.
[KISSING CLAP]
[GENÉSIO] DAUGHTER OF HEAVEN...
[CLÉBER] DECISION NIGHT AT MARACANÃ. FULL HOUSE.
LET'S MEET THE CARIOCA CHAMPION OF 99. FLAMENGO FACES
THE REAL CROSS. FLAMENGO NEEDS A VICTORY. HAS THE SUPPORT OF
GUYS AND THERE IS A BRAZILIAN FOOTBALL STAR ON THE FIELD,
TYPHOON. COME TO TRY TO TAKE FLAMENGO TO ANOTHER CONQUEST
OF TITLE. FOR ANOTHER OLYMPIC ROUND. AND THERE IS NO DOUBT THAT
THE PRESENCE OF THE TYPHOON MAKES FLAMENGO FANS
TRUST MUCH MORE IN THE POSSIBILITY OF VICTORY,
DESPITE THE DRAWING BEING THE OPPONENT'S.
♪OUVIRAM DO IPIRANGA♪
♪TO ​​THE PLACID BANKS♪
♪OF A HEROIC PEOPLE♪
♪O THE CHIN OF THE RETUMBANTE♪
[MONALISA] RED CARD.
[OLENKA] OH, WHAT THAT!
[SPEAKING]
[MONALISA] DID YOU SEE WHAT THEY DID TO THE POOR GUY?
I JUST WANT TO SEE WHAT THIS JUDGE IS GOING TO DO NOW. THERE...
[MOLLED] THE CLOWN. THIS IS A CLOWN. WHAT?
THIS JUDGE IS BOUGHT, HUH. THIS JUDGE IS BOUGHT.
HOW MUCH ARE YOU EARNING, YOU CLOWN?
[OLENKA] HERE. ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
[MONALISA] OH MY DAUGHTER, A PROMISE IS A PROMISE.
IF TYFÃO SCORES A GOAL AT THE END OF THE CHAMPIONSHIP,
I CUT MY WHOLE Ponytail.
[WHISTLE]
[MONALISA] OH, MY FATHER. I CAN'T SEE THESE THINGS, NO.
I GET NERVOUS. I'M FEELING SICK.
[CRUCILE] GO, TYPHOON. COME ON, HEY, TYPHOON.
FOR THE DIVINE, MAN, FOR THE DIVINE!
[JIMMY] WHAT IS THIS, BOSS?
[CUCIDHO] IT'S THE DECISION OF THE CARIOCA CHAMPIONSHIP, SHIT.
TYPHOON ON THE LAWN, JIMMY!
IF HE SCORES A GOAL, HE IS CONSECRATED
AND IT STILL WASHES THE SOUL OF MY DIVINE FOOTBALL CLUB.
EVEN THOUGH HE DOESN'T PLAY THERE ANYMORE, HE CAME FROM THERE, DAMN IT!
[JIMMY] MAYBE IT WOULD BE GOOD TO REFRESH YOUR MEMORY,
BUT HERE AT THE FIRM THERE IS ALSO A CHAMPIONSHIP DECISION.
THE EXECUTIVES OF THE SPANISH BANK
THOSE WHO WANT TO BUY FROM US HAVE ALREADY ARRIVED.
[CUCCILE] I KNOW, I KNOW, CALM DOWN,
CALM CALM. IT'S IN GOD'S HANDS.
TWENTY MILLION. TWENTY MILLION, TWENTY MILLION,
TWENTY MILLION, TWENTY MILLION...
[TV IN THE BACKGROUND]
[CRUCKLE] AH, ARE YOU BORING THE TV? SORRY, I'LL GO DOWN
THE VOLUME. DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS? IS THAT TODAY IS THE CHAMPIONSHIP DECISION
CARIOCA AND THAT IS... IT IS VERY, VERY IMPORTANT TO ME.
[MAN] "NO, DON'T WORRY."
AS "YOU" KNOW, "OUR" BANK "HAS"
INTEREST IN BUYING "SU" BROKER.
[CRUCCILE] "SI, SI." BUT HONESTLY, "YO NO"
I WASN'T EVEN THINKING ABOUT SELLING. THIS BROKER "ES MI" LIFE,
"YOU UNDERSTAND?" BUT YOU NEVER KNOW, NÉ, "I AM" ALL OUVIDOS.
WHO KNOWS "YO CHANGE" OF IDEA.
[MAN] "Y USTED HA PIENSADO" IN ANY AMOUNT?
[CRUCILE] "NO, NO. USTEDES" DID YOU THINK OF ANY VALUE?
NO, BECAUSE... OH NO, IT WAS A MISS, DAMN IT. IT WAS A FAULT, YOUR JUDGE!
YOUR JUDGE, IT WAS A FAULT. I'M GOING TO KILL THIS JUDGE!
THIS JUDGE IS REALLY A THIEF, YOU BOY, YOU NAUGHTER!
[CLÉBER] LEAL CRUZ PRO ATTACK. WITH GUILHERME'S BALL
PRO DEJA. RETURN TO GUILHERME AND THE BID IS DANGEROUS.
MAKE THE CROSSING. LET GO, JEDIEL,
[EXTENDED] GOAL!
[OLENKA] WHAT IS THIS?
[MONALISA] I... I CAN'T BELIEVE IT, OH MY JE...
OH MY LADY OF THE ROSARY,
TYFÃO HAS TO CHANGE THIS GAME!
[OLENKA] IH, YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE THE BID THERE.
[MONALISA] OH MY GOD, I CAN'T STAND WATCHING.
[CARMINHA] COFFEE, LOVE?
ARE YOU SURE YOU DON’T WANT ME TO MAKE NOODLES?
[GENÉSIO] OH, NO, I WANT NOTHING. I COMPLETELY LOST MY HUNGRY.
[PHONE RING]
[CARMINHA] HUM, MY GOD, WHO HAS THE COURAGE
TO CALL IN THE MIDDLE OF THE CHAMPIONSHIP DECISION?
[GENÉSIO] ANSWER, HUH.
[PHONE RING]
[CARMINHA] HELLO?
[MAX] FINALLY, RIGHT, CRAZY!
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN, SINCE I HAVE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU ALL NIGHT?
[CARMINHA] AH, AUNT HÉLIDA, HOW LONG!
OH, AUNT, YES, I COULDN'T REPLY TO YOUR LETTER,
BECAUSE I'M VERY BUSY, I'M SORRY.
[MAX] [STUMBLING] OK, I'VE GOT IT, I'VE GOT IT.
CAN WE MEET IN 20 MINUTES, AT LAJE DO JACIR?
[CARMINHA] YES, OF COURSE. I SEND YOU THE LETTERS THAT GRANDMA WROTE
FOR GRANDPA. I SEND YES. NEXT WEEK, WITHOUT FAIL.
OH AUNT, I'M SORRY BUT I'LL HAVE TO HANG UP NOW,
BECAUSE I HAD MY FOOT IN THE DOOR.
OK. KISS, AUNT.
[PHONE ON HOOK]
[CARMINHA] IT COULD ONLY BE AUNT HÉLIDA'S SUITCASE.
[TV IN THE BACKGROUND]
[CLÉBER] FLAMENGO GOES AGAIN.
HAVE YOU ALREADY LOOKED AT THE MOVEMENT OF THE TYPHOON,
HE LET IT GO, MADE THE TABLE WITH ADEILSON. IT HIT...
ON THE BEAM! FLAMENGO ASKS FOR THE GOAL, THE JUDGE LOOKS AT THE FLAG,
STAY IN DOUBT.
HARD BID! GIVES THE IMPRESSION...
[MONALISA] AH, THE BALL IS IN!
[OLENKA] WHAT IS THIS, BROTHER? WHAT IT IS?
[MONALISA] THE BALL IN. THE BALL IN! BURGLAR! BURGLAR!
[DIÓGENES] GO MY SON! DON’T BE DISCOURAGED, LOOK AT THE BREED!
[TOGETHER] TYPHOON! TYPHOON! TYPHOON! TYPHOON!
[MAN] "USTED" ASKED US FOR A NUMBER.
WE HAVE REACHED THIS NUMBER.
WE OFFER YOU
25 "MILHONES".
[CASH REGISTER]
[CRUCCILE] SORRY, BUT, ON THESE BASES,
I CANNOT EVEN START TALKING. [LAUGHS]
[MAN] ON WHAT BASIS "USTED"
WOULD YOU FEEL “COMFORTABLE” TALKING?
[CRUCIBLE] 40 MILLION. NOT ONE CENT LESS.
[MAN] IT'S WAY MORE THAN IT'S WORTH.
BUT, TO US, IT IS INTERESTING.
DONE DEAL.
[CRUCCILE] CLOSED! VERY GOOD VERY GOOD. TOMORROW THEN...
[MAN] CONGRATULATIONS. [CRUCCILE] THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE WILL CONTACT YOU TO DEFINE THE LATEST DETAILS...
"CHEERS, THANK YOU. SEE YOU LATER"
[JIMMY] "YES, SEE YOU LATER, BEUNÍSSIMO,
YES... THANK YOU, THANK YOU." TCHAU.
[LAUGHTER]
[CUCCIFIER] I'M RICH, A MILLIONAIRE.
I'M A MILLIONAIRE, IT'S GOAL, GOAL!
[JIMMY] I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU ASKED FOR 40.
[CRUCIBLE] WELL, IT'S BECAUSE I AM ME AND YOU ARE YOU,
JIMMY. I FEEL THINGS IN THE AIR, UNDERSTAND?
THIS IS WHAT DIFFERENTS A CRAZY PLAYER FROM A COMMON PLAYER, LIKE YOU,
DID YOU UNDERSTAND? DID I OR DIDN'T I SCORED A GOAL, HUH? AH!
[JIMMY] "BECAUSE I FEEL THINGS IN THE AIR."
[CRUCCILE] NOW IT'S UP TO YOU, TYPHOON. NOW IT'S UP TO YOU,
COME ON, DON’T LET THE PETECA DROP. COME ON, TODAY...
TODAY IS OUR BIG DAY, TYPHOON!
[CLÉBER] FULL STADIUM, ONE, ZERO FOR REAL CRUZ.
EVERYONE WAITING FOR THE BIG TYPHOON. THEN SERGINHO,
TOUCHED HIM, IN THE CHEST. BIG HAT! GO INSIDE THE AREA.
DRIBLED THE FIRST, LOOK AT THE GOAL! [EXTENDED] GOAL!
[SCREAMS OF CELEBRATION]
[MONALISA] LOOK, HE'S TALKING! LOOK, AH... LOOK,
YOU'RE SAYING YOU LOVE ME, OLENKA!
[TYPHOON] [SHOUTING] MONALISA!
[MONALISA] I LOVE YOU TOO! I LOVE YOU TOO!
[KISSING CLAP]
[MONALISA] MY LOVE, MY BEAUTIFUL! MY GORGEOUS GUY!
[CRYING] HE'S THE MAN OF MY LIFE, OLENKA!
[OLENKA] I KNOW!
[WANTED]
[MONALISA] COME ON, I'M READY FOR THE SACRIFICE.
[OLENKA] JURA?
[CARMINHA] A WANT TO HAVE A BEER.
I'M GOING TO THE BAKERY TO BUY. DO YOU WANT ME TO BRING YOU SOMETHING?
[GENÉSIO] NO. I WANT NOTHING, NO.
[CARMINHA] OK, I'LL BE BACK, OK? [GENÉSIO] OK.
[TV IN THE BACKGROUND]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] RITA! RITA! RITA, DAUGHTER! PAY ATTENTION TO THE FATHER,
DON'T FORGET: YOU CLOSE EVERYTHING HERE, DON'T OPEN THE DOOR
FOR NOBODY, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD! REMEMBER?
THE MONEY IS IN THAT BLACK BAG I TOLD YOU ABOUT,
THERE IN THE KITCHEN CABINET. YOU UNDERSTAND EVERYTHING, RIGHT?
DON'T OPEN THE DOOR TO ANYONE, FATHER'S COMING BACK.
[RITA] DAD. [GENÉSIO] FATHER IS COMING BACK!
[RITA] DAD, IT MUST BE DANGEROUS, DAD.
[GENÉSIO] LOCK EVERYTHING THERE, DAUGHTER! [RITA] NO, DADDY! FATHER!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] MAX!
[MAX] COME HERE, HOW DO YOU GET ME ONE OF THESE, CARMINHA?
[CARMINHA] WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
[MAX] THERE WAS ONLY SHREDDED PAPER INSIDE THAT BAG.
[CARMINHA] I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT. THE GENESIUM
WAS STOLEN. MAX, I DON'T LIKE THIS CONVERSATION AT ALL!
[MAX] I AM NOT ENJOYING THIS CONVERSATION AT ALL.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] YOUR PARTNER GOT YOU BACK, MAN!
[MAX] THAT "MY PARTNER TURNED ME AROUND", DON'T TRAVEL, SHIT! YOU ALREADY
I SAID THAT THIS PARTNER OF MINE IS TRUSTED, HE IS MY BROTHER.
[CARMINHA] YOU AND YOUR BROTHER, YOUR TRUSTED PARTNER!
IT'S NOT THE FIRST TIME YOU'VE FAILED! NOW IT WAS MY MISTAKE,
THAT I TRUSTED IN A NAIL YOU MADE!
[MAX] COME HERE, ARE YOU GOING TO OFFEND ME NOW? THIS IS ONLY MISSING,
CARMINHA, DON’T TRAVEL, NO, SHIT. WANT TO KNOW WHAT I THINK?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK? I THINK GENESIUM IS GIVING YOU
ONE TURN BACK, THE GENÉSIO WHO IS GETTING OVER YOU.
[CARMINHA] GENÉSIO DOESN’T EVEN PIT UP HIS TENT AT HOME.
THAT ANTA DOESN'T HAVE THE INTELLIGENCE FOR THIS.
THEY TOOK THE MONEY, MAX, I TELL YOU!
AND IF IT WASN'T YOUR PARTNER WHO SET IT UP...
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] SEE YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S TAKING ME A TRIP.
[MAX] CARMINHA... HEY, CARMINHA, PAY ATTENTION. LOOK AT ME,
LOOK WHO YOU'RE TALKING TO, IT'S ME, MAX, UNDERSTAND?
IT'S ME, I'M YOUR MAN, I'M YOUR BROTHER, UNDERSTAND? DID YOU UNDERSTAND?
[CARMINHA] I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ELSE, MAN. I DO NOT KNOW ANYTHING ELSE.
I KNOW THE MONEY IS MISSING. WAS THAT, MAX, THE MONEY MISSED?
[MAX] Yeah. AND DO YOU THINK IF I HAD ARMED UP
FROM YOU, I WOULD BE HERE, CRAZY? OF COURSE,
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN LEAKED A LONG TIME AGO, NOW.
WANT TO KNOW SOMETHING? I'M LEAVING.
[CARMINHA] DON'T GO LEAVE, MAX! DON'T LEAVE ME HERE ALONE.
[MAX] I'LL LEAVE YOU ALONE, BECAUSE YOU'RE WITH
THE HEAD IS TOO HOT FOR MY LIKE. WHEN IT GETS COOL,
YOU CALL ME, OK?
[CARMINHA] MAX! MAX!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] IT'S SAD TO SEE YOU NERVOUS, LOVE.
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] YOU TREATED YOUR BOYFRIEND VERY BAD,
HE UNFAIRLY OFFENDED HIM, BECAUSE HE WAS RIGHT WHEN HE SAID THAT
I ARMED YOU!
BY THE WAY THIS DOWNLOAD IS NOT THAT DUMB, NO, RIGHT?
[CARMINHA] STAY AWAY FROM ME, YOU OLD MAN!
[GENÉSIO] WHAT IS IT? DID YOU SAY "OLD"?
[CARMINHA] OLD MAN. [GENESIUM] OLD?
[CARMINHA] OLD MAN!
[GENÉSIO] I THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING TO MAKE A THEATRINE THERE, TALK...
INVENTING THAT "NO, LOVE, YOU DIDN'T LISTEN RIGHT!"
[CARMINHA] IT WAS HER, WASN’T IT? IT WAS YOUR DAUGHTER'S PLAGUE...
[GENÉSIO] WASH YOUR MOUTH, WASH YOUR MOUTH! TO TALK ABOUT MYSELF
DAUGHTER GO WASH YOUR MOUTH! [CARMINHA] YOU KNEW.
[GENÉSIO] RITINHA IS MINE... SHE IS MY GUARDIAN ANGEL,
MY GUARDIAN ANGEL.
[CARMINHA] YOU ARE TOO DUMB TO HAVE THIS LETTER. [LAUGHS]
[GENÉSIO] DO YOU KNOW WHAT I AM? [CARMINHA] HUM?
[GENÉSIO] I'M HAPPY TO KNOW THAT YOU'LL NEVER ARRIVE AGAIN
NEAR MY DAUGHTER! YOU WILL NEVER STEP YOUR FEET AGAIN
IN THAT HOUSE, YOU WILL GO BACK TO THE GUTTER FROM WHERE I TOOK YOU,
YOU DISGRACED SLUT! ILL THANKFUL! YOU STAY HERE!
[CARMINHA] LEAVE ME! [GENÉSIO] STAY HERE!
STAY AND LOOK AT ME! LOOK AT ME!
HOW DID YOU HAVE THE COURAGE TO DO THIS TO ME?
[CARMINHA] [LAUGHS]
[GENÉSIO] SPEAK! [CARMINHA] YOU REALLY ARE A DOWNLOAD,
HUH? IT'S REALLY A LOT TO BELIEVE THAT A WOMAN
I'M GOING TO WANT TO SPEND MY LIFE LOOKING AT YOUR FACE
AS A MONKEY, LISTENING TO YOUR MAMMOTH SNORING,
FEELING THAT OLD SMELL OF YOURS!
LISTENING TO THIS IDIOT CONVERSATION!
[GENÉSIO] DON’T WORRY, FROM NOW ON YOU WILL HAVE CONVERSATIONS
MUCH MORE INTERESTING WITH THE WOMEN IN THE PENITENTIARY,
WHEN I REPORT YOU TO...
[HIT IMPACT]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] YOU BITCH, COME HERE! COME HERE!
[CARMINHA] LEAVE ME! [GENÉSIO] YOU'RE GOING TO RUN AWAY FROM ME, NO!
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO RUN AWAY FROM ME, NO. I'M TALKING... AH!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[THUNDER]
[STEPS]
[GENÉSIO] OH MY GOD, YOU BITCH!
BITCH, I'LL PUT YOU IN JAIL, YOU...
[CARMINHA] GO TO HELL.
[GENÉSIO] AH!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] CADE... GO TO JAIL! OH! MY HEAD...
[CLÉBER] 44 MINUTES. IT RAINS AND IT RAINS A LOT IN MARACANÃ.
ONE BY ONE ON THE SCOREBOARD, THE TITLE GOES TO REAL CRUZ. BEAUTIFUL KILLING OF THE TYPHOON.
BIG HALF MOON! GO TO THE MARKING.
GET CLOSE TO THE AREA, HARD FOUL!
[MONALISA] MISSING! IT'S A MISS! OH, MY LADY, THE LADY
YOU CANNOT ABANDON ME NOW. OH MY FATHER!
[PANTING] OLENKA, NOW, IT'S GOING TO BE A GOAL!
[OLENKA] EAT, WATER.
[MONALISA] YOU'RE GOING TO SCORE A GOAL!
[DIOGENES] GOD IS A FATHER! HE'S GOING TO SCORE, HE'S GOING TO SCORE, HE'S GOING.
[THUNDER]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[WHISTLE]
[SCREAMS OF CELEBRATION]
[OLENKA] IS CHAMPION! HE'S A CHAMPION! HE'S A CHAMPION!
[TOGETHER] HE’S A CHAMPION! HE'S A CHAMPION!
HE'S A CHAMPION! HE'S A CHAMPION!
HE'S A CHAMPION!
[CRUCCILE] JIMMY! JIMMY, IT'S A LOT OF EMOTION TONIGHT, JIMMY,
GIVE ME A HUG! COME ON, LET'S FILL UP, JIMMY.
[JIMMY] NO, NO, I'M ALREADY DRINKING, THANK YOU. IT'S GREAT!
♪ESSA FESTA IS LEGAL♪
♪TÁ LEGAL♪
[CUCCILE] GOOD, GUYS, LOOK, THE PARTY IS VERY GOOD,
BUT I NEED TO FIND MY FAMILY NOW.
WHERE'S MY CELL PHONE, MAN? JIMMY, JIMMY, JIMMY.
COME HERE, JIMMY, JIMMY, CALL... CALL MY WIFE,
TELL ME I'LL MEET HER IN HALF AN HOUR
IN "GINO AND GINA", ARE YOU GOOD, MAN?
[JIMMY] SORRY, BUT WHICH WOMAN?
[CRUCICILE] VERONICA, OF COURSE!
♪THE FESTA IS LEGAL♪
♪ESSA FESTA IS LEGAL♪
[JIMMY] CRUCIBLE! CRUCIBLE, LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
I'M HAVING A DIFFICULTY... TO SAY THIS TO YOU,
BUT I NEED TO SAY. ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT GIVING ME SOME BONUS
SPECIAL FOR THE SALE OF THE COMPANY?
[CUCICULATE] THINK THE SPECIAL BONUS IS FOR YOU TO CONTINUE
EARNING THE SAME THING YOU WILL EARN IN MY NEW FIRM!
I COULD LEAVE YOU BEHIND, THE SPANISH WOULD PUT YOU IN THE TRASH,
BUT SINCE I'M A COOL GUY, I'LL TAKE YOU WITH ME, JIMMY!
LOOK, THINK NOT ABOUT WHAT YOU DIDN’T EARN, BUT WHAT YOU DID
YOU STOP LOST, UNDERSTAND? IT'S COOL...
♪THE FESTA IS LEGAL♪
[JIMMY] YEAH, ROSE. [ROSE] HI.
[JIMMY] THE CRUCIAL SAID TO TELL HIS WIFE TO MEET HIM
AT GINO AND GINA IN 20 MINUTES, OK?
[ROSE] OK, BUT WHICH WOMAN?
[JIMMY] NOÊMIA.
[CELLULAR DIALING]
[JIMMY] HELLO? HI, VERONICA, ARE YOU OK? CRUCIAL IS WITHOUT CELL PHONE,
HE ASKED TO MEET HIM AT GINO AND GINA IN HALF AN HOUR, OK?
[VERÔNICA] OK, GINO AND GINA IN HALF AN HOUR? IT'S OK.
OH, THE CRUCIBLE MUST BE SO HAPPY, RIGHT, JIMMY?
[NOÊMIA] OH, I WAS REALLY TRYING TO TALK TO HIM.
OK, IN AN HOUR AT GINO. OK, I WILL GO. THANKS.
[CARMINHA] IT FUCKED UP, MAX.
[MAX] WHAT'S UP? [CARMINHA] FUCKED UP EVERYTHING.
YOU WERE RIGHT, GENÉSIO SET US UP, HE WAS THERE
ON THE SLAB AND LISTENED TO EVERYTHING WE SAID.
[MAX] I TOLD YOU, I TOLD YOU!
[CARMINHA] [SHOUTING] OKAY, OKAY! YOU WERE REASONABLE!
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO? KNEEL AND APOLOGIZE?
I KNEEL, BUT NOW, WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
[MAX] NOW WE'RE NOT GOING TO DO ANYTHING. PEOPLE HAVE TO LEAVE
OUTSIDE. AT A TIME LIKE THIS, GENÉSIO SHOULD BE TAKING PART
FROM THE PEOPLE AT THE DELEGACY... [CARMINHA] WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT. STOP, LET ME THINK.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] IF I KNOW GENESIO WELL, HE TOOK THE MONEY
GO INSIDE THE HOUSE.
[MAX] HOW ARE YOU SURE OF THAT? HE MAY HAVE DEPOSITED
EVERYTHING IN THE BANK, CRAZY. [CARMINHA] IMAGINE, THE CREATURE IS
PRIMITIVE, DOESN'T LIKE TO PUT A LOT OF MONEY IN THE BANK.
[LAUGHTER] I GIVE MY LITTLE FINGER LIKE THAT OLD MAN GOT MAD
THE MONEY IS INSIDE THE HOUSE AND THE PEST OF THE GIRL KNOWS WHERE IT IS.
WELL I WOULD LIKE TO HAVE ANOTHER CHAT
WITH THAT FREAK. GENÉSIO IS FAIL, THIS TIME SHOULD BE
DRAGING TO THE DELEGACY. IT'S TIME FOR PEOPLE TO ACT, MAX.
LET'S GO HOME NOW! [MAX] NO, CARMINHA, NO.
WE'RE NOT GOING! [CARMINHA] WE'RE ALREADY ARRIVED
SEE YOU HERE, MAN. WE HAD ALL THIS WORK,
ARE WE GOING TO DIE ON THE BEACH?
[LELECO] HEY, I'M NOT GOING TO TALK... BABYNHA, LISTEN TO ME,
I'M NOT GOING TO TALK ON CAMERA? [MURICY] OH MY GOD!
THE REPORTER SAID SHE WANTS TO TALK TO MOM, MY LOVE, TO MOM.
[LELECO] AND, ACTUALLY, IS A MOTHER BETTER THAN A FATHER?
[MURICY] [LAUGHS] OF COURSE IT IS, RIGHT, BABYNHO? SORRY.
[LELECO] BUT...
[IVANA] OH, YOU CAN DO MAKEUP, AND I WILL ALSO APPEAR ON TV.
[MURICY] DAUGHTER, SHE WANTS TO TALK TO HER MOTHER.
[IVANA] GUYS, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING? I'M THE GUY'S SISTER!
[CLÉBER] THE DECISION NIGHT OF THE CARIOCA CHAMPIONSHIP
IT WAS DEFINITELY BY JORGE TUFÃO, THE GUNNER
OF THE COMPETITION HE SCORED TWO GOALS IN THE FINAL AND GUARANTEED THE TITLE
TO FLAMENGO. REPORTER FERNANDA PADILHA IS IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD
DE DIVINO, IN THE SUBURB OF RIO. FRIENDS AND FAMILY WAIT
THE CRACK FOR A PARTY THAT WILL GO ON INTO THE DAWN.
FERNANDA PADILHA.
[FERNANDA] DONA MURICY, IT MUST HAVE BEEN A GREAT EMOTION TO SEE
YOUR SON SHINES TONIGHT.
[LELECO] SPEAK UP, MURICY!
[MURICY] IT'S A LOT OF EMOTION, A LOT OF EMOTION. WE ALL HERE,
WE ARE VERY THRILLED.
WE NEVER IMAGINED SO MUCH EMOTION.
INCLUDING MY SON TYPHOON, BECAUSE HE IS MY SON, RIGHT?
SINCE HE WAS BORN, IN BUT...
[MONALISA] TYPHOON! AND YOU MY LOVE?
[TYPHOON] HI, LOVE! HAVE YOU SEEN THE MOST BEAUTIFUL THING?
I THINK IT'S THE HAPPIEST DAY OF MY LIFE.
[MONALISA] TODAY IS THE HAPPIEST DAY OF MY LIFE TOO.
[TYPHOON] LOVE, NOW... OH, NOW THE MONEY WILL COME IN,
NOW YOU WILL BE ABLE... YOU WILL BE ABLE TO LEAVE THAT ROOM,
DID YOU UNDERSTAND? I WILL MAKE YOU THE HAPPIEST WOMAN IN THE WORLD,
MY LOVE! [MONALISA] I'M WAITING FOR YOU!
UH! [RICE]
♪MÚSICA DRAMÁTICA♪
[GENÉSIO] OH... DISGRACED, DISGRACED.
[GENÉSIO] YOU GO TO CANA, DISGRACED, I'LL CATCH YOU.
YOU GO TO CANA!
♪MÚSICA DRAMÁTICA♪
[GENÉSIO] DISGRACED.
[GENÉSIO] I'LL GET YOU, YOU'RE GOING TO CANA, YOU DISGRACED.
I CATCH YOU...
♪MÚSICA DRAMÁTICA♪
[GENÉSIO] OH! THERE!
♪DEUS ME PROTEJA♪
♪FROM YOUR ENVY♪
♪DEUS ME DEFENDA♪
♪FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪DEUS ME SALVE♪
♪FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
♪DEUS ME AJUDE♪
♪FROM YOUR ANGER♪
♪DEUS ME IMUNIZE♪
♪FROM YOUR POISON♪
[MAN] WAITING FOR SOMEONE ELSE?
[VERÔNICA] I'M WAITING FOR ONE MORE PERSON, THANK YOU.
♪SPARE ME FROM YOUR END♪
[NOÊMIA] THANK YOU.
[MAN] HOW MANY PEOPLE WILL BE?
[NOÊMIA] TWO. ME AND ONE ELSE.
♪DEUS ME LEVANTE♪
♪DEUS WILL FORCE ME♪
♪GOD FORGIVE ME FOR WANTING♪
♪MAY GOD FREE ME♪
♪AND KEEP IT FROM YOURSELF♪
[CUCCILE] GOOD EVENING, MOREIRA.
[MOREIRA] OH! BY THE WAY, THE LORD IS BEING WAITED FOR,
MR CADINHO.
[URBAN ENVIRONMENT]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] THE PLAGUE PUT THE LOCK ON THE DOOR. STRENGTH, MAX.
♪I DISCOVERED THAT I LOVE YOU TOO MUCH♪
♪I DISCOVERED IT IN YOU♪
[GENÉSIO] CARMEN LÚCIA MOREIRA DE SOUSA, YOU'RE GOING TO JAIL!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[GENÉSIO] CARMEN LÚCIA MOREI... DE SOUSA,
YOU'RE GOING TO JAIL!
♪VERDADE♪
♪I DISCOVERED THAT I LOVE YOU TOO MUCH♪
♪I DISCOVERED IT IN YOU♪
♪MINHA PAZ♪
♪DESCOBRI...♪
[IMPACT ON THE CAR BODY]
[CAR BRAKE]
[THUNDER]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] OH MY LORD, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD!
YOU THREW YOURSELF IN FRONT OF MY CAR, MY LORD!
I SWEAR I DIDN'T SEE THE LORD! [GENÉSIO] OH!
[TYPHOON] I'M GOING TO TAKE YOU TO THE HOSPITAL.
[GENÉSIO] IT WON'T... THERE WON'T BE TIME.
[TYPHOON] NO, STOP... NO, YES GO, YES GO! HE IS GOING YES!
[GENÉSIO] I'M DYING. [TYPHOON] NO!
NO, NO, DON'T SAY THAT, DON'T SAY THAT.
[GENÉSIO] [PANTING] LISTEN! [TYPHOON] I HEAR.
LISTEN, LISTEN, LISTEN.
[GENÉSIO] [GRUNTING] FOR THE SAKE OF GOD.
♪MÚSICA DRAMÁTICA♪
[GENÉSIO] MY WIFE... MY WIFE,
CARMEN LÚCIA MOREIRA DE SOUZA...
[TYPHOON] YES, YOUR... YOUR...
[GENÉSIO] MY WIFE CARMEN LÚCIA...
[TYPHOON] THE LORD WANTS ME TO SAY SOMETHING
FOR YOUR WIFE? CARMEN LÚCIA MOREIRA DE SOUZA.
I WILL... I WILL TAKE CARE OF HER, I WILL PROTECT HER.
I PROMISE I WILL TAKE CARE OF YOUR WIFE, COME WITH ME.
I CARE, I HAVE MONEY, I HAVE A LOT OF MONEY.
I PROMISE I WILL TAKE CARE OF HER. I WILL TAKE CARE OF HER.
[GENÉSIO] WHAT I...
♪MÚSICA DRAMÁTICA♪
[THUNDER]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME ROCK WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY RHYTHM♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NOITE♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU GET TIRED♪
♪STIR AND REMOVE♪
♪SCALES THAT'S CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COMES TO MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAY STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MOVE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪SCALES THAT'S CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COMES TO MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAY STILL♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
.