[SILENCE]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] REACT, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD.
[TYPHOON] FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, DON'T DIE! DO NOT DIE,
OH MY GOD! I... I WILL TAKE CARE OF YOUR WIFE,
I PROMISE I WILL TAKE CARE. CARMEN LÚCIA MOREIRA DE SOUZA.
I WILL TAKE CARE OF YOUR WIFE, I PROMISE!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] AH...
[TYPHOON] THIS! A MAN HAS JUST BEEN RUN OVER.
HERE ON AVENIDA BRASIL, AT GUADALUPE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] IN FRONT OF A WRITTEN CONSTRUCTION SHOP
"GUADALUPE PAINTS". SEND AN AMBULANCE, FAST.
[IMPACT ON DOOR]
[CARMINHA] STRENGTHEN, MAX! BREAK IT UP!
[DOOR OPEN]
[STEPS]
[CARMINHA] APPEAR, PESTE, I KNOW YOU'RE HERE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] COLLECT THE MONEY. GET THE MONEY! OR FIND THE GIRL
OR FIND THE MONEY. HOLY SHIT!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] THERE'S NO USE OF HIDING.
MAKE IT EASY FOR ME, IT WILL BE BETTER FOR YOU!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] THE CLOSET, MAX.
[CARMINHA] HELP ME, MAN! HELP ME HERE!
[MAX] GO.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RAIN]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[SIREN]
[GENÉSIO] CAR... CARMEN LÚCIA MOREIRA DE SOUZA.
[TYPHOON] I'LL... I'LL TAKE CARE OF HER, I'LL...
I WILL PROTECT HER. I PROMISE THAT I WILL TAKE CARE OF YOUR WIFE!
COME WITH ME. I CARE, I HAVE MONEY,
I HAVE A LOT OF MONEY. I PROMISE I WILL TAKE CARE OF HER!
I WILL TAKE CARE OF HER.
[CARMINHA] THE GIRL IS HERE.
[MAX] NO, THIS GIRL IS NOT HERE AND EVEN IF SHE IS,
WHO GUARANTEES THAT THE MONEY WILL BE HERE
INSIDE THIS HOUSE? HE TELLS ME.
[CARMINHA] ENOUGH, MAX, THE MONEY IS HERE
AND THE GIRL IS WITH HIM.
[MAX] Yeah? HOW ARE YOU SURE OF THIS? HE TELLS ME.
ONE TIME LIKE THIS, GENÉSIO MUST BE SUPPORTING US
AT THE POLICE, MEN ARE KNOCKING OUTSIDE,
THIS CAN HAPPEN. WHAT DO YOU WANT? TO DANCE? IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
SUDDENLY IT'S A GENÉSIO SCALE, WHAT'S YOURS?
LET'S GET OUT.
[CARMINHA] [SHOUTING] STOP BEING SOOOO, MAX! YOU WANT TO LEAVE,
GO AWAY! I DON'T NEED ANY LOSS ON MY SIDE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[IMPACT ON THE GROUND]
[CARMINHA] NOISE OUTSIDE.
[MAX] I ALSO HEAR IT.
[DOOR OPEN]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] THE LANTERN, MAX, ON TOP
FROM THE KITCHEN CABINET. HANDLE!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] I GOT YOU, PESTE!
[RITA] LEAVE ME. LEAVE ME.
[CARMINHA] ARE YOU THINKING I’M KIDDING?
YOU'RE THINKING I'M KIDDING, RIGHT?
[RITA] I'M NOT AFRAID OF YOU!
[MAX] SURE YOU SAID THAT THIS LITTLE GIRL WAS REALLY SMART.
[CARMINHA] I KNOW THE OXES I PLOW. SO, GIRL,
WILL YOU TELL ME WHERE YOU HID THE MONEY?
[RITA] THERE IS NO MONEY AT ALL!
[CARMINHA] [SHOUTING] DON'T LIE!
[MAX] SPEAK!
[CARMINHA] SPEAK UP SOON OR IT'S GOING TO BE WORSE FOR YOU.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CUCTION] GIRL, PAY ATTENTION, FOR ALL PURPOSES,
I'VE NEVER BEEN HERE, UNDERSTAND? AND I'M GOING TO LEAVE THROUGH THAT DOOR,
DISAPPEAR, IF DONA NOÊMIA OR DONA VERONICA ASKS,
I'VE NEVER BEEN HERE, OK?
[MAN] OF COURSE, THE LORD WAS NEVER HERE, RIGHT.
BY THE WAY, THE LORD IS NOT HERE NOW, IS HE?
[PAULO] CRUCIBLE! AH, CRUCIBLE!
[CRUCCILE] PAULO MOTA, PAULO MOTA. BIG MAN.
[PAULO] LET ME INTRODUCE YOU TO MY WIFE MARIANGELA.
[CRUCIBLE] GREAT ROSÂNGELA!
[MARIANGELA] [STUMBLING] MARIANGELA.
[CUCTION] THAT'S RIGHT, ROSÂNGELA, LET'S SIT DOWN, GUYS, LET'S SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, PEOPLE, GO, SIT DOWN, SIT DOWN. THAT.
[CRUCILE] THIS.
[PAULO] I WAS TELLING MARIANGELA
THAT YOU MADE ONE OF THE BIGGEST DEALS OF RECENT TIME
ON THE MARKET, IT BROKE UP. YOU'RE RICH, HUH, CRUCIAL.
[CUCTION] DON'T SPEAK MY NAME, DON'T SPEAK MY NAME.
YES, IT'S FEAR OF KIDNAPPING.
[PAULO] DON'T FREAK, CRADIO...
[CUCTION] I ALREADY TOLD YOU NOT TO SAY MY NAME!
[PAULO] YOU'RE NOT FINE, BOY, YOU'RE NOT FINE.
[CRUCCILE] WHAT DRUG IS THIS?
[PAULO] MARIANGELA'S BIRTHDAY.
♪MANY HAPPINESS♪
♪MANY YEARS OF LIFE♪
♪CONGRATULATIONS TO YOU♪
♪ON THIS DEAR DATE♪
♪MANY HAPPINESS♪
♪MANY YEARS OF LIFE♪
[MARIANGELA] OH. THIS CRAZY FRIEND OF YOURS...
OH, HE'S LOOKING AT MY LEGS, HERE, OH...
[PAULO] CRUCIAL, CRUCIAL, ARE YOU CRAZY?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING DOWN THERE, BOY?
[CRUCCILE] SORRY, SORRY. IT'S THAT I FREAK OUT WITH CONGRATULATIONS,
IT'S PANIC SYNDROME.
[PAULO] OH, THEN GO TAKE CARE. I WANT TO BE ALONE
WITH MY WIFE IT'S HER BIRTHDAY, GET AWAY.
[CUCCILE] OK...
[MARIANGELA] LOVE! LOVE PLEASE...,
[CUCTION] I... I'M GOING TO FIGHT YOU, BOY. GET OUT,
GO AWAY... GET OUT... LOOK, GO, GO... LOOK, GET OUT OF HERE,
GET OUT OF HERE, GO, GET AWAY BEFORE YOU CATCH UP HERE.
GET OUT OF HERE, BOY. YOU ARE CRAZY.
[VERÔNICA] DAMN, I FORGOT MY LIPSTICK. [MUXOXO]
[NOÊMIA] WANT TO TRY MINE?
[VERÔNICA] OH, I THINK I'LL ACCEPT IT. THANKS.
[NOÊMIA] I NOTICED YOU TOO
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR SOMEONE FOR A LONG TIME.
[VERÔNICA] YEAH, IT LOOKS LIKE WE TWO GOT A CAKE TODAY, RIGHT?
[NOÊMIA] MY HUSBAND IS ALWAYS LATE, HE'S A MESS.
THIS TIME HE OVERCOME HIMSELF, LEFT ME AN HOUR PLANTED
WAITING FOR HIM, ON A SUPER IMPORTANT DAY FOR US.
[VERÔNICA] OH, MINE IS ANOTHER WRAP. I ALREADY KNOW, HE WILL
MAKE UP ONE OF THOSE STORIES HE ALWAYS COMES UP.
[NOÊMIA] THAT PEOPLE PRETEND TO BELIEVE.
[VERÔNICA] EXACTLY, WE WILL NEVER KNOW THE TRUTH.
[NOÊMIA] WANT TO KNOW THE TRUTH? WE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THEM, NOTHING. THEY COULD BE THUGS,
ARMS DEALERS, SPIES.
[VERÔNICA] MY HUSBAND SPENDS HALF OF THE WEEK IN SÃO PAULO,
LOVE, I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT HE'S UP TO THERE.
[NOÊMIA] MINE TOO. LIVES HALF OF THE WEEK IN SÃO PAULO.
DO YOU SEE THERE? HUSBAND IS ALL THE SAME, JUST THE ADDRESS CHANGES.
[VERÔNICA] YOUR LIPSTICK, THANK YOU.
[NOÊMIA] LUCK THERE, COMPANION.
[VERÔNICA] LUCK TO YOU TOO, LOVE.
[IVANA] DO I SEE MY BROTHER, NO, MOM, HAS HE ARRIVED?
[MURICY] NO, BUT IN COMPENSATION LOOK AT WHO SHOWED UP,
THE BRIDE PAU DE ARARA. GUYS, THIS WOMAN DOESN'T COME DOWN
IN MY THROAT. MY SON IS A CELEBRITY, HE DESERVES IT
A MUCH BETTER THING THAN THIS MANICURE.
[IVANA] OH, DON'T TALK ABOUT, MOM,
MONALISA IS A GREAT WOMAN.
[MONALISA] AH, MY FATHER IN HEAVEN, MERCY. THERE IS SURUCUCU
AT MY MOTHER-IN-LAW. MY FATHER, WHERE’S TYPHOON?
[SCREAMS OF CELEBRATION]
[TOGETHER] TYPHOON! TYPHOON! TYPHOON! TYPHOON!
[LELECO] HERE, O! THE SPONSOR'S SHIRT!
[MURICY] YEAH, FROM THE SPONSOR! COME ON MY SON,
NOW NOBODY HOLDS ME!
[LELECO] NOW PHOTO, NOW PHOTO. NOW THERE...
[MONALISA] DAMN, TYFÃO DIDN'T EVEN SEARCH FOR ME.
WHAT IS HAPPENING? I'M GOING TO TALK TO HIM.
[OLENKA] GO.
[DIÓGENES] I WANT YOU TO MEET COUNCILMAN SILVERINHA,
HE'S GOING TO GIVE A WATCH HERE AT THE CLUB.
[OLENKA] LICENSE, GUYS.
[MONALISA] GIVE LICENSE, GIVE LICENSE, GIVE LICENSE.
EXACTLY, DIÓGENES, THE CHAMPION IS MINE NOW.
JUST A MINUTE, COME HERE. [DIÓGENES] OK.
[MONALISA] WHAT IS IT, GUYS? WHAT'S GOING ON, HUH?
IS IT TIRED? DID SOMETHING HAPPEN? AND WITH ME?
IS IT BECAUSE I CUT MY HAIR? WHAT?
[TYPHOON] I NEED TO TALK TO YOU, ONLY YOU.
[MONALISA] OKAY, OKAY. LET'S GO TO THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS, COME ON.
[CARMINHA] YOU KNOW I'M NICE, YOU KNOW I'M NOT
I AM ABLE TO HURT YOU. NOW, MY FRIEND HERE, HE IS EVIL,
VERY BAD. I THINK IT'S GOOD FOR YOU TO SAY SOON WHERE IS THIS MONEY
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO GET HURT.
[RITA] WHOEVER HURT ME WILL GO TO JAIL ALONG WITH YOU.
DADDY IS COMING WITH THE POLICE, YOU GUYS GOT BAD!
[CARMINHA] DADDY WON'T ARRIVE.
[KNOCKS ON THE DOOR]
[RITA] I SAID, DIDN'T I?
[CARMINHA] MAN, WHAT SAID? YOU SAID NOTHING, GIRL!
[MAX] THIS IS A TRAP, DAMN IT!
[CARMINHA] SHUT UP, MAX, LET ME THINK!
[MAX] LET'S NOT THINK ANYTHING, LET'S GET OUT NOW!
[CARMINHA] WAIT! YOU PAY ME, PESTE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MAN] GOOD NIGHT.
[RITA] RUN, RUN, YOU BOY, RUN! RUN!
[MAN] CALM DOWN, LITTLE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] WAIT, HELP ME, MAN!
[MAX] JUMP, CARMINHA, JUMP.
[CARMINHA] I CANNOT, HELP ME.
[MAX] JUMP NOW, QUICK, COME!
[MAN] CARMEN LÚCIA MOREIRA DE SOUZA.
[CARMINHA] OH. [SIGH] DON'T LEAVE ME HERE ALONE, MAX.
[MAX] NOW IT CANNOT ANYMORE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MAN] IS DONA CARMEN LÚCIA THE LADY?
[CARMINHA] YES, IT'S ME.
[MAN] I'M AFRAID I HAVE BAD NEWS FOR YOU.
[CARMINHA] SPEAK SOON.
[MAN] HER HUSBAND, GENÉSIO DOS SANTOS, WAS RUN OVER
AND HE DIED. MY CONDOLENCES.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] WHAT IS IT?
[CARMINHA] WAS GENÉSIO RUN OVER?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] HE DIED?
[MAN] DIED INSTANTLY, LADY.
[RITA] IT'S A LIE, IT'S A LIE, MY FATHER DIDN'T DIE, HE'S COMING.
[CARMINHA] IT’S NOT POSSIBLE,
MY HUSBAND, MY GENESIS...
HE DIED.
MY GOD IN HEAVEN, POOR GUY.
[RITA] LIE, DADDY IS PLAYING,
HE WAS THE ONE WHO CALLED THE POLICE.
[CRY]
[CARMINHA] HE DIED, MY LOVE.
HE GONE AND LEFT US, BUT I'M HERE, OK?
I'M ON YOUR SIDE, OK? HUG ME, GO.
[RITA] LIE! LIE! SHE IS BAD, SHE IS BAD!
[CARMINHA] LOOK, MY LOVE, DADDY IS IN HEAVEN AND HE IS NOW
HE IS TOGETHER WITH HIS MOTHER, THE TWO OF THEM HAND IN HAND
WITH JESUS ​​CHRIST, OUR LORD.
[RITA] LIE, IT'S A LIE!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MAN] IS THIS GIRL THE DECEASED'S DAUGHTER?
[CARMINHA] PLEASE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] THIS QUARTER, IT IS PROBLEMATIC, POOR THING.
SHE IS A MOTHER'S ORPHAN AND NOW SHE'S A FATHER AND MOTHER'S ORPHAN.
[RITA] WHAT IS SHE SAYING? WHAT IS SHE SAYING, GUARD?
SHE IS DANGEROUS. DADDY GOES TO THE POLICE TO ARREST HER,
YOU HAVE TO ARREST HER.
[CARMINHA] WHAT IS THIS, MY LOVE? FOR GOD'S SAKE,
DADDY WOULDN'T LIKE TO HEAR YOU SAYING SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW THIS, MY LOVE, THIS IS NOT A JOKE
OF THUG AND GOOD GUY. COME HERE...
[RITA] LIE! SIR, THERE'S A THUG HERE, HE'S HER FRIEND,
HE IS HIDING AROUND HERE.
[CARMINHA] MY GOD, THERE IS NOBODY HERE, RITA.
WHAT IS THIS, RITA? FOR GOD'S SAKE. YOU'RE DISTURBED,
POOR THING. MY LOVE, LET'S ENTER THE HOUSE, COME ON. HE COMES.
[RITA] NO, NO, NO, NO.
[CARMINHA] POLICEMAN, HELP ME, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD!
YOUR GUARD, FOR THE SAKE OF GOD! I LOST MY HUSBAND, MY GOD!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO ANYMORE, I DON'T KNOW! IT HELPS ME!
RITINHA, I LOVE YOU, MY LOVE, I LOVE YOU.
[RITA] LIE! LIE!
[MAN] TAKE HER INSIDE THE HOUSE, PLEASE.
[RITA] NO, OFFICER, EVERYTHING IS WRONG.
[CARMINHA] FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO ANYMORE.
LET'S HAVE A GLASS OF WATER WITH SUGAR
FOR HER, RIGHT? [MAN] COME ON.
[RITA] [SHOUTING] SHE'S BAD! PLEASE DO NOT! SHE IS A WITCH,
PLEASE DO NOT. SHE IS EVIL, SHE IS A WITCH, SHE IS EVIL!
SHE IS VERY BAD, SHE IS A WITCH, SHE IS EVIL!
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] STAY CALM, MY LOVE,
I'M GOING TO TALK TO YOUR GUARD, TAKE THIS WATER, HERE.
TAKE IT, MY LOVE.
[GLASS CUP BREAKING]
[CARMINHA] OH.
[RITA] I WANT MY FATHER!
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] OH, I CAN'T HANDLE IT!
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] OH.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[RITA] NO! NO! NO! NO! NO! NO, YOU WITCH,
I HATE YOU, I HATE YOU! GET ME OUT OF HERE, GET ME OUT OF HERE,
I HATE YOU! I HATE YOU, YOU ARE A WITCH!
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] OH.
[MAN] I UNDERSTAND, LADY. JUST WHAT I NEED
THAT SOMEONE WILL RECOGNIZE THE BODY IN THE IML.
[CARMINHA] OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, PLEASE. NO,
I DON'T HAVE CONDITIONS, I DON'T HAVE.
IF YOU COULD BE SOMEONE ELSE... OH MY GOD IN HEAVEN... YOU HAVE THE...
THE NEIGHBOR, YOUR TOBIAS.
HE WAS A VERY FRIEND OF MY HUSBAND.
[MAN] NO, I WILL RELEASE THE LADY, A FRIEND RESOLVES.
I CAN STAY A LONGER TIME HERE, IF YOU NEED IT.
[CARMINHA] IT IS VERY KIND OF THE LORD.
THE LORD WAS ALREADY A TRUE ANGEL TO ME.
[STEPS]
[CARMINHA] AMEN.
[DOOR CRANKING]
[DOOR CLOSE]
[CARMINHA] AMEN.
AMEN.
[CARMINHA] [LAUGHS] GIVE IT TO IT, CARMINHA! I DON'T BELIEVE!
THAT WAS A GREAT GOAL.
[CARMINHA] AH-HA! HE DIED! [LAUGHS] DEAD!
[RITA] GET ME OUT OF HERE, GET ME OUT OF HERE.
[CARMINHA] [SCREAM]
[RITA] I HATE YOU, YOU ARE A WITCH!
[MONALISA] IT'S ME, RIGHT?
[TYPHOON] HUH?
[MONALISA] IS IT ME? AND WITH ME? ARE YOU REGRET
YOU HAVE ASKED ME TO MARRIAGE, RIGHT?
NOW YOU'RE BORED ABOUT THE SITUATION.
[TYPHOON] OH MONALISA, YOU ARE MY WIFE, MONALISA, DON'T FREAK.
[MONALISA] SO WHAT IS IT? WHAT IS IT, FOR THE SAKE OF GOD?
I TALKED TO YOU ON THE PHONE, YOU WERE ALL HAPPY,
THEN YOU COME HERE WITH THAT LIKELY FACE, SAY SOMETHING,
SAY SOMETHING.
[TYPHOON] I KILLED A MAN.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] WHAT?
[TYPHOON] I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T KNOW, I WAS... I DON'T KNOW,
IT WAS SUDDENLY, HE THREW HIMSELF IN... IN FRONT OF MY CAR,
I RUN OVER HIM.
[MONALISA] WELL, IF HE THREW HIMSELF IN FRONT OF YOUR CAR,
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
[TYPHOON] BUT I DON'T KNOW, IT WAS SUDDEN, I DON'T KNOW, I WAS...
I WAS HAPPY, I WAS SINGING, I DIDN'T SEE IT.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] ARE YOU SURE YOU DIED?
[TYPHOON] DIED. HE DIED THERE, IN FRONT OF ME.
I CALLED THE AMBULANCE, BUT HE WAS ALREADY DEAD. THE AMBULANCE...
WHEN THE AMBULANCE ARRIVED, IT TAKEN ME AWAY, I WAS TERRIFIED,
I RUN AWAY, I WAS AFRAID OF BEING ARRESTED,
IMAGINE IF I WAS ARRESTED ON THE HAPPIEST DAY OF MY LIFE? TODAY?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] NO, BUT YOU CALLED THE AMBULANCE,
YOU TRIED TO SAVE THIS MAN...
[TYPHOON] BUT I ACTED LIKE A CRIMINAL, MONALISA, I RUN AWAY!
I ACTED LIKE A CRIMINAL!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] MY GOD IN HEAVEN, I WAS AFRAID, IMAGINE
IF THE PRESS FIND OUT WHAT SHE WAS GOING TO DO WITH MY NAME,
IT WAS GOING TO DISTORT THE HISTORY, IT WAS... IT WAS GOING TO END MY CAREER.
THEN I WAS AFRAID.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
[MONALISA] I THINK I WOULD WAIT FOR THE AMBULANCE,
I WOULD GO TO THE DELEGACY. BUT YOU ARE DIFFERENT FROM ME,
YOU TRIED TO SAVE THIS MAN, TYPHOON.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] TYPHOON, MY LOVE, YOU ARE A GOOD MAN,
I UNDERSTAND YOUR SITUATION.
I, IN YOUR PLACE, WOULD ALSO BE PISSED.
[TYPHOON] I CAN'T FORGET HIM ASKING
SO I COULD LOOK FOR HIS WIFE,
CARMEN LÚCIA MOREIRA DE SOUZA, DON’T FORGET HER NAME.
[PAUSEDLY] CARMEN LÚCIA MOREIRA DE SOUZA.
[MONALISA] AND DO YOU THINK ABOUT LOOKING FOR THIS WOMAN?
[TYPHOON] OF COURSE I'M GOING TO LOOK FOR HIS WIFE,
IT IS CLEAR. I WILL HELP THIS WOMAN.
[MONALISA] IT’S GOOD, IT’S GOOD. THAT'S RIGHT. HE KNOWS,
NOTHING IN LIFE HAPPENS BY CHANCE, THIS IS DESTINY.
IF THIS MAN CROSSED YOUR PATH AND DIED SAYING
THE NAME OF THIS WOMAN, THIS WOMAN SOMEHOW,
SHE HAS ALREADY ENTERED OUR LIVES. GO THERE, LOOK FOR HER,
TRY TO HELP. NOW, SEE WHERE YOU'RE GOING TO GET INTO, MY LOVE,
WHY DID THIS MAN... IF THIS MAN DIED THROWN IN FRONT
OF YOUR CAR, HE COULD BE A DRINK, HE COULD BE...
[TYPHOON] NO, NO, MONALISA... MÓ TIOZINHO,
MÓ GUY OF A PUBLIC SERVANT. WELL, HIS WIFE MUST BE
A LADY, I'M GOING TO HELP THIS WIDOW.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[DOOR CLOSE]
[DOOR OPEN]
[MAX] SO WHAT?
[CARMINHA] DO YOU BELIEVE IN MIRACLES? DO YOU BELIEVE IT OR DON’T YOU BELIEVE IT?
[MAX] I CANNOT BELIEVE IT. ARE YOU WANTING
TELL ME THAT THE CROWN CROWNED UP, IS THAT REAL?
[CARMINHA] RUN OVER, CRUSHED BY A CAR. PUFF!
GONE, TURNED TO MUSH. [LAUGHS] IF IT MAKES IT EASIER,
YOU'LL HAVE TO TAKE A CUP, MY LOVE.
[MAX] I THINK THE GUY UP THERE IS GIVING YOU
A HUGE CREDIT.
[CARMINHA] SERIOUSLY, THE BOSS TIES HIMSELF TO ME,
DON'T YOU TIE UP, BOSS? BETTER THAN ORDERED, MAX.
DO YOU KNOW THE EXPRESSION MERRY WIDOW? BECAUSE SHE IS HERE, MY GOODNESS,
BEFORE YOU, THE MOST JOYFUL OF ALL ON THIS PLANET!
[MAX] OKAY, SO WE'RE GOING TO CELEBRATE THIS,
HAVE A PARTY... [CARMINHA] NOT YET.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] THE MONEY IS MISSING, HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
[RITA] [DISTANT VOICE] GET ME OUT OF HERE! TAKE ME OUT OF HERE!
I HATE YOU. I HATE YOU.
[CARMINHA] THIS CHILIQUENTA IS GETTING ON MY NERVES.
YOU CAN'T IMAGINE THE ATTACK SHE MADE IN FRONT OF THE POLICE OFFICER.
BUT YOU CAN LEAVE IT, I ALREADY KNOW A WAY TO DO IT
THIS GIRL OPENED HER MOUTH.
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME ROCK WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY RHYTHM♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪EVERYONE SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE EVERY NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU GET TIRED♪
♪STIR AND REMOVE♪
♪SCALES THAT'S CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COMES TO MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAY STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MOVE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪SCALES THAT'S CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COMES TO MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAY STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MOVE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[ALEXIA] WHAT I... OH, DOCTOR JACOB... DOCTOR JACOB,
I TOLD THE LORD, I'M NOT MIXING ALCOHOLIC DRINKS
WITH THE MEDICINE. OF COURSE I'M NOT. NO, I'M IN A BAR,
IT'S EVIDENT THAT I'M IN A BAR, DOCTOR JACOB,
BUT I'M DRINKING SODA. HUM... I SWEAR TO THE LORD.
GO BACK HOME? OH, DOCTOR JACOB, TONIGHT IS IMPOSSIBLE
GO BACK HOME. MY SEER TOLD ME THAT TONIGHT
I WOULD LEAVE, I WOULD FIND THE IDEAL BREEDER,
MY SON'S FATHER... YES, SHE SAID TONIGHT
I WAS GOING TO GET PREGNANT, DOCTOR JACOB. TODAY I WAS GOING TO GET PREGNANT!
I KNOW IT'S ALL SUGGESTION, DOCTOR JACOB,
OF COURSE I KNOW IT'S ALL SUGGESTION,
BUT THE FACT IS THAT TODAY I AM AT THE PEAK OF MY REPRODUCTIVE PERIOD,
IS NOT TRUE? SO...NO, MY OVA, I FEEL IT,
THEY ARE SCREAMING, THEY REALLY WANT TO BE, ALL OF THEM,
FERTILIZED. I'M SURE. I FEEL.
OH, DOCTOR JACOB, WHAT IS THIS? SO LET'S TALK THEN, LIKE THIS,
IN SCIENTIFIC TERMS, HOW MANY TIMES DO YOU THINK
THAT REPRODUCTIVE OPPORTUNITY, LIKE TONIGHT,
WILL IT REPEAT? VERY FEW TIMES. IF IT WILL BE REPEATED,
IS NOT IT? SO, THAT'S A FACT... BUT THAT'S IT!
OH DOCTOR JACOB, YOU ARE A PSYCHOANALYST, RIGHT,
YOU BELIEVE IN FREUD, I AM A WOMAN,
I BELIEVE IN Psychics. [GASKING]
[CRUCCILE] GOOD EVENING. A DOUBLE WHISKEY FOR ME.
[ALEXIA] OH, DOCTOR JACOB, YOU WON'T BELIEVE
WHAT I SEE HERE IN FRONT OF ME, DOCTOR JACOB,
A MAN IN A YELLOW TIE. THE SEER... THE SEER TOLD ME
THAT MY SON'S FATHER, IDEAL REPRODUCER,
IT WAS GOING TO BE A MAN WEARING A YELLOW TIE.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO HANG UP, DOCTOR JACOB. TOMORROW,
AT FOUR PM, OK?
[CRUCILE] ANOTHER DOUBLE WHISKEY, PLEASE.
[CRUCCILE] NO, I ORDERED ANOTHER DOUBLE WHISKEY.
[MAN] THIS DRINK
IT WAS THAT GIRL THERE WHO TOLD YOU TO OFFER IT.
[CRUCCILE] HI.
[ALEXIA] HI.
[CUCTION] I'M NOT VERY USED TO WOMEN
PAYING FOR MY DRINK.
[ALEXIA] OH, I KNOW. THEN PREFER THE DEMICE, THE SUBMISSIVE.
[CRUCILE] NO, NO, ON THE CONTRARY,
I LOVE THE POWERFUL.
[ALEXIA] SO YOU'RE READY TO BE SENT.
[CRUCCILE] [LAUGHTER]
[CRUCCILE] I HAD A KIND OF HARD NIGHT TODAY, YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW THE SAYING “LUCK IN BUSINESS, UNlucky in love”?
[ALEXIA] WHAT IS THIS? ARE YOU PLAYING YOUR SHIRT LIKE THAT?
[CRUCCILE] NO, I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
[ALEXIA] BECAUSE SEE CLOSELY...
YOUR LUCK CAN CHANGE, CAN’T IT?
HASN’T THE NIGHT JUST STARTED?
[CRUCCILE] Yeah. [LAUGHS]
[ALEXIA] I SEE YOU HAVE A PHYSICAL COMPLEXION
PRETTY GOOD, RIGHT? VERY GOOD REALLY. WERE YOU AN ATHLETE?
[CRUCIBLE] YEAH, ROWING CHAMPION AT 17 YEARS OLD.
[ALEXIA] OH, WE SOON SEE THAT YOU REALLY
IT COMES FROM A LINEAGE, A VERY HEALTHY FAMILY, RIGHT?
[CRUCCILE] MY GRANDFATHER DIED AT THE AGE OF 98
WITHOUT EVER HAD A CAVITY.
[ALEXIA] OH, HOW AMAZING!
[LAUGHS] AND CONTACT LENSES? DO YOU USE CONTACT LENSES?
[CRUCCILE] NO, I DON'T USE IT, I'M NOT MYOPE, NO.
[ALEXIA] AH! WOW, THAT'S GOOD, ISN'T IT?
AND THUS, NO DEGENERATIVE DISEASE IN THE FAMILY,
TYPE: NO ALZHEIMER'S, OR DIABETES.
[CRUCILE] WHAT'S THAT? IT'S A... IT'S A MEDICAL REPORT,
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT? THAT'S IT, DO YOU WANT A REPORT?
[LAUGHTER]
[ALEXIA] NO, JOKING.
[CRUCCILE] COME HERE, TELL A LITTLE ABOUT YOURSELF,
WHAT DO YOU DO...
[ALEXIA] I THINK IT'S BETTER TO KEEP ANONYMITY, RIGHT?
CAN I REQUEST THE ACCOUNT? WAITER PLEASE BRING THE BILL
FOR US? LET'S GO TO WHAT'S INTERESTING?
♪GOD PROTECT ME FROM YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
♪GOD HELP ME FROM YOUR ANGER♪
♪GOD IMMUNIZE ME FROM YOUR POISON♪
♪GOD SPARE ME FROM YOUR END♪
♪GOD PROTECT ME FROM YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
♪GOD HELP ME♪
[CRUCCILE] HI.
[ALEXIA] JUST A MINUTE, WAIT A MOMENT.
[CUCCIFIER] [LAUGHTER] LOOK, I WANT TO TELL YOU
THAT I DON'T KNOW YOUR NAME YET, BUT LOOK, I LOVED BEING SENT,
THE NIGHT WAS WONDERFUL.
WILL YOU TELL ME YOUR NAME NOW?
[ALEXIA] IT'S ALEXIA.
[CRUCCILE] Wow...
[ALEXIA] NO, NO, NO, NO, WAIT.
[CRUCCILE] WAIT. [ALEXIA] NO, COME HERE. O,
I'LL GIVE YOU YOUR THINGS, YES... TAKE YOU TO THE DOOR.
[CRUCILE] TO THE DOOR? NO, BUT ARE YOU GOING TO TAKE ME TO THE DOOR?
[ALEXIA] I'LL TAKE YOU.
[CRUCCILE] WANTS TO TAKE ME TO THE DOOR.
[ALEXIA] NO, BUT THEN, OH, BUT COME ON,
IS THIS NOT THE PROPOSAL? ISN'T IT SEX WITHOUT INVOLVEMENT?
[CRUCCILE] THAT, RIGHTLY, OUR MEETING WAS PERFECT
BECAUSE OF THIS, I'M LIVING IN THIS PHASE.
SINGLENESS, LONE WOLF, UNDERSTAND?
[ALEXIA] SO, NO... SO, ME TOO, LOOK,
ME ALSO, I DON'T WANT TO BE INVOLVED WITH ANYONE.
BUT, FREEDOM IS PRICELESS, ISN’T IT?
[CRUCIBLE] IT'S TRUE, IT'S TRUE. BUT THAT
IT DOESN'T MEAN THAT WE CAN'T SEE EACH OTHER AGAIN, RIGHT?
[ALEXIA] NO, WE CAN SEE EACH OTHER.
AFTER ALL, THE FUTURE BELONGS TO GOD, DOESN’T IT?
[CRUCCILE] YEAH... THAT'S RIGHT, YEAH.
[LAUGHS] LISTEN, JUST ONE MORE THING:
WE DIDN'T USE CONDOMS.
[ALEXIA] NO, DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT THAT TOO,
I... I TAKE THE PILL.
[CRUCILE] OH, WONDERFUL.
[ALEXIA] SEE YOU SOON! [SIGH]
OH MY GOD. OH, MY SAINT GERALDO, OH MY SAINT SARA,
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, MAKE A BABY BE BORN HERE IN THIS BELLY,
PLEASE.
[DOOR OPEN]
[CARMINHA] RITA.
[RITA] DON’T LAY YOUR HAND ON ME!
[CARMINHA] I WON'T PULL,
I WANT TO MAKE PEACE WITH YOU.
I PREPARED BREAKFAST FOR BOTH OF US.
HE COMES.
[STEPS]
[CARMINHA] SIT DOWN. EAT A LITTLE.
[RITA] IT'S NO USE.
I'M NOT GOING TO TELL YOU WHERE THE MONEY IS.
[CARMINHA] I KNOW YESTERDAY WAS NOT EASY FOR YOU,
NEITHER FOR ME. I KNOW, TOO, THAT YOU DON'T LIKE ME,
THERE IS NO REASON TO LIKE IT,
BECAUSE I WAS NEVER NICE TO YOU. BUT DON'T THINK
THAT I DIDN'T SUFFER. IN MY WAY, I LIKED YOUR FATHER.
[RITA] LIAR! [CARMINHA] NOW IT DOESN’T MATTER
MORE IF YOU BELIEVE ME OR NOT, GIRL.
I'M GOING AWAY! I'LL GET OUT OF HERE AND YOU'LL SEE YOURSELF
FREE FOREVER. I MADE A SHOPPING, THE PANTRY IS FULL.
AND HERE IS A LIST OF YOUR SCHOOL'S TELEPHONE NUMBER,
FROM YOUR DOCTOR, IF YOU NEED IT.
I HOPE THAT ONE DAY YOU FORGIVE ME. WHEN YOU GROW UP,
YOU WILL UNDERSTAND THAT NOBODY IS JUST GOOD, NOR JUST BAD.
[RITA] YOU ARE JUST EVIL. YOU ARE NOT PEOPLE!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] I COULD HAVE BEEN A GOOD MOTHER TO YOU.
I SWALLOWED A LOT OF TOAD IN LIFE BECAUSE OF YOU AND NOW IT'S ENOUGH.
I GIVE UP. I THROW IN THE TOWEL. YOU TAKE THIS MONEY
FROM YOUR FATHER AND SEE IF YOU CAN BE HAPPY.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] I GOT YOU, TRASH. [RITA] [GASKING]
[CARMINHA] SEE IF EVERYTHING IS THERE, MAX.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] SHUT UP, SHUT UP!
[MAX] THERE'S ALL THE MONEY... IT'S HERE. IF YOU ASK ME
SORRY, I CAN EVEN SAVE YOU OF WHAT I'M THINKING
IN DOING IT WITH YOU. ASK FOR SORRY.
[SHOUTING] SORRY!
[SPIT]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] YOU CAN LEAVE IT, I'LL SEND YOU
TO A VERY COOL PLACE.
NOW, WHO WILL EDUCATE YOU, MY DAUGHTER, IS LIFE!
NOW YOU WILL BE LIKE ME. IT WAS THE STREET THAT EDUCATED ME!
IT WAS THE NEED, IT WAS THE REALITY,
REAL LIFE. TAKE THAT BAD OUT OF HERE, MAX.
[RITA] WHERE IS HE GOING TO TAKE ME?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RITA] NO, LET GO OF ME! HELP!
[MAX] RELEASE, RELEASE, YOU WON'T GO...
[RITA] HELP! SOMEONE HELP ME!
HELP... HELP, NO!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RITA] I DON'T WANT TO GO.
[RITA] GET ME OUT OF HERE! TAKE ME OUT OF HERE
[KISSING CLAP]
[RITA] YOU EVIL! PLEASE, I DON'T WANT TO GO. PLEASE,
PLEASE DO NOT! PLEASE! PLEASE PLEASE,
I DO NOT WANT TO GO. [CRYING] PLEASE NO!
PLEASE! I DO NOT WANT TO GO...
[SILENCE]
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, MONALISA, NO. DON'T GET UP, NO.
[MONALISA] "PSST!" [TYPHOON] OH, DON'T GET UP, NO.
SAY IT'S A NIGHTMARE, SAY I DIDN'T RUN OVER
THAT GUY. [MONALISA] LOVE, CALM,
RESTS. YOU FELT SICK YESTERDAY, SLEEP A LITTLE MORE.
[TYPHOON] NO... I WON'T BE ABLE TO REST.
I WILL NOT REST. I NEED TO FIND THIS WOMAN,
LIKE... CARMEN LÚCIA. I NEED TO FIND HER,
IF NOT, I WILL NOT HAVE REST, I WILL NOT HAVE PEACE.
[MONALISA] WAIT, LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
SO, LET'S SAY YOU FIND THIS WOMAN.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO TELL HER? HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT THIS?
[TYPHOON] I'LL SAY THAT I WAS FRIENDS WITH HER HUSBAND,
IF SHE NEEDS HELP. [MONALISA] BUT DO YOU THINK THAT
SHE NEEDS HELP? [TYPHOON] YOU CAN FIND OUT, RIGHT?
[MONALISA] OH MY GOD. IT IS TRUE THAT PEOPLE
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING, DO YOU? WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS WOMAN,
IF SHE... SHE COULD HATE THAT HUSBAND. SHE COULD, I DON'T KNOW,
YOU'RE SEPARATING FROM HIM... [TYPHOON] MONALISA,
HE DIED IN MY ARMS, SPEAKING HER NAME.
WHAT DO YOU THINK? HE WAS IN LOVE WITH HER OF COURSE.
[MONALISA] I'M AFRAID YOU'LL GET MORE AND MORE INVOLVED.
BE CAREFUL, MY LOVE.
[TYPHOON] [SIGH] I THINK THE ONLY THING YOU'LL DO WITH
MAY I FEEL BETTER AFTER ALL I DID IS FIND
THIS WOMAN IS THE REQUEST OF THE DEAD.
[MONALISA] IT WAS NOT A REQUEST. HE SAID HER NAME,
HE DIDN'T EVEN FINISH THE SENTENCE.
[TYPHOON] IT WAS A REQUEST. I FELT LIKE THAT, MONALISA, I WILL
BELIEVE IN MY INTUITION. DID YOU UNDERSTAND?
NOW, HOW DO I FIND THIS WOMAN?
[MONALISA] AH, FIRST THING, WE HAVE TO KNOW WHERE
HE'S GOING TO BE BURIED, RIGHT? WE NEED TO DISCOVER WHAT
CEMETERY. WHERE WAS THE ACCIDENT?
[TYPHOON] AVENIDA BRASIL, AT GUADALUPE.
[MONALISA] SO, LET'S CALL ALL THE CEMETERIES IN THIS
REGION. ARE YOU THE ONLY ONE RUN OVER? GENÉSIO FONSECA MOURA, WE THINK,
HE WILL BE BURIED AT THE RICARDO DE ALBUQUERQUE CEMETERY.
[TYPHOON] I'M GOING THERE.
[MONALISA] MY GOD, I'M SO AFRAID, BABY, LOOK WHERE
YOU'RE GOING TO GET INTO MYSELF. YOU ARE NOW FAMOUS,
IT CAN HAPPEN ANYWAY.
[TYPHOON] I NEED TO GO.
[MONALISA] DO YOU WANT ME TO GO WITH YOU?
[TYPHOON] NO. NO NEED, MY LOVE.
[KISSING CLAP]
[STEPS]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[RITA] STOP THE CAR, I WANT TO GET OUT!
TO THE CAR, I WANT TO GET OUT!
[MAX] CAN YOU BE QUIET, RIGHT?
PEOPLE ARE ALREADY ARRIVING.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[RITA] WHAT PLACE IS THIS?
[MAX] IT'S OUR WAY.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE A STOP HERE, OH.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MAX] THIS HERE IS UNCLE NILO, RITINHA, HE IS OUR FRIEND.
[NILO] DO YOU LIKE CARAMEL, FIA?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[RITA] NO, DON'T LEAVE ME HERE! PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME HERE!
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME HERE! PLEASE, I'M ASKING YOU!
PLEASE I APOLOGIZE! I SWEAR, PLEASE!
[NILE] STOP, GIRL, STOP!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[RITA] DON'T LEAVE ME HERE, DON'T LEAVE ME HERE!
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME! DO NOT LEAVE ME!
I WANT MY FATHER, I WANT MY FATHER!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NILE] I'M WAITING FOR YOU AT HOME. SOON,
WE'RE GOING TO DINNER, SEE, FIA?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[BIRD SONG]
[CRY]
[NATURE AMBIENCE]
[MAN] AND GENESIO'S DAUGHTER?
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] I THOUGHT IT WAS BETTER TO LEAVE HER AT HOME.
[CRY]
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] SAVE THE POOR GIRL FROM THE BURIAL.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] CARMEN LÚCIA.
[CARMINHA] ME.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CAR ALARM]
[CARMINHA] AREN'T YOU TUFÃO, PLAYING FOOTBALL?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] [SNIFF] YES... YES, YES.
[TYPHOON] MY CONDOLENCES. I...
HE WAS A VERY FRIEND WITH HER HUSBAND.
WOULD YOU LET ME TAKE YOU HOME?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[CARMINHA] WERE YOU FRIENDS WITH GENÉSIO?
[TYPHOON] WAS.
VERY FRIEND.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] DON'T YOU WANT TO GET IN THE CAR? I...
I WILL EXPLAIN EVERYTHING ON THE WAY.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[STEPS]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] GENESIO NEVER MENTIONED MY NAME, DID HE?
[CARMINHA] NO. NEVER.
I MEAN, WHEN YOU APPEARED ON TELEVISION,
HE SAID YOU WERE A CRAZY, RIGHT, THOSE THINGS.
[TYPHOON] HER HUSBAND WAS A VERY GENEROUS MAN.
IN REALITY, I FUCKED UP WITH HIM A LOT IN THE PAST.
[CARMINHA] IS IT REAL?
[TYPHOON] Yeah. WHEN I STARTED PLAYING FOOTBALL,
WHEN I WAS NOBODY, HE...
IT GAVE ME A LOT OF STRENGTH. IT HELPED ME A LOT.
[CARMINHA] Yeah?
[TYPHOON] Yeah.
[CARMINHA] GENÉSIO WAS A SAINT.
[TYPHOON] Yeah. A SAINT.
A GOOD MAN, RIGHT?
[CARMINHA] VERY GOOD.
[TYPHOON] HE WAS LIKE A BROTHER TO ME.
AND THEN, WHEN I WAS SUCCESSFUL, I MADE MONEY...
SUCCESS GOES TO PEOPLE'S HEADS, DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE?
[CARMINHA] I IMAGINE.
[TYPHOON] WE END UP TURN YOUR BACK ON JUST
THE COOLEST PEOPLE, PEOPLE WHO LIKE YOU
FOR WHAT YOU ARE. NO... NOT BECAUSE OF YOUR SUCCESS.
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE.
[TYPHOON] AND [EXTENDED] THE...
GENÉSIO WAS ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE.
FOR A LONG TIME, I WANTED TO GET CLOSER BETWEEN, BUT...
MONTH IN, MONTH OUT, PEOPLE PUSH WITH OUR BELLIES
AND SUDDENLY, I HAD THE NEWS OF HIS DEATH.
I... WAS DEVASTATED.
[TYPHOON] NOW, I...
IF POSSIBLE, I WOULD LIKE TO DO SOMETHING
TO HELP HIS FAMILY, TO HELP YOU.
[TYPHOON] DID HE HAVE CHILDREN?
[CARMINHA] NO.
HE NEVER HAD CHILDREN.
[DUMPHOUSE ENVIRONMENT]
[NILO] COME IN, FIA.
[DOOR CRANKING]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NILE] YOU MUST BE HUNGRY, RIGHT?
ARE YOU SERVED? O, COME, COME.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NILE] OKAY.
[RITA] THIS JACKET IS MINE!
[NILE] IT'S GOOD FOR YOU TO GET USED TO IT, HERE.
HERE, OH, EVERYTHING IS EVERYBODY'S AND NOTHING IS NOBODY'S, RIGHT?
OH, IT'S ENDING. She sits THERE, GO, SIT THERE.
YOU CAN GO, GO, GO, GO, GO.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[LAUGHTER]
[NILE] THE NEW COLLEAGUE IS USED TO EATING THIN PAPA.
[NILE] EAT, EAT, OKAY.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CAR ENGINE]
[TYPHOON] WHICH IS THE HOUSE?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] DON'T YOU KNOW?
GENÉSIO LIVED ALMOST HIS WHOLE LIFE HERE, IN THIS HOUSE,
SINCE HE MARRIED ANOTHER WOMAN OF HIS,
WHO DIED AWAY, DO YOU REMEMBER HER?
[TYPHOON] UHUM, I REMEMBER.
[CARMINHA] HELENA.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] YEAH, HELENA.
[CARMINHA] THE HOUSE IS THERE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] HOW COULD I FORGET, RIGHT?
[CARMINHA] DO YOU MIND COMING IN WITH ME?
[CRYING] I DON'T WANT TO GO INTO THE HOME ALONE,
GENÉSIO WILL NOT BE THERE ANYMORE, WAITING FOR ME AS ALWAYS.
[CRY]
[TYPHOON] OF COURSE, OF COURSE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] YOU CAN COME IN.
GENESIO WAS AN EXEMPLARY HUSBAND,
I NEVER LET ANYTHING MISS IN THIS HOUSE.
TREATED ME LIKE A QUEEN,
HE DIDN'T EVEN WANT ME TO WORK.
[TYPHOON] DID HE LEAVE YOU WELL AFFORDED?
[CARMINHA] GENÉSIO HAD NOTHING, HE LEFT ME NOTHING,
I DON'T EVEN HAVE ANY WAY TO PAY THE RENT FOR THIS HOUSE.
[TYPHOON] NO, I CAN ADVISE THAT WITH THE GREATEST PLEASURE.
[CARMINHA] WAIT, SO YOU'RE MAKING ME FEEL LIKE
A BEGGAR. I DON'T NEED ALMS, NO, SEE?
[TYPHOON] NO, NO, NO, SORRY, SORRY...
NO, IT WAS NOT MY INTENTION.
[CARMINHA] NO, AND THEN, THE LAST THING WE
NEEDS, WHAT PEOPLE THINK
AT A MOMENT LIKE THIS, IT'S CASH. YOU'RE WELCOME!
[TYPHOON] OF COURSE, OF COURSE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] MY LIFE AND GENESIO'S...
I NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD BE LUCKY TO FIND A COMPANION
SO PERFECT FOR ME.
PERFECT IN EVERY WAY, IN SIMILAR TASTES,
IN THE PROGRAMS WE WOULD LIKE TO DO,
IN THE WORLDVIEW...
DO YOU KNOW THAT PERFECT MOVIE COUPLE? [LAUGHS]
IT WAS ME AND GENÉSIO. IT WAS SO HAPPY, MY GOD,
SO MUCH HAPPINESS, THAT WE ALMOST HAD NO SOCIAL LIFE.
IT WAS JUST ME AND HIM IN THIS WORLD.
OH MY GOD,
NOW I KNOW WHAT LONELINESS MEANS,
IT FEELS LIKE I'M ALONE IN THE MIDDLE OF A DESERT.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] WHAT WILL IT BE LIKE TO WAKE UP TOMORROW, MY GOD...
WAKE UP TOMORROW, ON A SUNDAY, WITHOUT MY GENÉSIO! THERE!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] LOOK...
[TYPHOON] NOW YOU HAVE A FRIEND.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] UH... [THROAT CLEAR]
WHAT DID YOU USED TO DO WITH GENÉSIO ON SUNDAY?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] BARBECUE. EVERY SUNDAY GENESIO
HE TOOK ME TO EAT BARBECUE.
[TYPHOON] YOU ACCEPT AN INVITATION FROM ME TO GO TOMORROW
IN A BARBECUE?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] I'LL THINK.
[TYPHOON] I'LL COME HERE TOMORROW, TWO PM.
[CARMINHA] I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ELSE.
I'M NO LONGER RESPONSIBLE FOR MYSELF.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] IF YOU DON'T MIND, NOW I...
I WOULD PREFER TO BE ALONE WITH MY PAIN.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] CLEAR, CLEAR, CLEAR.
[TYPHOON] I'LL COME HERE TOMORROW, SO, HUM?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] [WHISPERING] I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
[CARMINHA] IS TODAY MY DAY, MY GOD?
[MUXOXO] DALE, CA...
[CARMINHA] [WHISPERING] DALE, CARMINHA!
[NILE] [SHOUTING] COME ON! LET'S "WORK", GIRL!
COME ON, YOU'VE ALREADY SLEPT A LOT! LET'S GO, LET'S "TRABAIÁ"
THE GARBAGE TRUCK IS COMING!
EVERYONE, LET'S "WORK", COME ON, COME ON!
COME ON, LET'S "WORK", PUT ON YOUR SHOES TO PROTECT YOUR FEET!
A NEW TRUCK IS COMING! HEY THERE, LET'S "WORK".
COME ON, EVERYONE "TRABAIANO"!
[RITA] WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
[NILE] [LAUGHTER] JÉSSICA WILL TEACH YOU, RIGHT, JÉSSICA?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[JÉSSICA] THIS IS SO YOU DON'T HURT OR GET SICK.
[RITA] BUT WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO?
[JÉSSICA] COLLECT TRASH, LIKE EVERYONE. YOU HAVE TO COLLECT GLASS,
CANS AND HARD PAPER, WHICH PAYS BETTER. IF YOU FIND A PAN,
IT'S DONE, BUT IF YOU DON'T SAVE A MONEY EVERY DAY,
THE NILE GETS ANGRY, VERY ANGRY.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[JÉSSICA] WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR, BOBA? HE COMES! FAST!
[CARMINHA] ENTER, MY LOVE, ENTER.
[DOOR CLOSE]
[CARMINHA] SO, WAS EVERYTHING OK?
DID YOU GIVE THE GIRL TO NILO?
[MAX] I FEEL SORRY FOR THE GIRL.
[CARMINHA] THIS IS NO TIME FOR CRYING, WHAT IS DONE,
IT'S DONE. TODAY IS A DAY OF CELEBRATION!
[MAX] COME HERE, WHAT IS THIS? THEN, IF DOING THIS TYPE
ALL JOY WHY? YOU HAD SO MUCH FUN AT THE BURIAL
FROM YOUR HUSBAND, IS THAT IT?
[CARMINHA] NOT JUST THAT, THERE'S MORE.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE IT, TODAY IS REALLY MY DAY, MAX.
IF I TELL YOU, NOBODY WILL BELIEVE IT!
[MAX] OH, SPEAK.
[CARMINHA] DO YOU KNOW WHO SHOWED UP AT THE CEMETERY CLAIMING THEMSELVES A FRIEND
FROM GENÉSIO AND WANTING TO OFFER ALL TYPES OF FINANCIAL HELP
FOR A WIDOW HERE? [MAX] HUM?
[CARMINHA] TYPHOON, FOOTBALL PLAYER.
[MAX] NO... WAIT, ARE YOU...
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT TYPHOON, THE FLAMENGUIST,
THE CHAMPIONSHIP GUNNER? [CARMINHA] HIMSELF.
IT'S NOT THAT HE GIVES A GRAVE TO THE SUCKER OF GENÉSIO AND STILL SENDS ME
A GIFT LIKE THIS, MAX? [MAX] BUT WAIT, TELL ME
ONE THING, BUT WAS THE TYPHOON A FRIEND OF GENESIO?
[CARMINHA] IF IT WAS OR WASN'T, I DON'T KNOW, THIS IS THE WHOLE STORY
VERY WEIRD, BUT ONE THING IS CERTAIN: I FEEL THERE IS A GAME
WITH THE FACE. WRITE WHAT I'M TELLING YOU, MAX,
I'M GOING TO MARRY THE TYPHOON.
[CARMINHA] HAVE YOU EVER IMAGINED ME, A FOOTBALL PLAYER’S WIFE?
FAMOUS, MAX? HUH, HUH? [LAUGHS]
WE'RE GOING TO BREAK THE BANK, MY LOVE.
[MAX] COME HERE, JUST A LITTLE, OKAY?
CAN YOU HAVE A LITTLE LITTLE RESPECT?
[CARMINHA] WHAT IS IT, MA X? ARE YOU GOING TO TEACH A MORAL LESSON NOW? YOU ARE CRAZY?
WHEN WILL ANOTHER OPPORTUNITY LIKE THIS FALL FROM THE SKY,
OF GOLDEN, SO WE CAN GET OUR HANDS ON GROWN PEOPLE’S MONEY?
[MAX] OKAY, AND WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO? MAY I STAY
HAPPY THAT MY WIFE IS GOING TO BED WITH ANOTHER MAN?
[CARMINHA] WERE YOU JEALOUS OF GENÉSIO? DID NOT HAVE.
SO, MY LOVE, SAME THING. [MAX] NO, IT'S NOT THE SAME THING,
NO, MA'AM, IT'S DIFFERENT. GENÉSIO WAS A CROWN,
THIS GUY IS A BIG BOY, ALMOST MY AGE, UNDERSTAND?
FOOTBALL PLAYER, RICH, FULL OF... LOOK, WE DIDN'T HAVE
ARRANGEMENT THAT WE GO TO SÃO PAULO, TO START A NEW LIFE,
AS SOON AS WE COULD GET SOME MONEY? READY.
WE HAVE ALREADY GOT THE MONEY, WE ALREADY HAVE EVERYTHING RIGHT.
NOW, WE MADE THIS SUCK, SHALL WE GET OUT?
[CARMINHA] WHAT A LOT? ONLY IF IT'S FOR YOU, MAX!
MIXURUCADA, FOR ME IT IS MIXURUCADA. THINK BIG.
TAKE A LOOK, TYPHOON, FOOTBALL STAR, MILLIONS OF DOLLARS,
PAINTED BIG FISH IN THE AREA.
[MAX] YOU'RE COMPLETELY CRAZY, YOU'RE FREAKING OUT,
YOU ARE CRAZY, DELIRIOUS, UNDERSTAND?
AND THEN, WHO GUARANTEES YOU THAT THIS GUY IS GOING TO MISS YOU?
HE TELLS ME. [CARMINHA] I UNDERSTAND MEN,
YOU KNOW THAT. I SAW IT IN HIS EYE
THAT HE IS NEEDY, UNSAFE,
IT'S PURE THE POOR THING...
IT'S GUILTY.
[CARMINHO] THAT'S IT, HE'S GUILTY,
AND THAT'S WHERE I CREATE MYSELF.
[MAX] LET ME JUST TELL YOU A QUICK QUICK:
WITH THESE 50 DICKS WE CAN JOIN SOCIETY
WITH THAT FRIEND OF MINE, THAT BROTHER I TOLD YOU ABOUT
AND WE'LL BE ABLE TO MAKE A COOL STOP.
[CARMINHA] SHUT UP, SHUT UP, MAX, SHUT UP.
HELP ME THINK HERE. WHY IS THIS TYPHOON SO GUILTY?
HE SAID THAT HE OWED GENESIO SOME MONEY, THAT GENESIO
IT HELPED HIM AT THE BEGINNING OF HIS CAREER, GENÉSIO NEVER TOLD ME
NONE OF THAT. AFTER, HE DIDN'T KNOW RIGHT WHERE IT WAS
THIS HOUSE HERE ON THE STREET. THEN I CAUGHT HIM IN A LYING
WHEN I COMMENTED THAT THE NAME OF THE FIRST WOMAN IN GENESIO
IT WAS HELENA, HE CONFIRMED. THE DECEASED CALLED MARTA.
[CARMINHA] THIS GUY DOESN'T KNOW WHO GENESIO IS.
THIS GUY NEVER MET GENÉSIO.
THEN WHY DID HE APPEAR AT THE CEMETERY?
WHY DOES HE WANT TO HELP ME SO MUCH?
[MAX] I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T KNOW, YOU'LL SEE...
GO SEE THIS TYPHOON ALSO GAVE A... A BLOW ON THE SUCKER
FROM GENÉSIO, THEN TYPHOON GOT RICH, GENÉSIO DIED,
THE BLAME... I DON'T KNOW, LET'S STOP TALKING ABOUT THIS GUY,
I'M STARVING, I WANT TO DRINK A BEER
AND LET'S DO IT... [CARMINHA] I KNOW! I ALREADY KNOW!
OH MY GOD, HOW DID I NOT THINK OF THIS BEFORE?
IT WAS THE TYPHOON THAT RUN OVER GENESIO!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME ROCK WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY RHYTHM♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪EVERYONE SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE EVERY NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU GET TIRED♪
♪STIR AND REMOVE♪
♪SCALES THAT'S CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COMES TO MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAY STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MOVE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪SCALES THAT'S CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COMES TO MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAY STILL♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
.