[SILENCE]
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE IT WAS HIM.
[CARMINHA] MAX, NO BO RECORD
THAT THE DRIVER WHO RAN OVER
GENÉSIO CALLED THE AMBULANCE,
BUT THEN IT DISAPPEARED.
THE AMBULANCE GUYS,
AT THE TIME, THEY SAW A FOUR BY
FOUR OVER THERE.
[CARMINHA] [LAUGHTER] TYPHOON HAS ONE
FOUR BY FOUR!
OH MY GOD I COULDN'T
BE EVERYTHING MORE PERFECT FOR ME.
[CARMINHA] BEYOND THE FIRST MANÉ
DON'T GIVE ANYTHING ABOUT ME TO THE POLICE,
THE SECOND SUCKER STILL STAYS
GUILTY OF HAVING RUN OVER
THE CUCKOLD HUSBAND,
AND LOOK FOR HIS WIDOW TO
OFFER HELP? [LAUGHTER]
SPEAK, MAX! SPEAK!
SAY THAT THE GUY UP THERE DOESN'T
GET INTO ME! SPEAK!
♪I WANT TO GIVE A GIFT♪
♪MY BEAUTIFUL MAIDEN♪
♪IT'S NOT SILVER, NOR IS IT GOLD♪
♪IT'S A VERY SIMPLE THING♪
[WOMAN] OH, AS IF. UI!
IT'S TIGHT IN HERE, HUH?
[ADAUTO] NO, IT'S YOU
SPACIOUS.
HERE, WRITE WHAT I'M TELLING YOU
SAYING, THIS YEAR,
WHEN IT IS DECEMBER 31, 99
PRA 2000,
AT MIDNIGHT, BOOM!
THE WORLD WILL EXPLODE,
THERE WILL BE NOBODY LEFT, WILL THERE BE NOBODY LEFT?
DIE ALL...
[SILAS] OK, OK, OK,
OK... OK, ADAUTO.
IN THE MEANWHILE, LET'S ENJOY AND
CATCH UP, OK?
[ADAUTO] AH, WE'LL GO THERE
DRINK, RIGHT?
[SILAS] HEY! [LAUGHTER]
[LELECO] WHAT'S UP?
[MURICY] LELECO, THE FEIJOADA
IT WAS FOR THE FAMILY, THE HOUSE IS
INFESTED WITH PENETRA.
[LELECO] WHAT PENETRATES?
[MURICY] LOOK AT THIS BUNCH OF
GROWN GUY THERE,
LOOTING THE HAM THAT I
I PREPARED IT FOR MY SON.
[LELECO] IS OUR FAN CLUB
SON, WIFE.
[MURICY] OH YEAH? THEN OK,
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO THEN?
I THINK I'LL PUT IT ON THE WHEEL
THOSE TWO KILOS OF DRUMET
OF CHICKEN THAT YOU SENT
OVER THERE IN THE FREEZER.
[LELECO] NO, NOT THE DRUMET, NO
GO PUT IT ON THE WHEEL, DON'T GO...
[MURICY] AH, I WILL, DO YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE IT'S FOR THE FAN CLUB
OF OUR SON, ISN'T IT? XI!
LOOK WHO'S HERE,
THE COUNTRY BRIDE, I THINK
TODAY I'M JUST GOING TO GET BORED.
[MONALISA] OH, LELECO, ARE YOU OK?
[LELECO] COME IN.
[MONALISA] DONA MURICY.
[MURICY] HI, MY DAUGHTER, GO
ARRIVING.
[MONALISA] HERE,
I BROUGHT MY EGG FAROFINHA
THAT THE TYPHOON LOVES. [LAUGHTER]
[MURICY] I DON'T KNOW WHAT A FAD
WHAT DO THESE PEOPLE HAVE TO BRING
FOOD, RIGHT? IT SEEMS LIKE WE
IS POOR,
THERE WILL BE A SHORTAGE OF FOOD, RIGHT?
[MONALISA] NO, IT WASN'T FOR
THAT.
[MURICY] THIS FAROFA IS DRY,
IT'S DRY, I THINK IT'S BETTER TO GO BACK
FOR THE FIRE WITH A LITTLE BACON,
OTHERWISE PEOPLE WILL CHOKE.
[Sledgehammer] MRS. MURICY, YOU
LELECO. I AM THE HAMMER.
[LELECO] WHO IS MARRETA?
[Sledgehammer] THAT PLAYED WITH TYPHOON.
[LELECO] HEY HAMMER!
[SLEDGEHAMMER] AND THIS ONE IS MINE
COUSIN, KENYA.
[LELECO] HERE YOU GO, KENYA
COME IN.
[KENYA] I WAS THE FIRST
TYPHOON'S GIRLFRIEND.
[MONALISA] IT IS CLEAR THAT THERE IS
A LONG TIME, RIGHT?
[MURICY] MONALISA! MONALISA,
THIS IS THE WAY TO TALK TO PEOPLE
PEOPLE?
[PARTY ATMOSPHERE]
[MONALISA] DONA MURICY, STAY
TREATING THESE PEOPLE WELL
THAT IN A LITTLE TIME IT WILL BE LIKE THIS
PREGNANT WOMAN
SAYING THAT THE TYPHOON IS THE FATHER, OK?
[DIOGENES] HEY GUYS, WHERE IS THE
TYPHOON, PEOPLE?
THIS BOY WILL NEVER ARRIVE?
[LELECO] DIOGENES, DIOGENES,
TYPHOON IS COMING,
DON'T WORRY, GO HAVE A TAKE
CAIPIRINHA THERE.
[DIOGENES] I'M GOING TO DRINK ONE
CAIPIRINHA.
[LELECO] WE'RE GOING... GOING,
GO, GO, MY BLACK GIRL...
[MURICY] OW!
[LELECO] LET'S DANCE, MY LOVE.
[MURICY] OH, OUR LADY. THIS
BREATH OF CACHACA, NOT EVEN DEAD,
GO LOOK FOR THE TYPHOON, GO
LOOK FOR THE TYPHOON,
LELECO, FOR ME, FOR THE LOVE OF
GOD, GO, SON, GO, GO.
TAKE YOUR HAND AWAY. OH MY GOD, I WISH
TO KNOW WHERE MY SON IS,
THAT'S ALL I WANTED TO KNOW.
[MONALISA] [STUTTERING] HE WAS
SOLVE A...
SOME LITTLE PROBLEMS FOR ME.
[MURICY] OH, YOU WERE SEEING ONE
THING, THEY HAVEN'T EVEN GET MARRIED YET
AND YOU'RE ALREADY GIVING WORK TO
MY SON DOES IT FOR YOU?
[LELECO] DON'T GET INVOLVED, MURICY.
[MURICY] NO, GUYS, SORRY,
BUT MY SON,
HE NEEDS TIME IN LIFE
HIS TO THINK ABOUT HIS CAREER,
TO THINK ABOUT HIS LIFE.
NO, NO, THIS THING IS NOT
IT'S WORKING, IT'S NOT WORKING.
[LELECO] WHAT'S NOT WORKING
RIGHT?
[MURICY] THIS IS TOO FAST
ENGAGEMENT, YOU KNOW?
IT'S TOO FAST. SHE STAYS
SPEAKING OF THE OTHER GIRLS,
BUT YOU'LL SEE THAT IT WAS HER WHO
GOT HER BELLY TO GET MARRIED QUICKLY,
IS THIS WHAT'S HAPPENING? IT'S BECAUSE
THIS IS WHAT MY SON IS NERVOUS ABOUT,
IT'S SO WEIRD
WAY? TELL ME.
[MONALISA] NO, DONA MURICY, THE
THERE IS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE TYPHOON PROBLEM
TO DO WITH MY BELLY NOT EVEN
WITH THE ENGAGEMENT,
THE LADY IS POSING WITH HAND
MASS, BUT YOU DON'T KNOW
NOTHING ABOUT YOUR CHILD'S LIFE.
IN FACT, YOU NEVER KNEW.
WHO TOOK THE TYPHOON OUT OF THE DRUNKENNESS,
WHO MADE HIM LOSE WEIGHT,
WHO TOOK HIM OUT OF THE BAD TIDE,
IT WASN'T YOU, NOR YOURS
HUSBAND, IT WAS ME, OK?
[LELECO] IT WAS HER, IT WAS HER, IT WAS
SHE, MURICY.
WE KNOW THAT, MONALISA.
[MURICY] WE KNOW WHAT?
PEOPLE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING,
THE ONLY THING I KNOW IS THAT THE
MY SON, YOU KNOW? HE DESERVED IT
A MUCH BETTER THING THAN
THIS RUDE MANICURIST.
[MONALISA] YOU'RE TAKING A LOT OF FUN
WHY, DONA MURICY?
UNTIL THE OTHER DAY YOU WERE
CAMEL.
AND THE LADY'S FATHER
IT SEEMS TO COME FROM PIAUÍ
ON A PAW'S PERCH, IT DIDN'T COME FROM
PLANE, NO. DID YOU COME BY PLANE?
[MURICY] MY DAUGHTER, BUT NOW
YOU LOST, SEE? YOU LOST.
BECAUSE I, DEAR, I WAS BORN IN
RIO DE JANEIRO,
I WAS BORN IN A HOSPITAL ROOM,
DID YOU UNDERSTAND IT?
I WASN'T BORN, JUST LIKE THAT, IN THE MIDDLE OF
CAATINGA
AND I WAS NOT EVEN SUCKLED BY A MULE,
YOU DID.
[TYPHOON] HEY, WHAT'S UP?
HAPPENING HERE?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
[LELECO] WHAT'S GOING ON
IT'S THAT... THAT, THAT
IT'S NOT HAPPENING, NOTHING, MY
SON. THE BEANS ARE HOT,
THE GORÓ IS GREAT, LET'S GO... LET'S GO
SING.
[TYPHOON] NO, FATHER, EXCUSE ME
THAT I HAVE TO SAY
WITH MONALISA. MONALISA, COME HERE.
[LELECO] GO THERE, MY DAUGHTER,
GO THERE.
[MURICY] THIS WOMAN IS
GETTING READY
OF OUR SON, HUH. BUT YOU
CAN WRITE
WHAT I'M SAYING, SHE IS
ARMANDO.
[MAN] SPEAK CRACK!
[TYPHOON] CLOSE IT, CLOSE IT,
MONA LISA.
[MONALISA] EXCUSE ME, EXCUSE ME
LICENSE.
IMAGINE TELL ME IF IT IS POSSIBLE,
ONE OF THE GREATEST PLAYERS IN BRAZIL
LIVING WITH PARENTS AND I LIVING
AT THE BACK OF MY SALON
IN A CUBICLE, OK? IMAGINE, IF THE
PEOPLE CAN'T EVEN GET PEACE
TO BE ABLE TO TALK,
IMAGINE DATING.
[TYPHOON] COME HERE, SIT HERE,
MY QUEEN, PAY ATTENTION,
I JUST ARRIVED FROM EUROPE,
I HAVEN'T HAD TIME YET,
I'LL BUY OURS SOON
APARTMENT, WE DATE
IN THE LIVING ROOM, IN THE BEDROOM, IN THE HALLWAY,
IN THE BEDS, WHEREVER YOU WANT.
[MONALISA] OK, OK. SO,
THEN, HE WENT THERE AND FOUND THE WIDOW
FROM THE GUY? DID YOU TALK TO HER?
[TYPHOON] IT WAS HORRIBLE.
[MONALISA] WHY? SHE GOT IT
THAT YOU RUN OVER YOUR HUSBAND
HER? WHAT DID YOU SAY?
[TYPHOON] NO, I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING,
MONALISA, BUT SHE WAS
CRYING, I WAS SAD, I WAS
SUFFERING A LOT, DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
[MONALISA] BUT WHAT ARE YOU?
DID YOU TELL HER?
[TYPHOON] WELL, LIKE "WHAT I
I SAID", I SAID WHAT WE
AGREED, THAT I WAS A FRIEND
FROM HIM, BUT YEARS AGO
THAT I DIDN'T SEE HIM.
[MONALISA] BUT DID SHE BELIEVE?
[TYPHOON] FA... I... GAVE THE
LUCKIEST, THEY FINISHED
TO MARRY, SHE IS VERY
YOUNGER THAN HIM.
[MONALISA] NO, BUT SHE... SHE IS
YOUNG? IS SHE LIKE A LITTLE GIRL?
[TYPHOON] NO, IT'S NOT A LITTLE GIRL, IT'S
NEWER, NEWER. THEN...
[MONALISA] HUM... MORE...
MORE BEAUTIFUL?
[TYPHOON] MY GOD IN HEAVEN,
MONALISA, WHAT IS THIS?
MAN, I'LL BE GOOD ATTENTION
ATTENTION? I WAS NERVOUS
HOLY SHIT, DO YOU THINK THAT
I WILL KEEP REPAIR
IS THE GIRL PRETTY?
IT BROKE MY HEART WHEN I
I ARRIVED THERE AT THE CEMETERY,
LOOKING AT HER, CRYING FOR
DAMN, THEN TAKE HER
TO HER HOUSE WHERE THEY GO
THEY LIVED AND THEIR LIFE
TOGETHER, DO YOU THINK IT'S EASY?
[MONALISA] DID SHE HAVE A CHILD?
[TYPHOON] THANK GOD THERE WASN'T ANY
CHILD, AT LEAST THAT.
NO CHILD, NO CHILD.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[JESSICA] NOT THAT, REMEMBER? THERE IS
TO COLLECT GLASS, CANS AND PAPER
HARD. THAT'S WHAT PAYS WELL.
FIRST DAY IS HARD, AFTER
YOU GET USED TO IT.
[RITA] BUT I'M NOT
FROM HERE, I HAVE A HOUSE.
[JESSICA] NOBODY IS FROM HERE, FOOL,
WE'VE BEEN HERE FOR A WHILE.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD. OH, OKAY
ARE I SELLING THIS JACKET?
I LOOKED IN THE TRASH. YOU'LL FIND IT
LOTS OF GOOD STUFF IN THE TRASH TOO.
COME ON, COME ON, LET'S GO AND PICK UP.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MAN] FIVE REAIS.
[MAN] 11 REAIS.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NILO] WHO HIDE THE MONEY
UNCLE IS PUNISHED, HUH?
SEVERE PUNISHMENT.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NILO] SIX REAIS? THAT'S ALL?
ARE YOU SURE?
GO.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[RITA] WE DON'T
NEVER REST?
[JESSICA] WE ALMOST DIDN'T
REST, WE WORK
ALL DAY LONG. THE NILE LIKES IT
A LOT OF MONEY.
[TALK]
[RITA] AND THOSE CHILDREN?
CAN THEY PLAY?
[JESSICA] THESE CHILDREN ARE
CHILDREN DIFFERENT FROM US,
THEY ARE THE LUCKY BOYS.
THEY'RE LUCINDA'S BOYS.
[LUCINDA] OH, KIDS! HERE
SANDWICH, HERE, KIDS!
STOP, STOP, STOP, LET'S EAT,
COME ON, POTATO, GET IT NOW
YOUR SANDWICH HERE. OH,
YUMMY! [LAUGHTER]
GIVE A KISS, GIVE A KISS, GIVE A KISS.
[POTATO] WANT TO PLAY?
[POTATO] WOW, YOU'RE SO MUCH
SERIOUSLY, HUH?
[RITA] LEAVE ME!
[POTATO] IS COOL...
[RITA] GO AWAY! MY BAG!
[POTATO] [LAUGHTER] COME AND GET IT.
[RITA] [LAUGHTER] I GOT IT.
[POTATO] OK. YOU'RE GOOD
RACING, HUH?
[RITA] YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S A NAIL.
[POTATO] OH, YOU FOOL. I WANT TO
I LET YOU CATCH ME.
[RITA] LIE.
[POTATO] TRUE.
[SCREAMS]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[NILE] COME HERE! COME HERE!
DO YOU WANT TO EXPLAIN TO ME THAT
IS THIS A CLOWN?
WHY ARE YOU NOT THERE?
WORKING
WITH YOUR LITTLE FRIENDS, HUH?
WHERE'S THE BAG I GAVE YOU
FILLING UP WITH TRASH? WHERE'S THE BAG?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY RHYTHM♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK IT♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[NILO] HAVE YOU LOST YOUR LANGUAGE?
WHERE'S THE BAG I GAVE YOU?
WHY ARE YOU NOT THERE?
WORKING
WITH YOUR LITTLE FRIENDS? I WANT
KNOW! WHAT DO YOU THINK?
FOOD FALLS FROM THE SKY, HUH?
MADAM?
HERE THERE IS ONLY ONE LAW: WHOEVER DOESN'T
WORK, DON'T EAT.
[POTATO] LET GO OF HER, NILO! WIDE
SHE!
[NILO] BUT YOU NEED IT
A SCRATCH, HUH?
I MISS GIVING SOME BEAUTIFUL
A FEW FLAPS, HUH, KID?
[LUCINDA] ENOUGH, NILO!
[NILO] THIS KID IS
IN NEED OF A CONCEALER.
[LUCINDA] HE'S MY PROBLEM.
[POTATO] DON'T LET THE NILE DO IT
EVIL
WITH MY FRIEND, LUCINDA.
[LUCINDA] YOU HAVE A FRIEND
NEW? WHAT'S HER NAME?
[RITA] MY NAME IS RITA.
[NILO] RITA, GO TO WORK,
LET'S GET TO WORK.
[POTATO] DON'T LET HIM DO IT
THAT'S IT, MOTHER LUCINDA.
[LUCINDA] IT'S NO USE, WE
CAN'T DO ANYTHING,
YOU KNOW THE LAW OF GARBAGE. I AM
KEEPING AN EYE ON YOU, OK, NILO?
[NILO] WHAT'S UP, LUCINDA, WHAT'S UP?
WE DON'T MATCH? HERE, EACH
ONE MESSES WITH YOUR LIFE. AH!
LET'S WORK, LET'S WORK,
LET'S WORK, LET'S WORK!
[LUCINDA] LET'S GO. LET'S GO. WE
YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING, NO.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LAUGHTER]
[MONALISA] OH, WAIT, WHAT?
AGONY! LET ME OPEN MY EYES.
LET ME OPEN MY EYES.
[TYPHOON] "TCHARAM"!
[MONALISA] CHAMPION! WHAT A PLACE
IT'S THAT?
[TYPHOON] THIS HERE, MY
PRINCESS, IT'S A SUITE
PRESIDENTIAL, MY FIRST
LADY. SO, IT IS...
[MONALISA] PEOPLE, THIS IS
A PALACE.
[TYPHOON] YOUR MAJESTY, WANT TO
A CHAMPAGNE?
LIKED THE SURPRISE?
[MONALISA] I LOVED IT, I LOVED IT.
WAIT, I'LL HELP YOU.
[TYPHOON] GET USED TO IT... WHY
THIS CRAP DOESN'T WANT TO OPEN?
GET USED TO IT, BECAUSE FROM NOW ON
AGAINST
YOUR LIFE WILL BE LIKE THIS, MY
LOVE.
[MONALISA] THAT'S IT. [SCREAMING]
[TYPHOON] HEY! [LAUGHTER] NOW I'M GOING
SERVE YOU...
[LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] A "FLÛTE".
[MONALISA] OH, IT WILL SERVE THE
WHAT?
[TYPHOON] A "FLÛTE".
[MONALISA] A "FLÛTE"?
YUM! "FLÛTE" IS PRETTY. IT SMELLS
GOOD.
[TYPHOON] SMELL?
[MONALISA] AND "TIM-TIM". HUM! UH!
[TYPHOON] IT'S BAD, RIGHT?
[MONALISA] IT'S TOO BAD, YOU
DO YOU HAVE A COLD BEER THERE?
[TYPHOON] I TOOK A LONG TIME TOO
GODDAMN I'M GETTING USED TO IT
WITH CHAMPAGNE, ONLY AFTER I
I PLAYED AT PARIS SAINT-GERMAIN
THAT I HAVE LEARNED TO LIKE. NOW,
NOT YOU, MY PRINCESS,
YOU WILL GET USED TO IT SINCE
NOW WITH LUXURY
AND WITH WEALTH, BECAUSE, OF
FROM NOW ON,
YOUR LIFE WILL BE LIKE THIS.
[MONALISA] OH, I MATCH WITH
THIS HERE,
I AGREE. DID YOU KNOW THAT ONCE A
FORTUNE TELLER TOLD ME
THAT IN AN INCARNATION I WAS A
QUEEN?
I THINK SHE'S RIGHT.
[TYPHOON] REALLY?
[MONALISA] WOW.
[TYPHOON] MY LOVE, I WANT YOU TO
YOU SEE THE HOUSE
THAT I WANT TO BUY FOR US.
LATER, WHEN THE CHILDREN COME,
THEN YOU WILL HAVE EVERYTHING
WHATEVER YOU WANT,
YOU CAN EVEN TAKE A BREAK FROM THAT
YOUR SALON.
[MONALISA] NO, NO, NO,
NO, I DON'T WANT TO TAKE TIME OFF,
NO WAY. NO, IMAGINE!
I AM NOT A WOMAN I WAS BORN TO BE
STAY IN BARRA
IN MEN'S PANTS, NO, NOT ME
I'M A SLAVE.
MY LIFE IS SALON.
LOOK, I'LL PROVE TO YOU THAT I
I CAN MAKE A LOT OF MONEY
WITH MY FORMULA OF
SMOOTHING,
WHEN I OPENED MY SALON. I
I ALREADY HAVE SOME OF THE MONEY.
[TYPHOON] I HAVE THE OTHER PART,
I'LL LEND IT TO YOU, YOU OPEN THE SALON.
[MONALISA] NO WAY.
IF NOT, YOUR MOTHER WILL STAY
GETTING FUCKED UP,
SAYING THAT I'M ALREADY GETTING INTO IT
HAND ON YOUR MONEY.
[TYPHOON] WHAT MY MOTHER WHAT?
ARE YOU THINKING THAT I'M DOING IT?
SYMPATHY FOR YOU, GIRL? I
I BELIEVE,
IT'S A GOOD DEAL FOR ME, YOU KNOW
WHY?
BECAUSE I KNOW YOURS
STRAIGHTENING. DO YOU UNDERSTAND? IT'S BRILLIANT.
A BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY FOR
ME.
WE OPEN TOGETHER, WE TURN
PARTNER. HALF YOURS, HALF MINE.
[MONALISA] I DON'T KNOW, LET'S SEE,
LET'S SEE, LET'S SEE.
[TYPHOON] DO YOU THINK WITH LOVE?
[MONALISA] I'LL THINK ABOUT IT, BUT NO
I WILL THINK ABOUT BUSINESS
NOT NOW. [LAUGHTER] NOW WE
GO TRY THIS BED.
[TYPHOON] AH... THERE, YES. THERE
YOU THINK ABOUT IT LATER
IN OUR BUSINESS WITH LOVE.
[SILENCE]
[STEPS]
[NILE] [MOAN]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CHILD] NO, STOP, NO
I HID NOTHING.
[NILO] TAKE OFF YOUR SHOES.
[CHILD] NO, THERE IS NOTHING
IN THE SHOE.
[NILO] HOW IS THERE NOT? LET'S SEE.
[CHILD] NO, NO.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[NILO] WHAT IS THIS HERE? WHAT
WHAT IS THIS HERE?
LIE HAS SHORT LEGS! WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS IT?
CAN YOU EXPLAIN TO ME WHAT THIS IS?
HERE, YOU LOUSE?
CAN YOU EXPLAIN ME?
[CHILD] NO, PLEASE,
NO, I APOLOGIZE.
[NILO] YOU HAVE NOTHING TO ASK FOR
SORRY, NO! GO TO WORK!
GO TO WORK!
[CHILD] I'M HUNGRY.
[NILO] GO TO WORK HUNGRY! AND
IF YOU DON'T BRING 10 REAIS,
DON'T EAT! COME ON! EVERYONE
WORKING, FOOD IS OUT!
EVERYBODY WORKING! EVERYBODY
WORLD!
COME ON, I WANT TO SEE THE BAG FULL OF
TRASH!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[NILO] COME ON, COME ON, COME ON, I WANT
SEE THE FULL GARBAGE BAG!
I'M SICK OF IT! LET'S GO, LET'S GO, LET'S GO,
YOU GANG, I'M SICK OF IT!
I'M SICK OF IT!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CHILD] THANK YOU.
[NILO] [SHOUTING] DON'T GO!
NOBODY HELP HER!
LEAVE HER THERE, IT'S GOOD FOR
LEARN.
I WANT TO SEE EVERYONE SINGING
TRASH, LET'S GO!
LET'S GET FUCKED UP! I WANT TO SEE
SICK OF IT! SICK OF IT!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MAX] IS GETTING READY FOR YOUR
LITTLE SOCCER PLAYER, HUH?
[CARMINHA] DOESN'T GET FULL.
[MAX] [LAUGHTER] SEE THERE, HUH. NO
YOU WILL DO A LOT OF THINGS,
OTHERWISE IT WILL END
SUSPICIOUS.
REMEMBER YOU JUST LOST
YOUR HUSBAND.
[CARMINHA] MAKEUP OK
DISCREET, DRESSED TOO.
[MAX] I DON'T KNOW IF YOU ARE
CALLING THAT NECKLINE
DISCREETLY, I DON'T KNOW. YOU WHAT
HE KNOWS.
[CARMINHA] EMPTY TALK,
DUDE. ARE YOU CRAZY?
COME HERE, DID YOU FIND OUT EVERYTHING? DID YOU FIND OUT EVERYTHING
ABOUT TYPHOON LIFE?
DETAILS, DETAILS, I WANT
DETAILS, HOW MUCH DOES HE EARN?
[MAX] DO YOU WANT ME TO START?
FOR THE GOOD PART
OR THE BAD PART?
[CARMINHA] THE GOOD ONE, OF COURSE.
[MAX] WELL, THE GOOD THING IS THAT HE
EARN 100K, PLUS ADVERTISING.
AND THE BAD THING, MY LOVE, IS THAT
HE'S ENGAGED.
[CARMINHA] DO YOU KNOW WHOSE?
[MAX] I KNOW, FROM A HAIRDRESSER,
MANICURE, PARAIBAN.
[CARMINHA] PARAIBAN MANICURE?
[LAUGHTER] THINGS WILL BE MORE
EASIER THAN I THOUGHT.
[MAX] UH-HUM. IT LOOKS LIKE THIS
PARAIBANA IS ARRIVED.
[MONALISA] WHAT IS THIS LIKE?
HERE? HADDOCK TO THE "BERENOARE"?
[TYPHOON] NO, ASK FOR THIS ONE,
Oh, "STEAK AU POIVRE",
THIS ONE IS GOOD.
[MONALISA] IS IT GOOD?
[TYPHOON] I ATE IN FRANCE.
[MONALISA] I'M GOING TO ASK NO, YOU KNOW
WHAT DID I REALLY WANT?
CHICKEN DRUMSTICK.
[TYPHOON] STUFFED WITH CHEESE.
[LAUGHTER] LET'S ASK, IT'S DONE.
I'M GOING TO GO OUT, MY LOVE.
[MONALISA] WELL, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[TYPHOON] OH, I PROMISED YOU
OLD MAN'S WIDOW
THAT I WAS GOING TO TAKE HER TO
BARBECUE RESTAURANT.
[MONALISA] HEY, TYPHOON, WHAT'S IT LIKE?
WHAT IS IT? WE ARE CELEBRATING
HERE IS YOUR CHAMPIONSHIP, BIGGER
ROMANTIC ATMOSPHERE,
YOU WILL GO OUT TO POWER
FIND THAT WOMAN?
[TYPHOON] I JUST PROMISED HER,
MY LOVE, I PROMISED,
THE WOMAN IS A WRECK. AT LEAST,
I KNEW THAT 12H
YOU WERE GOING TO TRY YOURS THERE
DRESS
AND I COULDN'T GO WITH YOU, RIGHT,
NO?
I NEED TO ALLEVIATE THIS GUILT.
TAKE A LITTLE
THIS WEIGHT OFF MY SHOULDERS,
DID YOU UNDERSTAND?
BUT TODAY I WILL PUT A STONE
ON THIS SUBJECT.
THINKING ABOUT GIVING HER A HOUSE.
[MONALISA] A HOUSE?
[TYPHOON] Yes.
[MONALISA] YES, A HOUSE CAN BE
A REALLY GOOD ONE.
[TYPHOON] I KILLED HER HUSBAND,
I ENDED HER LIFE,
YOU HAVE TO PAY FOR THIS. NOW,
MY LOVE, DON'T WORRY,
I GO AND COME BACK QUICKLY,
TRY ON YOUR DRESS
AND ON THE WAY BACK WE WILL CELEBRATE
IN THIS MANSION, IN THIS PALACE,
NO TIME TO END, OK?
[MONALISA] OK, I UNDERSTAND,
SEE? BUT IT GOES AND COMES BACK FAST!
[TYPHOON] ASKS FOR EVERYTHING
IT'S CHICKEN DRUMSTICK.
I WILL BE BACK SOON,
MY... MY QUEEN.
[KISS SNAP]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NILO] THAT'S IT?
[RITA] THAT'S IT.
[NILO] YOU HAVE TO LEARN
TO PICK UP TRASH RIGHT. OH!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[RITA] GIRL, GIVE ME ONE.
[RITA] JESSICA!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] I SEE THAT YOU
HE IS A MAN OF HIS WORD.
[TYPHOON] I DIDN'T SAY THAT
VINHA? 2PM SHARP.
SO, ARE WE GOING TO EAT THAT CHULETA?
[CARMINHA] SORRY, BUT NO
GIVE. I DON'T HAVE THE CONDITIONS
TO LEAVE HOME.
[TYPHOON] COME ON, IT WILL BE
QUICKLY, "BANG".
[CARMINHA] IT REALLY DOESN'T WORK,
THANK YOU SO MUCH. WHAT I MOST
I WANT TO LOCK MYSELF IN A ROOM
DARK AND WAIT FOR THIS PAIN
THAT I FEEL IN MY SOUL IMPROVING.
[TYPHOON] DID YOU EAT SOMETHING?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] I CAN FIND MYSELF, YOU CAN
LEAVE, DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME,
NO. GO HOME,
COME BACK TO YOUR LIFE.
[TYPHOON] YOU DIDN'T EAT
NOTHING, RIGHT? COME, COME HERE.
[CARMINHA] HOW CAN I
EAT? HOW CAN I
EAT? [CRYING] I LOST IT
MY HUSBAND YESTERDAY, MY GOD,
MY LIFE IS OVER.
[TYPHOON] IT'S... LOOK AT YOU
YOU NEED TO FEED, COME HERE,
COME HERE, LET'S GO... LET ME, LET ME
TAKE YOU, COME WITH ME, YOU
NEED TO FEED, NEED TO
EAT, GIRL. COME HERE, IT WILL BE
QUICKLY. HERE WE GO, HERE WE GO,
IT'S HALF AN HOUR, IT'S "PA-PUM",
YOU NEED TO EAT, YOU NEED TO
FEED. SOON,
YOU COME HOME. EMPTY BAG
DOESN'T STAND UP. SO, IT WILL BE
QUICKLY, IN HALF AN HOUR
YOU'RE HOME AGAIN.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CAR ENGINE]
[STEPS]
[NILO] YOU STILL DON'T. AH,
STILL LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT,
IS IT, JESSICA? [LAUGHTER] TELL ME, WHO
WHO GAVE YOU FOOD,
HUH, LITTLE LICE? TELL ME,
WHO GAVE YOU FOOD?
[JESSICA] NOBODY, NOBODY
HELPED ME.
[NILO] OF COURSE IT HELPED. YOU WERE
DRAGING HERSELF, ALL DIZZY
HUNGRY, NOW I'M ALREADY
FACING. BETTER SAY
WHO HELPED YOU, SAY.
WAIT, I HAVE
A GOOD LITTLE THING
I KNOW YOU'LL LIKE IT.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[NILE] OH, JESSICA! [LAUGHTER]
COOKIE, BRAND NEW, BRAND NEW.
WHOLE BAG, ONLY
FOR YOU, GET IT.
THERE'S MORE, LOOK. THIS LITTLE OVERALL,
LOOK AT THIS BEAUTIFUL LITTLE OVERALL.
IT'S BRAND NEW, I FOUND IT IN THE TRASH,
BUT I ALREADY WASHED IT, IT'S CLEAN.
THERE IS ONE MORE THING, THAT
I KNOW YOU WERE CRAZY
FOR HER, THE SANDALINHA.
[JESSICA] CAN YOU GIVE ME THE SANDAL?
[NILE] NOW.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[JESSICA] IT WAS HER, IT WAS RITA.
[NILO] YOU'VE JUST ARRIVED AND YOU'RE ALREADY
GETTING READY, RIGHT? BUT THERE'S NO WAY
PROBLEM, NO, YOU WILL
LEARN THE HARD WAY.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RITA] GET OUT OF HERE, YOU
PILE OF TRASH.
[NILO] BUT HOW SOMEONE IS SHE?
SAME...
OH! OH, YOU WRETCH, THAT I
GOT IT. GET OUT OF THE WAY, YOU BITCH!
RITA! YOU BAD LITTLE GIRL, YOU
I'LL GET YOU, YOU BITCH, COME HERE.
RITA! DON'T RUN AWAY, RITA! RITA.
GET THIS CRAP OFF
TRUCK IN FRONT OF ME!
GET OUT OF HERE! RITA! RITA! I LOVE YOU!
I CATCH YOU, YOU LITTLE GIRL,
I'LL GET YOU. YOU BITCH... NO
THERE'S NO USE IN HIDING.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[NILO] RITA! THERE'S NO USE IN
TO HIDE,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING TO RUN AWAY? YOU ARE GOING TO
HAVE TO GO BACK...
YOU WILL DISAPPEAR, YOU WILL STAY WITH
HUNGER...
YOU WILL KNOCK ON THE DOOR OF THE HOUSE
AND YOU'LL HAVE TO BEG ME
OPEN THE DOOR.
WHERE ARE YOU, RITA?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
YOU'LL HAVE TO SHOW UP, BECAUSE
YOU WILL STARVE TO DEATH
HERE IN THE TRASH!
YOU WILL WANT TO EAT AND YOU WILL
TO BEG
FOR ME TO OPEN THE DOOR OF MY
HOME!
YOU WILL HAVE TO HUMBLE YOURSELF IN MINE
FRONT...
THEN WE WILL BE ACCOUNTABLE, THEN
WE WILL BE ACCOUNTABLE. RITA!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[CLICKING OF CUTLERY]
[TYPHOON] WHY DON'T YOU EAT ONE
LITTLE? IT WILL BE GOOD FOR YOU.
[CLICKING OF CUTLERY]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] SORRY, NO
I CAN. IMPOSSIBLE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] I'LL HAVE A WHISKEY
IF YOU FOLLOW ME.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] I'LL FOLLOW YOU. WAITER!
TWO WHISKIES.
[CARMINHA] YOU REALLY ARE A
VERY CHARITABLE SOUL,
TYPHOON.
IT'S YOUR CUSTOM TO HELP WIDOWS
LONELY LIKE ME?
[TYPHOON] IT'S NOT THAT, IT'S THAT THE
GENÉSIO HAS ALWAYS BEEN A GUY
VERY... VERY IMPORTANT IN
MY LIFE,
I AM SURE THAT WHERE
WANT HIM TO BE...
HE WOULD BE PLEASED THAT I
I'M ON YOUR SIDE RIGHT NOW.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] [VOICE OVERWHELMED] LET'S GO
MAKE A TOAST TO GENÉSIO?
[TYPHOON] TO GENESIO.
[GLASS CLAPPING]
[CARMINHA] GENESIO, MY
GENESINHO.
MY LIFE COMPANION.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] LIKED CHILDREN
MORE THAN ANYTHING IN LIFE.
IT'S A PITY HE DIDN'T HAVE CHILDREN.
[SNIFLE]
WE PLANNED TO HAVE IT.
[TYPHOON] DID YOU PLAN?
[CARMINHA] I'M... WANT TO
TO SAY...
I WAS UNDERGOING TREATMENT FOR
THAT.
IT WAS OUR BIGGEST DREAM, BUT NOW
IT'S TOO LATE.
I THREW IN THE TOWEL.
[TYPHOON] DON'T SAY A THING
THIS. RIGHT? [LAUGHTER]
WE NEVER... KNOW THAT
LIFE HAS IN STORE FOR US,
YOU MAY BE SURPRISED.
[CARMINHA] WHAT A SURPRISE?
MY LIFE IS OVER,
MY LIFE PROJECT.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] THIS SON OF MINE WITH
GENESIO WOULD GROW
IN A HAPPY HOME, A HOME
PERFECT, WITH A...
A FATHER AND A MOTHER WHO WOULD LOVE
HE MORE THAN ANYTHING IN LIFE,
WHO LOVED EACH OTHER MORE THAN ANYTHING
IN LIFE.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN MARRIED?
[TYPHOON] NO.
[CARMINHA] SO YOU DON'T
DO YOU KNOW WHAT LUCK IS?
TO FIND A HAPPY MARRIAGE.
[SIGH] EVERY SINGLE DAY
MAN SURPRISED ME,
HE ALWAYS CAME TO ME WITH A GIFT,
THERE WAS NO ROUTINE WITH GENÉSIO,
FOR GENESIO LIFE WAS ONE
ADVENTURE,
WHEN I LEAST EXPECTED IT HE CAME TO ME
I GRAB HIM BY THE ARM
AND HE TOOK ME TO A THEATER, TO
A CINEMA,
FOR A ROMANTIC DINNER, FOR A
UNEXPECTED JOURNEY
THAT HE PREPARED FOR ME
HIDDEN...
[CRYING] OW!
[CRYING] THEN A CAR CAME.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] AND STARTS
THE LIFE OF OUR LOVE.
GO, GO.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] A CRETIN, AN IDIOT
ANY
WHO DOESN'T KNOW WHAT HE'S DOING
DRIVING A CAR.
A KILLER DOES THIS TO
PEOPLE.
I DON'T EVEN LIKE TO THINK ABOUT IT.
I THINK I'D BETTER GO HOME
I'M NOT FEELING WELL.
[TYPHOON] [STUTTERING] I LOVE YOU
I TAKE IT. WAITER! TELL US.
[CARMINHA] OH!
[NILO] [SHOUTING] YOU GO TO SLEEP
IN THE TRASH, HUH, RITA!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NILE] RITA!
[NILO] I'LL WAIT FOR YOU AT HOME,
HUH?
WE'LL TALK LATER, WAIT
WE CAN TALK!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CRY]
[POTATO] HEY, YOU!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[POTATO] DON'T BE SAD. COME
WITH ME, WE WILL BE HAPPY.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] I DIDN'T WANT TO GO IN
AT HOME ALONE.
COME IN, PLEASE.
[DOOR CLOSE]
[CARMINHA] IT'S VERY STRANGE
GET HOME AT THIS TIME
AND NOT LISTEN TO MY LITTLE VOICE
GENESIO CALLING.
ONCE AGAIN, I... I REALLY
I DO NOT KNOW HOW TO THANK YOU.
[TYPHOON] YOU DON'T HAVE TO THANK ME.
[THUNDER]
[TYPHOON] AH... I HAVE TO GO
ALTHOUGH.
[THUNDER]
[CARMINHA] I KNOW I DON'T
I HAVE THE RIGHT TO ASK YOU FOR THIS.
[TYPHOON] YOU CAN ASK.
[CARMINHA] ONE MORE LEFT
A LITTLE?
JUST UNTIL I GET USED TO IT
IDEA
TO BE ALONE IN THIS HOUSE,
15 MINUTES ONLY... ONLY UNTIL
RAIN PASS, PLEASE.
[TYPHOON] OK.
YES, I'LL STAY A LITTLE LONGER.
[CARMINHA] I'M GOING TO MAKE ONE
WHISKEY.
[TYPHOON] HUM...
[BELL]
[DOOR OPEN]
[MONALISA] AH.
[SCRACKLING OF WHEELS]
[MAN] GOOD EVENING, MADAM.
[MONALISA] GOOD NIGHT, GOOD NIGHT.
[SCRACKLING OF WHEELS]
[MAN] DINNER.
[MONALISA] CHICKEN DRUMSTICK AND
CHICKEN BROILED, IT'S GOOD.
[LAUGHTER] I BET NOBODY EVER
YOU ASKED FOR THIS, HUH,
TELL THE TRUTH. [LAUGHTER]
[MAN] EXCUSE ME. A GOOD
NIGHT.
[MONALISA] SORRY, GOOD NIGHT.
[DOOR CLOSE]
[MONALISA] MY GOD IN HEAVEN,
WHERE IS TYPHOON?
[TYPHOON] [STUTTERING] NO, I
I'M... I'M NOT... SATISFIED.
[CARMINHA] JUST A LITTLE MORE.
[CUP FILLING]
[CARMINHA] A HOLY REMEDY.
[ICE FRICTION IN THE GLASS]
[TYPHOON] WHAT DAY WILL IT WIN?
THE RENT OF THIS HOUSE?
[CARMINHA] NEXT WEEK.
[TYPHOON] SO, HOW WAS I
SAYING,
IT IS... I WANTED TO HELP YOU
FIND A HOUSE
IN THESE VICINITY...
[CARMINHA] [SIGH] FORGET IT
THAT, FORGET IT...
[TYPHOON] NO, NO, YOU
ALREADY...
YOU CAN START SEARCHING NOW
A HOUSE, IF YOU WANT.
♪HITS AGAIN♪
♪WITH HOPES♪
♪MY HEART♪
[CARMINHA] IT'S THE MUSIC
FAVORITE OF GENESIO.
AT THIS TIME, HE MUST BE THERE
SKY
WITH A SAMBA CIRCLE WITH
TOPPER.
[CARMINHA] I WISH I WAS THERE
ALSO.
[TYPHOON] NO, DON'T SPEAK...
LOOK, WAIT,
DON'T TALK NONSENSE, OK?
I HAVE A FRIEND WHO IS... WHO IS
BROKER,
HE CAN HELP YOU...
[CARMINHA] NO LONGER NEEDS
HOME, YOU DON'T NEED ANYTHING ELSE.
[CLUTTERED VOICE] GENÉSIO IS ME
WAITING,
I WANT TO GO AWAY, MY GOD.
[CRYING] I WANT TO LEAVE.
I THOUGHT...
"CARMINHA, YOU CAN'T DO IT
A NONSENSE,"
BUT IS IT STUPID? I
I DON'T THINK IT'S NONSENSE.
I THINK IT'S THE RIGHT THING TO DO
TO DO.
[TYPHOON] NO, NO, NO
HE SPEAKS...
WAIT, DON'T SAY THAT,
YOU HAVE YOUR WHOLE LIFE FOR
GO AHEAD, DON'T SAY THAT.
[CARMINHA] [VOICE OVERWHELMED] THAT
A WHOLE LIFE AHEAD OF YOU?
TELL ME, GENESIO IS NO LONGER
HERE.
IF I LEAVE, NOBODY WILL GIVE
FOR LACK OF ME...
[TYPHOON] YES YOU WILL... YES YOU WILL
YOU WILL FIND A PERSON,
YOU WILL BE HAPPY,
BECAUSE YOU'RE YOUNG AND YOU'RE
BEAUTIFUL. DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
[CARMINHA] YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHAT AM I SAYING, MAN
GOD IN HEAVEN?
GOD WRITES RIGHT BY LINES
PIES,
ISN'T THAT WHAT THE BIBLE SAYS?
[CARMINHA] AND HE TOOK MY
HUSBAND.
[VOICE OVERWHELMED] WHAT THE FUCK?
IS THIS GOD WHO DOES THIS TO ME?
♪I'M SURE I SHOULD♪
[CARMINHA] OH MY GOD, I DON'T
I CAN THINK SO.
I CAN'T THINK LIKE THIS, THAT'S
A BLASPHEMY,
MY GOD, IT'S BLASPHEMY!
[CRY]
[CARMINHA] I AM CATHOLIC, I
I HAVE GOD,
THIS IS HOW I HAVE TO THINK.
[TYPHOON] YOU HAVE ME TOO.
YOU HAVE A FRIEND HERE FOR
ANY TIME.
[RAIN]
[CARMINHA] CAN I MAKE YOU ONE?
ORDER AMOUNT?
[TYPHOON] YOU CAN. OF COURSE.
[RAIN]
[CARMINHA] [WHISPERING] SINCE
THAT GENESIO DIED,
I DIDN'T GO INTO THE ROOM.
CAN YOU COME IN THERE WITH ME?
[RAIN]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] GENESIO LAY DOWN
ALWAYS ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF THE BED.
[TYPHOON] WANT ME TO GET ONE
WATER FOR YOU?
A SLEEPING PILL?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[STEPS]
[CARMINHA] DO YOU KNOW WHAT I
I REALLY WANTED?
THAT YOU WOULD LAY IN BED, IN
SIDE OF GENESIO
AND STAY LAY DOWN UNTIL I FELL ASLEEP.
[CRYING] I CAN'T STAY
ALONE NOW.
NOT IN THIS ROOM, MY GOD, NO
WITH THIS RAIN.
I CAN'T, MY GOD, I'M
SO HELPLESS.
[CRY]
OH MY GOD.
I'M SORRY, I KNOW I DON'T
I HAVE THE RIGHT
TO ASK YOU FOR THIS. WE ARE OVER
TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
[TYPHOON] ALL RIGHT, I... I
I'LL LAY DOWN A LITTLE BIT HERE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] LAY DOWN.
[CARMINHA] OH, PLEASE, ME
HUGS.
[CRYING] I MISS YOU SO MUCH
HIS, MY GOD.
I MISS HIM SO MUCH.
[CRY]
[CARMINHA] THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, MY JESUS.
THANKS THANKS THANKS,
THANK YOU THANK YOU,
YOU ARE AN ANGEL, MY GOD. IT WAS
GENESIO THAT BROUGHT YOU.
IT WAS GENÉSIO WHO SENT YOU HERE
TO SAVE ME.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY PACE♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
.