[SILENCE]
[POTATO] COME ON, COME WITH ME.
[RITA] I'M NOT GOING.
[POTATO] YOU MUST BE DYING
HUNGRY.
[RITA] GO AWAY.
[POTATO] IF YOU STAY THERE, YOU
YOU WILL GET SICK.
[RITA] AND WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO
WHAT'S WITH THAT?
YOU ARE NOTHING MINE.
[POTATO] YES I AM, I AM YOUR FRIEND.
TRUST ME.
I WILL TAKE YOU TO A PLACE
LEGAL,
BETTER THAN THE HOUSE OF THE NILE.
I ALSO RUN AWAY FROM THERE.
[RAIN]
[POTATO] COME, GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
HE COMES.
[RAIN]
[CRYING]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[KISS SNAP]
[TYPHOON] WAIT... WAIT... WAIT...
[CARMINHA] IT WAS GENÉSIO WHO GAVE YOU
DID YOU SEND IT HERE?
[TYPHOON] I HAVE... I HAVE
A BRIDE. I HAVE...
[CARMINHA] YOU... OH MY
GOD, YOU ARE AN ANGEL.
IT WAS GENÉSIO WHO SENT YOU
HERE.
[TYPHOON] DON'T DO IT, DON'T DO IT
THAT.
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE IT WAS HIM.
[TYPHOON] MY GOD IN HEAVEN...
[CARMINHA] I WILL LIVE,
GENESIO, I WILL LIVE. I WILL
TO LIVE.
OF COURSE I WILL LIVE. I LOVE YOU
I PROMISE,
I WILL NEVER THINK ABOUT IT AGAIN
CRAZINESS, GENESIO. OF COURSE.
OF COURSE, MY LOVE. OF COURSE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[TELEVISION IN THE BACKGROUND]
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪KNOW US WELL♪
♪NEITHER THE SAME NOR DIFFERENT♪
♪IT'S NOT BEFORE OR AFTER♪
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪IT'S WHAT WE FEEL♪
♪NEITHER GUILTY OR INNOCENT♪
♪IN THIS STORY OF US TWO♪
[TYPHOON] THIS SHOULD NOT HAVE HAPPENED
HAPPENED.
[CARMINHA] NO, YOU SHOULDN'T.
[RAIN]
[CARMINHA] MY GOD IN HEAVEN, WHAT
DID I DO IT?
[TYPHOON] I'M ENGAGED. MY
BRIDE MUST BE WAITING FOR ME,
I HAVE TO GO AWAY.
[STEPS]
[CARMINHA] I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH YOU
TO SAY.
[RAIN]
[TYPHOON] I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT EITHER
WHAT TO SAY.
[RAIN]
[CARMINHA] I'M VERY
EMBARRASSED, SEE?
I'M SORRY, OK?
THAT I DON'T KNOW WHERE I WAS WITH
THE HEAD,
I THINK I'M GETTING
CRAZY.
IT'S JUST THAT, FOR A SECOND...
IT'S AS IF YOU WERE THE GENESIO,
AS IF MY GENESIS
HAD COME BACK TO ME.
[RAIN]
[CARMINHA] I'M SO CRAZY
REALLY, I'M SO CRAZY.
[TYPHOON] I THINK I AM TOO
GOING CRAZY,
BECAUSE I'M ABOUT TO GET MARRIED.
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE, OF COURSE.
[TYPHOON] YOU KNOW THAT.
[CARMINHA] I KNOW. OF COURSE.
[TYPHOON] THEN. FOR ALL
EFFECTS,
THIS NEVER HAPPENED. OK?
[CARMINHA] NO, YOU CAN STAY
QUIET.
NOBODY WILL KNOW,
MY SHARE,
NOBODY WILL EVER KNOW
YOU'RE WELCOME.
[TYPHOON] ARE YOU GOING TO BE OKAY?
[CARMINHA] DON'T WORRY
WITH ME, NOT.
[TYPHOON] WHEN WILL YOU HAVE IT?
WANT TO DELIVER THIS HOUSE?
[CARMINHA] NEXT WEEK, BUT
FORGET ABOUT IT.
[TYPHOON] NO, NO, I WANT IT
YOU STAY IN MY APARTMENT
THAT IS EMPTY, EVEN US
FIND A HOME FOR YOU.
[CARMINHA] NO, NO, FORGET IT
THAT'S IT, FORGET ABOUT IT.
[TYPHOON] ACCEPTING THIS HOUSE WOULD BE
A FAVOR YOU'RE DOING ME.
[CARMINHA] WE'LL THINK ABOUT IT LATER
IN THAT.
NOW, GO AWAY, GO, FOR
PLEASE,
I DON'T WANT TO KEEP YOU UP ANYMORE
HERE.
[STEPS]
[CARMINHA] I'M SORRY, OK?
I'M SORRY.
[RAIN]
[CARMINHA] "ACCEPT THIS HOUSE
IT WOULD BE A FAVOR
THAT YOU WOULD BE DOING TO ME."
LEAVE ME, I'LL MAKE IT FOR YOU
THIS FAVOR,
IDIOT. FOOL. [LAUGHTER]
[RITA] IS THIS YOUR HOUSE?
[POTATO] IT'S MOTHER'S HOUSE
LUCINDA. THAT'S WHERE I LIVE.
[RITA] A BEAUTIFUL HOUSE.
[POTATO] I KNOW. MOTHER LUCINDA
MADE THIS HOUSE
WITH THE THINGS WE COLLECT
THERE IN THE TRASH.
SHE IS THE BEST PERSON IN THE WORLD.
I WILL FIND A WAY FOR YOU
LIVE WITH US.
[RITA] ARE WE NOT GOING TO COME IN?
[POTATO] THERE ARE TWO
CHILDREN IN THE HOUSE,
MOTHER LUCINDA SAYS SHE DOESN'T HAVE ANY
NO MORE SPACE FOR ANYTHING.
[RITA] I GOT YOU INTO A PROBLEM, DIDN'T I?
HE WAS?
[POTATO] OH, STOP THE NONSENSE,
I FIND A WAY OUT EVERYTHING.
YOU'LL SEE.
BUT YOU WILL STAY THERE WHILE
I TALK TO MOTHER LUCINDA.
I'LL GET YOU SOME FOOD
FOR YOU, HERE WE GO.
[LUCINDA] HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MAKING IT AGREE
ALL WET, BOY?
[POTATO] NO, IT'S JUST...
I'M JUST HUNGRY.
[LUCINDA] WHAT WHAT
ARE YOU UP TO IT?
[POTATO] NO, I'M NOT GETTING READY
NOTHING, MOMMY.
[LUCINDA] THEN GO TO LIE DOWN, GO.
TAKE OFF THOSE CLOTHES, BOY,
YOU HAVE TO WAKE UP EARLY TOMORROW.
[POTATO] I'LL TAKE IT OUT NOW.
[POTATO] YOU MUST BE
STARVING.
[POTATO] BUT FIRST
CHANGE THOSE CLOTHES THERE,
IF NOT YOU'LL GET THE FLU.
I TURN TO THE SIDE.
[POTATO] OK, I'LL GO PRO
SIDE AND KEEP MY EYES CLOSED.
[RITA] IT CAN TURN.
[POTATO] [LAUGHTER]
[RITA] WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING AT, FOOL?
[POTATO] YOU LOOK LIKE
EMERSON, MY FRIEND.
[RITA] HUM... FUNNY.
[RITA] I'LL HAVE TO STAY
HIDDEN HERE?
[POTATO] JUST A LITTLE BIT. UNTIL
I EXCHANGE AN IDEAS WITH MOTHER.
[RITA] THANK YOU.
[POTATO] BUT THERE IS ONLY ONE THING
THAT MOTHER LUCINDA SAYS THAT HERE
IT IS FORBIDDEN TO BE SAD.
SLEEP WELL. ANYTHING
I'M OVER THERE.
[CARMINHA] I CALLED
FOR YOUR CELL PHONE
TEN THOUSAND TIMES
AND YOU DON'T ANSWER, RIGHT?
[MAX] I GAVE A LITTLE SLAPPING,
RIGHT, DEAR?
[CARMINHA] CARMINHA SCORED A GOAL,
ONE TO ZERO FOR US.
[MAX] WHAT IS IT? DID YOU GET IT?
TAKE THE GUY TO BED?
[CARMINHA] [LAUGHTER] IT WAS A HIT,
BUT I DID IT.
[MAX] AH, CUTE.
[LAUGHTER] THAT'S COOL.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO TYPE?
CELEBRATE THIS WITH YOU,
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
[CARMINHA] ARE YOU JEALOUS?
I DIDN'T SAY I HAD
GAME WITH THE GUY, HUH?
[MAX] WHAT "GAME" WHAT?
WHAT "GAME"? DON'T TRAVEL,
CARMINHA, THE GUY IS ENGAGED,
DO YOU THINK HE WILL DISMISS IT?
HIS BRIDE AND GOES
STAY WITH YOU?
[CARMINHA] WILL NOT DISMISS,
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO DELIVER THAT YOU HAD SEX
WITH ME AND THE TWO WILL FIGHT,
HOW MUCH DO YOU WANT TO BET?
[THUNDER]
[MONALISA] YOU CAN ORDER DINNER,
BECAUSE I ALREADY ATE ALL THE SUPPER
IN THESE HOURS THAT
I WAITED FOR YOU.
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, SORRY.
[MONALISA] "SORRY",
OKAY, WHAT'S THE EXCUSE?
I'M PAYING TO SEE.
[TYPHOON] THE WOMAN WENT CRAZY,
THE WOMAN SAID SHE WAS GOING TO KILL HERSELF,
UNDERSTAND? I DIDN'T GET IT
GO AWAY, I WAS SCARED
HER DOING SOMETHING CRAZY.
I ALREADY HAVE A DEATH
ON MY BACK,
IMAGINE A SECOND DEATH.
[MONALISA] WHAT A SMELL
IS THIS IT? DID YOU DRINK, TYPHOON?
[TYPHOON] I HAD A LITTLE WHISKEY.
[MONALISA] YOU DRANK BEER... YOU...
YOU SPEAK, YOU ARE
SMELLING LIKE A WOMAN!
YOU HAD FUCK WITH THIS ONE
WOMAN, TYPHOON?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY PACE♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK IT♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[MONALISA] TYPHOON, RESPOND!
GOT MUTE?
DID YOU HAVE SEX WITH THIS WOMAN?
[TYPHOON] NO, OF COURSE NOT.
[MONALISA] YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO LIE.
I SEE,
IT'S WRITTEN ON YOUR FOREHEAD THAT YOU
HE HAD SEX WITH THIS WOMAN!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, I DON'T KNOW
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN,
OK? BECAUSE SHE... SHE ASKED FOR IT
SO I COULD LAY DOWN ON THE SIDE
HER, WHERE HER HUSBAND
I LAY DOWN,
BECAUSE SHE WAS AFRAID OF
BE ALONE.
[MONALISA] NO, NO, NO! ME
SAVE THE DETAILS,
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD. I'M NOT
BELIEVING IN THIS.
YOU KNOW? IT'S GOOD FOR ME!
[TYPHOON] STOP, MONALISA!
I WAS DRUNK, I WAS CRAZY,
DID YOU UNDERSTAND?
[MONALISA] WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THAT YOU DID A CHARITY,
IS THAT IT? YOU GOT DRUNK
OF WHISKEY AND GOT ​​THIS
WOMAN, FOR CHARITY, FOR GUILT
FOR HAVING RUN OVER HER HUSBAND?
I CAN'T BELIEVE I AM
LISTENING TO THIS!
[TYPHOON] FORGIVE ME, FORGIVE ME, ME
FORGIVE.
[MONALISA] "FORGIVEN ME"...
[VOICE OVERWHELMED] IT'S "FORGIVE ME",
THAT'S WHAT YOU HAVE TO TELL ME.
YOU LEAVE ME HERE ALONE,
PLANTED, ON OUR NIGHT OF
ENGAGEMENT CELEBRATION
AND YOU GET WITH A WOMAN. YOU
TURNS TO ME AND SAY:
"SORRY, FORGIVE ME", IS THAT IT?
[TYPHOON] MONALISA,
I NEVER DID THIS AND I NEVER WILL AGAIN
I WILL DO IT AGAIN.
[MONALISA] YOU WILL NOT COME BACK TO
DO, NO.
YOU WILL NOT DO IT AGAIN,
DO YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE IT ALL ENDED BETWEEN
PEOPLE!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, DON'T DO THAT.
DON'T SAY THAT,
THAT YOU ARE THE WOMAN OF MY
LIFE,
WE WILL STAY TOGETHER UNTIL
PEOPLE GET OLD, UNDERSTAND?
IT'S NOT BECAUSE OF A STUPIDITY
ONE WE CAN SEPARATE!
[MONALISA] LOOK, MINE
FRIENDS OF THE SALON,
THEY WERE RIGHT.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] THEY WERE RIGHT,
DO YOU KNOW WHY?
FAME HAS GONE TO YOUR HEAD.
[VOICE OVERWHELMED] DO YOU THINK THAT
YOU ARE THE OWNER OF THE WORLD, THAT
YOU CAN NOW STEP ON
IN PEOPLE. I WAS BLIND, ONLY
THAT I WAS BLIND WITH PASSION,
BUT NOW MY EYES ARE
OPENING!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA... NO, THAT'S IT
IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, MONALISA?
[MONALISA] WHERE ARE YOU
DO YOU THINK I WILL?
I'M LEAVING!
[TYPHOON] I'LL GO WITH YOU.
[MONALISA] YOU WON'T, NO. YOU
YOU WILL STAY HERE ALONE,
IN YOUR "TOP EXECUTIVE SUITE KING
"SIZE"!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, DON'T DO THIS
WITH ME, MONALISA.
[MONALISA] NO, THERE ISN'T
PROBLEM.
IF LONELINESS ATTACKS YOU, YOU CAN
CALLING A WIDOW WHO JUST GOT OVER
OF LOSING HER HUSBAND, BECAUSE
AFTER ALL,
THIS IS YOUR SPECIALTY
NOW,
GRAVEYARD CATCHMAN! [SIGH]
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪KNOW US WELL♪
♪NEITHER THE SAME NOR DIFFERENT♪
♪IT'S NOT BEFORE OR AFTER♪
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪IT'S WHAT WE FEEL♪
♪NEITHER GUILTY OR INNOCENT♪
♪IN THIS STORY OF US TWO♪
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪IT'S NOT A WORK OF CHANCE♪
♪IT'S A PLAN DESIGNED♪
♪ SIMPLE THING TO UNDERSTAND ♪
[TYPHOON] MONALISA! ENTER THE
CAR, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD!
[WOMAN] GUYS, IT'S THE TYPHOON!
[MONALISA] WANT IT FOR YOURSELF?
[LAUGHTER] YOU CAN TAKE IT. TAKE HER TO
DISCOVER THE SUITE,
SHE WILL LOVE IT.
[TYPHOON] MONALISA! MONA...
♪FOR YOU♪
♪FAR FROM YOU♪
♪MY HEART IS LOST♪
♪THE WORLD IS DIVIDED♪
[CHILD] PASS ME A... A
FORK.
[CHILD] THERE.
[LUCINDA] LOOK AT THE CAKE
RAIN COMING OUT!
[CHRIES OF CELEBRATION]
[CHILD] I DID IT!
[LUCINDA] WOW, LOOK AT THIS,
SLEEPING BEAUTY WOKE UP!
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU ARE ALWAYS THE FIRST TO
GET UP TO MAKE COFFEE
IN THE MORNING.
[POTATO] I DIDN'T SLEEP RIGHT, NO,
IT WAS... IT WAS VERY HOT.
[LUCINDA] WELL, BUT EMERSON DIDN'T
FOUND A NICE FAN,
THIS WEEK, IN THE TRASH? HUH? ALREADY
DID IT RUIN?
[POTATO] NO. IT'S... I DON'T KNOW, MOM,
I JUST SLEPT A LITTLE MORE.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
[LUCINDA] NO,
SLEPT A LITTLE MORE,
WHY, RIGHT?
ARRIVED LATE, ALL WET, IN THE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE RAIN.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[POTATO] I... I FIXED IT THERE
ROOF OF THE CHICKEN COOP,
THAT THE CHICKENS WERE
WETTING WITH THE STORM.
[LUCINDA] THE CHICKENS, HUH? [LAUGHTER]
OH, THERE'S VITAMIN IN THE FRIDGE,
OF AVOCADO.
[LUCINDA] SO, LET'S EAT,
LET'S EAT!
LET'S GET THINGS READY TO GO
TRASH!
YOU DON'T MISS OUT ON BREAKFAST,
NO, SEE?
WE'RE WAITING FOR YOU OUT HERE,
OK?
AND LOOK, THERE'S A RAIN CAKE,
I JUST DID IT.
COME ON. GOT IT, GOT IT, GOT IT,
DID YOU GET THE GLOVES? WHERE ARE THEY?
SO NOW WE GO. [LAUGHTER]
LET ME SEE.
AI... HEY, HELLO! WANT TO TALK TO
WHO?
[LAUGHTER] GIVE HIM THIS ONE,
PUT THE LITTLE BIRD IN THERE, OH.
WELL, SINCE THERE'S NO BIRD,
PUT THE FEATHER, PUT IT HERE.
HEY! [LAUGHTER] OH, GUYS, LOOK WHAT
I FOUND IT HERE.
OH... HERE, BETHANY, O, BETHANY,
WHAT I FOUND HERE.
OH, BETHANY, I FOUND A MIRROR, OK?
ENTIRELY.
[BETANIA] [LAUGHTER] WOW, THAT'S A LOT
THE EXPERIMENT IS COOL.
[LUCINDA] [LAUGHTER] OH, THING
BEAUTIFUL.
THE MIRROR IS ENTIRE AND
Fancy, huh? HUM... OH! [LAUGHTER]
[NILO] WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
WHAT ARE YOU TODAY?
COME ON, GIRL, GET SICK OF
TRASH. I WANT TO SEE, LET'S WORK.
AND THIS SHAMELESS GUY HERE, HUH?
SHAMELESS,
ARE YOU SLEEPING? GO GET SOME TRASH,
KID, GO PICK UP TRASH...
BECAUSE THIS THING DOESN'T...
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] OH! SO, THAT'S IT
A SNAKE HAD BITTEN, HUH?
[NILE] AH, ALTHOUGH YOU MUST
ARE YOU MISSING A CERTAIN THING?
SNAKE, RIGHT? BUT FOR THOSE WHO CREATE IT
A RATTLESNAKE INSIDE THE HOUSE,
DON'T BE SCARED OF
ANYTHING.
[LUCINDA] OH, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING,
DEVIL?
[NILO] I'M TALKING ABOUT BATATA, HE
IS PROTECTING THE NEW GIRL.
[LUCINDA] ARE YOU ACCUSING THE
POTATO WHAT?
[NILO] FOR HAVING HIDDEN MY
NEW GIRL, SHE'S GONE.
[LUCINDA] AH, BUT I DON'T DOUBT IT
MUCH THAT YOU HAVE DONE
WITH HER WHAT HAVE YOU DONE WITH HER?
SO MANY OTHERS, RIGHT?
MAY THE POOR GIRL'S BODY APPEAR
THERE IN THE MIDDLE OF THE SAND.
NOW, DO YOU WANT TO ACCUSE BATATA?
[NILO] SHE IS SPECIAL, SHE IS
PAPA-FINA, IT'S NOT FOR PLAYING
OUT NO. SHE'S HERE, I
I KNOW, I FEEL,
BUT IF I KNOW IT WAS THE
POTATO THAT HID HER,
OUR DEAL OF NOT ONE
INTERFERE IN OTHER PEOPLE'S LIVES
GO TO HELL, HUH?
FOR THE CUCUIA.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] POTATO! COME HERE,
BOY. COME!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] RUN!
[POTATO] WHAT'S UP?
[LUCINDA] HEY BATATA, WHERE ARE YOU?
DID YOU HID THE NILE GIRL?
[POTATO] BUT... WHAT A GIRL,
MOTHER?
[LUCINDA] OH, YOU KNOW VERY WELL
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT,
WHY ARE YOU COVERING UP FOR HER
I KNOW SINCE LAST NIGHT.
[POTATO] OH, MOM, IT WAS NOTHING.
[LUCINDA] OH, WHAT'S THE FIRST ONE
LAW AT HOME, HUH?
[POTATO] HAVE NO SECRET. ONE
TRUST IN OTHERS.
[LUCINDA] WHERE ARE YOU?
HID THE GIRL? SPEAK.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RITA] POTATO?
[LUCINDA] COME. COME WITH ME, COME.
HE COMES.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] GO, GO, GO.
[LUCINDA] YOU CAN EAT AS MUCH AS YOU WANT,
BUT THEN YOU HAVE TO HUNT YOUR OWN
HEADING, OK?
[POTATO] NO, MOTHER LUCINDA, SHE
THERE'S NOWHERE TO GO.
HER FATHER DIED, THERE WERE ONLY THEM
TWO.
[LUCINDA] BUT, POTATO, YOU KNOW,
NOT HERE...
POTATO, THERE'S NO WAY HERE ANYMORE
NOBODY. THERE ARE 12 MOUTHS TO EAT,
12 SON TO... GIVE MEDICINE, TO
PUTTING ON CLOTHES, IT'S NOT POSSIBLE,
THERE ARE NO CONDITIONS, RIGHT?
[RITA] YOU ARE VERY GOOD,
MOTHER LUCINDA, YOU CAN SEE IT IN YOUR EYES.
BUT THANK YOU ANYWAY. THANK YOU,
POTATO.
[POTATO] SHE'S NOT GOING AWAY! IF
IF SHE LEAVES, I'LL GO WITH HER.
[LUCINDA] OH, LET GO OF IT
"BRAVALRY",
ARE YOU WANTING TO SHOW OFF?
GIRL, IS IT?
[POTATO] IF SHE GOES BACK TO THE NILE,
SHE WILL DIE, OR MAYBE TURN
ANOTHER ONE OF THOSE DEMONS THERE.
[RITA] LEAVE IT, BATATA, I KNOW MYSELF
TO TURN,
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE ANY TROUBLE.
[RITA] DONA LUCINDA DOESN'T WANT
TROUBLE WITH ME.
[POTATO] OH, SO THERE ISN'T ANY
MORE NILO, THERE IS NOTHING ELSE.
I'M LEAVING THIS DUMP.
ME AND YOU, RIGHT, RITA?
LET'S GO TOGETHER.
[LUCINDA] WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
TALKING?
[POTATO] THAT'S RIGHT, MOM
LUCINDA, IT'S DECIDED!
IF RITA CANNOT STAY HERE IN
HOME, I RUN AWAY WITH HER
AND WE FIND A WAY TO
GO THIS WAY.
I'M GOING TO GET MY STUFF RIGHT AWAY
I COME BACK.
[LUCINDA] IT'S A LITTLE ANIMAL
HARD HEADED, HUH?
[POTATO] BYE, MOTHER LUCINDA, ONE
ONE DAY I COME TO VISIT YOU.
[LUCINDA] AND I CAN KNOW WHERE
ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO HAVE LUNCH?
AND WHERE WILL YOU SLEEP?
[POTATO] OH, WE ASK FOR ALMS
TO EAT, RIGHT, RITA?
[RITA] AND SLEEP UNDER THE
MARQUISE.
[LUCINDA] ARE YOU TAKING A BLANKET?
IF IT GETS COLD, YOU'LL CATCH A COLD
AND THERE WILL BE NOBODY TO
TAKE SYRUP ON A SPOON, OK?
[POTATO] IF I DIE, I DIE.
[ALL] MOTHER LUCINDA, HE'S GOING
STARVE TO DEATH, PLEASE,
DON'T LET ME. DON'T LET ME, MOTHER
LUCINDA.
[LUCINDA] HEY BATATA, STOP IT
DRAMA, POTATO, RITA STAYS!
RITA STAYS!
[LUCINDA] HEY! I'LL TELL YOU...
[CHRIES OF CELEBRATION]
[CHILD] YEAH, MAN! I KNEW IT!
I KNEW IT, MAN!
[OLENKA] MONALISA. WAKE UP.
WAKE UP,
YOUR MAN IS DOWN THERE. HE'S WITH
SOME DARK CIRCLES FROM THE DAY BEFORE YESTERDAY,
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
[MONALISA] TELL HIM TO GO AWAY.
TELL THAT DONKEY NEVER AGAIN
TO APPEAR.
[OLENKA] ARE YOU SURE?
[MONALISA] I HAVE.
[OLENKA] OK, IF YOU DON'T
IF YOU WANT IT, THERE ARE SOMEONE WHO WANTS IT.
[MAN] [DISTANT VOICE]
ATTENTION, ATTENTION, ATTENTION,
RESOUNDING THAT YOU MISS
MONALISA.
HER GROOM, THE MYTH OF THE DIVINE,
THE KING OF THE LAWNS, THE HERO OF
OUR PEOPLE,
JOR-JOR-JOR-JORGE TYPHOON, ASK FOR
YOUR EXCELLENCY
LET HIM SHOW HIS GRACE! [LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, LOOK, I
I PROMISE IT'S THE LAST THING
WHAT I WILL ASK YOU IN LIFE, COME
OUT HERE.
[TYPHOON] COME HERE AND LISTEN TO WHAT I SAY
I HAVE TO TELL YOU.
DO YOU WANT ME TO KNEEL DOWN?
OK, I'M KNEELING DOWN
HERE IN FRONT OF EVERYONE.
[TYPHOON] I WANT TO ASK YOU,
MY LOVE, TO COME OUT HERE
TO HEAR WHAT I HAVE FOR YOU
TO SPEAK.
[MONALISA] THIS IS THE PARROT
HERE IN FRONT OF MY PLACE
WORK? I'LL GO TO YOURS
GAME TO MAKE A SCANDAL?
YOU WILL SCARE AWAY THE PARISH. FOR
PLEASE, CAN YOU PULL THIS CAR
FROM HERE I HAVE NOTHING LEFT
TO TALK TO YOU,
GET OUT OF MY LIFE!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, LISTEN TO ME.
[TYPHOON] I'M AN IDIOT, ONLY
I MAKE A STUPID MISTAKE.
NOW, YOU ARE THE BEST WOMAN IN THE
WORLD. YOU ARE MY TALISMAN,
MY GUIDE, MY LUCKY FIG.
I AM NOTHING WITHOUT YOU,
YOU ARE THE WOMAN OF MY LIFE.
[MONALISA] COME, TYPHOON, STOP
THEREFORE!
[TYPHOON] NO, BECAUSE I AM
SO I AM YOURS. THE BODY,
THE SOUL, THE HEART, UNTIL THE
DEATH DO US PART.
AND I'M SURE, MY LOVE,
WHAT IF I STAY WITHOUT YOU
I WILL DWIN UNTIL I DIE, I
I KNOW THAT.
I'M ASKING YOU NOT TO
LET IT HAPPEN,
DON'T LET ME DIE.
[TYPHOON] FORGIVE ME.
♪THIS IS WHY I LIVE FOR YOU♪
[MONALISA] DON'T TALK LIKE THAT
WITH ME.
♪BECAUSE NOBODY HAS THE RIGHT♪
♪TELL US WHAT IS PERFECT♪
♪IN THIS STORY THAT IS♪
♪JUST THE TWO OF US♪
[TYPHOON] YOU WILL NOT
TO REPENT,
YOU WILL BE THE MOST LOVED WOMAN
OF THE WORLD.
[TYPHOON] COME WITH ME, LET'S STAY
TOGETHER FOREVER.
♪JUST THE TWO OF US♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[CONCEIÇÃO] CAN I TAKE THE
PLATE OF YOUR CRUCIBLE,
DONA VERONICA?
[VERONICA] LOVE, THE DISH, THE
CHAIR, THE CLOTHES IN THE CLOSET,
YOU CAN TAKE EVERYTHING THAT IS HIS AND
DELIVER TO THE FIRST CARTWORKER
THAT APPEARS IN FRONT.
CLOWN!
[BELLING]
[VERÔNICA] OH, IT'S HIM! IT'S GOING TO BE
FACE TO THE DOOR,
I CHANGED THE LOCK. LOOK, YOU
THIS MAN WILL NOT LEAVE ME
COME IN HERE, HUH, CONCEIÇÃO.
[CONCEIÇÃO] IT'S NOT YOURS
CRUCIBLE, NO, DONA VERÔNICA,
IT'S FROM THE STORE, THEY CALLED THE INTERCOM
PORTARIA.
[VERONICA] WHICH STORE?
[DOOR OPEN]
[WOMAN] GOOD AFTERNOON! THEY SENT
DELIVER THESE DRESSES HERE.
[CONCEIÇÃO] I CAN SEND
COME BACK, MADAM?
[VERÔNICA] YOU CAN! WAIT, LET IT GO
COME IN JUST A LITTLE.
[VERÔNICA] IS IT FOR ME TO CHOOSE?
[WOMAN] NO, IT WAS ALL BOUGHT
FOR YOU.
♪GOD PROTECT ME♪
♪OF YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME♪
♪OF YOUR BITTERNESS♪
[VERONICA] ONE THING IS
TRUE,
CARLOS EDUARDO KNOWS MY
I LIKE.
♪GOD HELP ME♪
♪FROM YOUR ANGER♪
[VERÔNICA] I'LL PROVE IT.
♪OF YOUR POISON♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR END♪
♪GOD PROTECT ME♪
♪OF YOUR ENVY♪
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[VERÔNICA] ARE YOU THINKING THAT
BUY ME, HUH, CARLOS EDUARDO?
LOVE, I'M SO CUTE, SEE? I
I'M NOT COCKROACH, NO.
DO YOU REALLY THINK I'M GOING TO COME DOWN?
THERE TO FIND YOU
AT THE RECEPTION?
[VERONICA] I DON'T WANT TO KNOW
NO SURPRISE AT ALL, OK?
YOU TAKE THIS LITTLE SURPRISE OF YOURS AND
GO TAKE SALT!
[VERÔNICA] SOMETIMES IN LIFE
PEOPLE HAVE TO BE FIRM,
CONCEIÇÃO. I DON'T WANT TO KNOW ABOUT
SURPRISE, I'M NOT LEAVING HERE.
♪GOD GOD GO WITH ME♪
♪GOD SUPPORT ME♪
♪GOD LIFT ME UP♪
♪GOD GIVE ME STRENGTH♪
[CRUITLING] WANT TO TAKE THE TEST
DRIVE NOW OR LATER? HUM?
[CRUCIBLE] IT'S YOURS. COME IN, HUM?
[CRUITLING] HUM, OH, FOR YOU. HUH?
DID YOU FEEL THE BANK?
ITALIAN LEATHER. SMELL OF
NEW CAR. HUH?
BE CAREFUL IF YOU STEP ON IT
ACCELERATOR IT FLIES. [LAUGHTER]
[VERÔNICA] YOU'RE NO GOOD,
CRUCIBLE.
[CAR ENGINE]
[CRUCIFIX] [CLEARING] HOW IS IT
WAS THE WEATHER THERE, CIÇA, HEAVY?
[CIÇA] THE LORD REALLY WANTS IT
KNOW THE TRUTH, YOU CRUCIBLE?
[CRUCIBLE] OK, LOOK, I'M GOING TO HAVE
I WANT TO GO BACK TO BRASILIA.
TRY TO HELP VERÔ TO GIVE A
RELAXED, OK?
PREPARE A BUBBLE BATH,
SERVE THAT LITTLE CUP OF
CHAMPAGNE
IN THE LATE AFTERNOON THAT SHE SO MUCH
DO YOU LIKE IT, OKAY?
LOOK HERE, LOOK, AT YOU.
[CRUCIBLE] A BONUS,
OK?
THANK YOU, CIÇA.
[NOÊMIA] IT'S THE END! It's
UNACCEPTABLE!
NOT EVEN WHEN I WAS 18 YEARS OLD, ONLY
I WAS DATING A HIPPIE,
I WAS STANDING PLANTED IN THE
RESTAURANT WAITING FOR SOMEONE!
[CIDA] DONA NOÊMIA, YOUR DUDU IS HERE
THERE.
[NOÊMIA] TELL THIS MAN THAT
I WANT TO SEE HIM DEAD!
BY THE WAY, IF HE LEAVES THIS WAY
BETTER,
I'M NOT EVEN GOING TO THE BURIAL.
[CIDA] DONA NOÊMIA, I THINK
YOU BETTER GO OUTSIDE,
HE'S IN AN AMBULANCE!
[NOÊMIA] [SCREAMING] DUDU! LET'S GO.
[NOÊMIA] DUDU! DUDU, WHAT?
DID IT HAPPEN, DUDU?
[MAN] WAS IN A CAR ACCIDENT,
THERE WERE MANY INJURIES,
IT IS IMPORTANT THAT HE STAYS
REST.
[NOÊMIA] MY GOD, WHAT MADNESS!
YOU HERE ALL HURT AND I'M THERE
INSIDE WITH ANGRY, CIDA.
[CRUCIBLE] I TRIED TO COMMUNICATE
IN THE HOSPITAL,
BUT I LOST MY SENSES.
[NOÊMIA] DOESN'T SPEAK, DOESN'T SPEAK,
DON'T SPEAK.
PRESERVE YOURSELF, PRESERVE YOURSELF.
PREPARE A MEAL FOR MY
CHUCHUZINHO,
AN ANGEL'S HAIR WITH PESTO.
COME ON, CIDA, YOU CAN BRING HIM
HERE COMES CIDA.
[MAN] GONE.
[CRUITLING] REALLY GOOD, HUH?
DAMN.
HERE IT IS, LOOK, WAIT A
A LITTLE LITTLE.
GREAT, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[MAN] OH, CHECK IT OUT
RIGHT.
[MAN] HEY.
[CRUCIBLE] WELL, THERE WERE NO 300
REAL?
[MAN] 350, RIGHT?
AND THE UNION FEE OF
ACTORS? HUM, I SAID, FAT.
[CRUITLING] OK, HERE IT IS.
[MURICY] I DON'T BELIEVE WHAT
I AM LISTENING.
YOU CAME BACK WITH THAT ONE
BANDIT?
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, MY SON,
GIVE UP ON THAT WOMAN,
LEAVE HER ALONE!
[TYPHOON] I LOVE MONALISA,
MOMMY.
I AM INFORMING YOU THAT
I WILL MARRY MONALISA.
[MURICY] WITH SO MANY WOMEN IN THIS
WORLD,
WHY DID THIS BOY GO?
JUST CHOOSE THAT ONE
BADLY DRESSED RETIRED?
[LELECO] YOU CHOSE A LOT
WELL YOUR WIFE,
MY SON. MONALISA IS A WOMAN OF
VALUE.
[MURICY] YOU DON'T LISTEN, NO
LISTEN TO WHAT THIS OLD MAN SAYS
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND ANYTHING
FROM THAT.
[LELECO] I DON'T UNDERSTAND ANYTHING
FROM THAT?
WHAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND ABOUT THIS...
OH, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY,
I REALLY DON'T UNDERSTAND ANY OF THIS,
WHY I MARRIED YOU.
[MURICY] OH, THANK GOD.
[IVANA] PEOPLE, STOP FIGHTING,
FOR GOD'S SAKE.
[TYPHOON] LOOK HERE YOU ARE
ALSO, SISTER,
I WANT THE MONALISM TO BE
VERY WELL TREATED
FROM HERE ONWARDS IN HERE
AND I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT ANYMORE
WORD "CANGACEIRA".
AND I WILL BECOME A MEMBER IN
SALON SHE IS OPENING.
[MURICY] I'M TALKING, I AM
TALKING.
SHE HASN'T EVEN STEPPED ON THE ALTAR YET
AND YOU'RE ALREADY PUTTING YOUR HAND IN YOURS
POCKET.
[TYPHOON] MOM, FOR YOUR
GOVERNMENT, SHE JUST ACCEPTED ME
AS A PARTNER AFTER A LOT
INSISTENCE.
I JUST WANT IT BECAUSE I THINK IT
THAT WILL BE A GOOD DEAL FOR
ME, UNDERSTAND?
[IVANA] I THINK SO TOO. DONE,
I SAID, MOM.
AND I SAY MORE, THIS FORMULA OF
STRAIGHTENING SHE INVENTED
IT'S A SHOW, I AM IT MYSELF
CUSTOMER.
THEN, LOOK, IT WILL MAKE A LOT OF MONEY
FOR US, HUH? TRUST ME.
[MURICY] THANK YOU SO MUCH, IVANA.
I THANK.
I THROW IN THE TOWEL, RIGHT?
IT LOOKS LIKE THIS MARIA IS BEAUTIFUL.
IS IT OK "MARIA BONITA"?
IT SEEMS LIKE SHE HAS BEwitched YOU
EVERYONE, RIGHT?
[MURICY] AFTER YOU GIVE
WITH THE DONKEYS IN THE WATER,
DON'T SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU
THAT THIS SALON BUSINESS
HAIRDRESSING IS A SCAM.
IT'S A HOAX.
[IVANA] OH! SHE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT
ARE YOU TALKING, PEOPLE.
[TYPHOON] PAY ATTENTION, SISTER,
I STILL WANT
MAY YOU BE MY PARTNER, YOU
NOT GOOD AT ACCOUNTING?
SO, I'M COMING IN WITH THE
MONEY,
MONALISA WITH TALENT, AND YOU
CLEAN THE HOUSE.
[IVANA] IT TOOK ME A WHILE, I'M IN.
[LELECO] AND WHERE DO I GO IN?
[IVANA] YOU, FATHER, HOW ABOUT
YOU'RE GOING TO PLAY POOL, HUH?
THERE AT THE BAR. WHERE YOU NEVER
IT'S OUT, RIGHT? [LAUGHTER]
OH, DAD. SO, DID YOU LIKE IT?
THE STREET IS GREAT, OH, THERE IS A POINT
BY BUS AT THE DOOR.
TELL ME IF IT'S NOT THE IDEAL POINT
FOR US TO OPEN THE SALON?
[MONALISA] IVANA, YOU GOT IT RIGHT
IN FULL.
[TYPHOON] HERE, O, MY
PRINCESS, I JUST DON'T WANT TO
LOSE MY WIFE FOR
WORK, HUH?
YOU HAVE TO BE AT HOME, AT LEAST
LATE, AT 6PM, HUH?
[MONALISA] LEAVE IT, OLENKA
IT'S THERE TO SURRENDER TO ME.
SHE IS THE CO-PILOT OF THE SALON, IS IT OR
IT IS NOT?
[OLENKA] YEAH, I CAN'T WAIT
THAT'S READY, HUH?
[CELEBRATING SHOUT]
[MONALISA] OH, WHAT EMOTION.
WILL NOBODY COME?
[IVANA] WHAT IS THIS?
[TYPHOON] OH MONALISA, TODAY IS THE
FIRST DAY,
WHAT DO YOU WANT, GET IN LINE
DOOR? THAT'S TOO MUCH, RIGHT?
[IVANA] OH, AUNT ANARAÍ
GUARANTEED
THAT FIVE MORE COLLEAGUES WERE COMING
MY GYMNASTICS TOO.
[OLENKA] HERE, SISTER, I'M TALKING,
THIS SALON IS GOING TO BE A BIG HOUSE! [LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] Oh!
[MONALISA] AH! WELCOME!
ARE YOU OK, MRS. ZULEIDE?
LOOK, YOU'RE GOING TO WIN A
FREE STRAIGHTENING
SINCE YOU WERE MINE
FIRST CUSTOMER.
[OLENKA] [LAUGHTER] COME AND I'LL GO
PREPARE YOUR HAIR NOW.
[TYPHOON] FOR FREE?
♪I CHERISH THE MOMENTS WITH YOU♪
♪RESPECTFULLY I SAY TO THEE♪
♪I'M AWARE THAT YOU'RE CHEATING♪
♪WHEN NO ONE MAKES♪
♪ME FEEL LIKE YOU DO♪
♪UPSIDE DOWN♪
♪BOY, YOU TURN ME♪
♪INSIDE OUT♪
[OLENKA] GREAT! VERY GOOD. LOOK
OVER THERE. SHOW YOU BACK HERE,
LOOK. SEE? IT'S FLAT,
HUH? IT'S GOING TO BE AWESOME.
TELL US ABOUT THE SALON.
[MONALISA] PLEASE, O, THE
TREATMENT, OK? CONTINUE AT HOME.
THANK YOU, LINDA.
[MONALISA] GO WITH GOD, OK?
[MONALISA] WHO IS THE
NEXT?
[IVANA] THE GIRL OVER THERE
LEFT.
GIRL, OH, I'M ALREADY DISTRIBUTING
UNTIL PASSWORD.
[MONALISA] [LAUGHTER]
♪SITTIN' HERE EATIN' MY HEART♪
♪OUT WAITIN'♪
♪WAITIN' FOR SOME LOVE TO CALL♪
♪DIALED ABOUT A THOUSAND♪
♪NUMBERS LATELY♪
[IVANA] GUYS, I DIDN'T TELL YOU
YOU? HAIR STRAIGHTENING
IT'S A GOLD MINE. GET EVERYTHING AND
VISIT, JUST IMAGINE
THE AMOUNT OF CURLY HAIR
THAT STILL EXISTS IN THE WORLD.
[IVANA] WAIT, WAIT, LET'S GO
ORGANIZE THIS HERE,
IT IS ON A FIRST COME BASIS.
[OLENKA] AH!
♪GONNA HAVE SOME LOVE TONIGHT♪
♪HOT STUFF♪
♪I NEED♪
♪I WANT SOME HOT STUFF♪
[MONALISA] YOU CAN SPEAK, DOCTOR,
IT'S SERIOUS, RIGHT? I KNOW IT IS,
BECAUSE I'M FEELING SO
WEIRD, I KNOW IT'S COMING TO BE A BOOM
AROUND THERE. MY FATHER, I AM
READY, I JUST ASK YOU
ONE THING, DON'T ASK ME TO STAY
RESTING TODAY, BECAUSE TODAY
IT'S MY ENGAGEMENT PARTY, EVERYONE
MY FAMILY IS COMING
FROM PARAÍBA, I DON'T HAVE
CONDITION TO STAY IN BED, NO.
[MAN] THIS IS A PERFECT DAY FOR
YOU RECEIVE THE NEWS
THAT I HAVE TO GIVE YOU. YOU
YOU'RE PREGNANT, MONALISA.
[MONALISA] [LAUGHTER] PREGNANT?
I... I'M... I'M PREGNANT?
[MONALISA] I'M FULL,
YOUR DOCTOR?
AUNT DÉA, I MISS YOU SO MUCH! [LAUGHTER]
OH COUSIN HOSEAS, OH, HOW GOOD! OH
JUNO, DID YOU HAVE A GOOD TRIP?
[JUNO] THIS IS TOO FAR,
THE JOURNEY SEEMS LIKE IT NEVER ENDS
NEVER.
[MONALISA] WHY NOT
THEY ACCEPTED THE PLANE TICKET
WHAT DID I OFFER YOU?
[HOSEA] NEITHER I NOR JUNO
LET'S GET ON THAT ANIMAL
OF FLYING IRON.
[MONALISA] [LAUGHTER] AUNT DÉA, AUNT
DÉA, I... I WANT TO TELL YOU
ONE THING. I WANT THE
LADY BE THE FIRST TO KNOW.
I'M PREGNANT WITH THE TYPHOON!
[DÉA] HOW WONDERFUL, MY
DAUGHTER!
[MONALISA] I FOUND OUT
I HAVEN'T EVEN TOLD YOU ABOUT THIS NOW
FOR HIM YET. I WILL TELL
TODAY, AT THE PARTY.
AT TOAST TIME. [LAUGHTER]
[DÉA] MY OUR LADY, THIS
THE PARTY WILL BE A THRILL,
MY DAUGHTER! HOW BEAUTIFUL!
[MAX] [GRUNTING] [LAUGHTER]
[CARMINHA] MARGARIDA APPEARED.
[MAX] WHAT'S UP, HOT?
[CARMINHA] WHERE HAVE YOU GONE?
YESTERDAY?
[MAX] "WHERE DID I GET MYSELF INTO YESTERDAY",
I WAS WORKING FOR YOU, MISS,
RIGHT? I GOT TO GO OUT WITH MY FRIEND
BRIDE OF THE TYPHOON,
THE ONE WHO WORKS IN THE SALON.
LOOK, WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT A VIEW! UP HIGH, THERE,
KIDDING, I LIKED THE APARTMENT
THAT THE IDIOT LOANED YOU...
[CARMINHA] THIS CRAP, MAX?
YOU'RE REALLY UNCONSCIOUS, RIGHT?
[MAX] OH, STOP THAT. THERE.
[CARMINHA] COME HERE, DON'T GO TO ME
ASK HOW IT WAS
NOT THE DOCTOR, HUH?
[MAX] HUM...
[CARMINHA] DO YOU REMEMBER THAT I
I WENT TO THE DOCTOR YESTERDAY,
OR DID YOU FORGET?
[MAX] I REALLY FORGOT, WHY?
ANY PROBLEM?
[CARMINHA] PROBLEM, IT IS...
IT DEPENDS ON THE POINT OF VIEW.
[MAX] I DON'T UNDERSTAND, YOU
ARE YOU SICK?
[CARMINHA] I'M PREGNANT.
[MAX] PREGNANT... PREGNANT WITH
ME?
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE IT IS
YOU, MAX.
[MAX] WHAT ELSE...
[CARMINHA] IT'S YOUR FAULT, YOUR FAULT
TOO LAZY TO USE A CONDOM.
AND IT WASN'T THE FIRST TIME.
[MAX] STOP IT... STOPPED IT,
STOP! DON'T SAY THAT WAY,
MAN, A CHILD IS COMING
FOR THE WORLD. OUR SON,
WHAT THE FUCK...
THIS TIME IT WILL BE DIFFERENT,
THE OTHER TIME WE WERE
IN A BAD BLOCK,
NOT THIS ONE,
WE ARE FINE
ON TAPE, MY LOVE.
[CARMINHA] HOW GOOD, MAX?
WHAT ARE YOU REFERRING TO?
TO THE CARAMINGUÁ THAT GENÉSIO
LEFT ME?
[MAX] WHAT THE FUCK, MAN?
WOW, ME HUH! AND THE HOUSE?
THE HOUSE THAT THE TYPHOON WILL GIVE YOU?
[CARMINHA] LITTLE DOWNTOWN HOUSE
MIXED LACE,
ALL MIXED UP.
[MAX] OH, HEY, CARMINHA,
STOP IT, MAN,
STOP YOUR MANIA
OF GREATNESS!
[CARMINHA] I HAVE A MANIA
OF GREATNESS YES AND IT IS THANKFUL
TO MY DELUSION OF GREATNESS,
THAT WE ARE NOT IN THE DUMP.
[MAX] COME HERE, TELL ME SOMETHING.
WHEN WILL WE KNOW
IF IT'S A BOY OR A GIRL,
HUH? HUM?
[CARMINHA] IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I WOULD TAKE IT OFF FOR ME.
[CARMINHA] OH NO,
THIS BABY CAME AT A GOOD TIME.
A CHILD
WHO NEEDS A FATHER.
[MAX] YES, THAT'S IT.
AND THE FATHER IS HERE, HUM?
[CARMINHA] WHAT THE FUCK, DAD, MAX?
YOU, FATHER? FATHER IS THE ONE WHO PAYS
THE ACCOUNTS.
[MAX] NO, WAIT,
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU WON'T SAY
THAT THIS SON IS FROM TYPHOON,
THAT THIS IS TOO MUCH FORCE,
CARMINHA. STOP IT!
[CARMINHA] STOP BEING STUPID,
MAX. I WILL DO MUCH BETTER.
[CARMINHA] I WILL SAY THAT THE SON
IT'S FROM GENESIO. IF A WIDOW
A HOUSE IS WORTH, HOW MUCH, NOT
IS THE COMPLETE PACKAGE WORTH IT?
A LITTLE ORPHAN
INSIDE THE WIDOW, HUH?
[CARMINHA] DID YOU DO YOUR PART?
SAID IT, FOUND OUT
ABOUT MONALISA
WITH THAT WOMAN?
[MAX] THAT'S ANOTHER STORY,
RIGHT? I'LL TELL YOU THE FOLLOWING.
[CARMINHA] HUM?
[MAX] IF I WERE YOU,
I LOST HOPE OF STAYING
WITH THIS GUY, SEE?
THIS MONALISA IS FIXING UP
AN ENGAGEMENT PARTY
AND HE SAID THAT PARAÍBADA
IT HAS ALREADY GONE DOWN ENTIRELY
TO RIO DE JANEIRO.
[CARMINHA] ENGAGEMENT PARTY?
[CARMINHA] VERY INTERESTING.
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[CRUCIBLE] HEY, ROSE, CALL
VERONICA AND NOÊMIA
AND TELL THEM THAT THE TICKETS
FOR NEW YEAR'S EVE
THEY'RE ALREADY BOUGHT, OK?
THANKS.
[SIGH] THANK GOD IT'S ALREADY OVER
AT THE END OF THE YEAR, I'M EXHAUSTED.
[JIMMY] I DON'T UNDERSTAND, NO.
ARE YOU GOING TO TRAVEL WITH BOTH OF THEM?
[CRUITLING] NO, LUCKILY FOR ME,
NOÊMIA ALWAYS LIKES TO PASS
NEW YEAR'S EVE ALONE MEDITATING
IN A BUDDHIST TEMPLE IN NEPAL,
AND I'M GOING TO TAKE VERONICA TO
A LITTLE RESORT IN THE MALDIVES.
[PHONE RINGING]
[ROSE] [ELECTRONIC VOICE]
DONA NOÊMIA ON LINE ONE.
[CRUCIFIX] [SIGH] HI, NONO.
READY FOR NEPAL?
[NOÊMIA] WHAT NEPAL, CRUCIBLE?
HAVEN'T YOU BEEN READING THE NEWSPAPERS?
THERE WILL BE A MILLENNIUM BUG,
WHEN IT TURNS FROM 99 TO 00,
COMPUTER WILL MELT,
THE AIRPORT WILL BE CLOSE,
TO TOLL CANCELLATION
IT WILL BE A MATTER.
THIS NEW YEAR'S EVE I WANT
PASS HERE IN RIO,
YOU SAID THAT TOO
I WANTED TO STAY.
[CRUCIBLE] ME? I GO, I GO.
I WILL STAY IN RIO,
OF COURSE, I'LL STAY IN RIO.
[NOÊMIA] THAT'S GREAT,
SO WE'RE GOING TO BREAK UP
THIS MILLENNIUM TOGETHER,
HUGGING WITH TOMÁS.
WE CAN CALL IT LIKE THIS,
ABOUT THREE FRIENDS, JUST PERSONAL
MORE INTIMATE, RIGHT, DUDU?
[EXTENDED] OH! WHY
THAT WE DON'T RENT
A HOTEL SUITE IN COPA
TO SEE THE FIREWORKS?
WHAT DO YOU TELL ME?
[CRUCIBLE] HUM...
[PHONE RINGING]
[CRUCIBLE] JUST A MINUTE,
LOVE, JUST A MINUTE.
[ROSE] [ELECTRONIC VOICE]
DONA VERÔNICA ON LINE TWO.
[CRUCIBLE] OH MY GOD.
HELLO? LOVE?
[VERÔNICA] WHAT'S UP, CADINHO?
BAGS READY FOR THE MALDIVES?
[VERÔNICA] WHAT DO YOU MEAN, MISTAKEN
FROM THE SECRETARY? CARLOS EDUARDO,
ARE YOU CRAZY? SPENDING NEW YEAR'S EVE
IN RIO? LOVE, NOT EVEN DEAD!
[CRUITLING] OH, VERONICA, YOU DON'T
YOU'VE BEEN READING THE NEWSPAPERS, HAVEN'T YOU?
THERE WILL BE THE MILLENNIUM BUG.
THE PLANE WILL CRASH, IT WILL CATCH FIRE
AT THE AIRPORT. NO, I KNOW
THAT WE AGREED ON, LOVE,
BUT I CHANGED MY MIND. IT'S FOR
OUR FAMILY'S SAFETY,
UNDERSTAND? THINK CAREFULLY, LOOK,
WE RENT, LIKE THIS,
A PRESIDENTIAL SUITE AT THE HOTEL
LUXURY, CALL YOUR FRIENDS,
SEE THE FIREWORKS FROM UP THERE.
HUH? THINK ABOUT IT.
WAIT, WAIT, JUST A MINUTE,
LOVE, ONLY... I HAVE
I NEED TO SIGN SOME PAPERS HERE.
[CRUCIBLE] HELLO, NONO? CLOSED.
SURE, I WILL BOOK A HOTEL,
LEAVE IT TO ME. IT WILL BE BEAUTIFUL,
SEE? I LOVE YOU TOO, LOVE.
O... LOOK, DON'T FORGET TO GIVE
THE SYRUP I BOUGHT
FOR TOMÁS, OK?
A KISS. I LOVE YOU TOO, NONO.
[CRUCIBLE] SEE, THINK
WITH LOVE, WITH AFFECTION.
YES, IT WILL BE BEAUTIFUL. WE WILL PASS IT ON
NEW YEAR'S EVE IN BRAZIL
WITH OUR FRIENDS, OK? MORE
WE'LL TALK TO EACH OTHER LATER.
ME, ME... LATER WE
SAY, I LOVE YOU, I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
BYE, BYE, BYE.
JIMMY, YOU BOOK
ALL THIS FOR ME.
[JIMMY] WAIT, ARE YOU SURE?
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TWO PARTIES
WITH HIS TWO WIVES
IN THE SAME HOTEL? CRUCIBLE,
CRUCIBLE, YOU'RE GOING TO DIE FROM THIS.
[CRUILT] YES, YES.
I'M EXHAUSTED,
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
TWO WOMEN, TWO FAMILIES.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT?
I NEED IT?
[JIMMY] SOME ALONE TIME?
[CRUCIBLE] NO, A LOVER.
[ALEXIA] [EXTENDED] OH. MY
GOD IN HEAVEN,
WHAT THIS
GUY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
[ALEXIA] HELLO?
[CRUCIBLE] HI, ALEXIA? THIS IS
CARLOS EDUARDO,
THAT GUY FROM THE OTHER NIGHT, FROM
BAR OF...
[ALEXIA] I KNOW, I SEE IT
YOU HERE ON THE INTERCOM.
[CRUCIBLE] AH! [LAUGHTER]
[CADINHO] HI, HOW ARE YOU?
[CLEARING] YES, I WAS
I WAS PASSING BY AND I THOUGHT,
SUDDENLY, I DON'T KNOW, DO A
VISIT, COME UP THERE,
HAVE A COFFEE, RIGHT?
[ALEXIA] LISTEN, CARLOS EDUARDO,
RIGHT?
I WILL BE VERY HONEST WITH YOU
YOU, THE COFFEE
THAT WE BOTH HAD TO TAKE,
WE ALREADY TOOK IT THAT NIGHT.
[CRUCIBLE] HOW?
[ALEXIA] YES, I AM A WOMAN
VERY INDEPENDENT,
COMPLETELY DETACHED, AND,
HONESTLY,
I DON'T USUALLY HAVE SEX TWO TIMES
TIMES WITH THE SAME MAN.
THE LAST THING I WANT IN
MY LIFE,
IT'S A COMMITMENT, UNDERSTAND?
[CRUITLING] I KNOW, BUT LOOK, IT'S
EXACTLY WHAT I WANT.
LOOK, I... I SWEAR TO YOU, I
I WILL NOT GET INVOLVED EITHER.
I... I JUST WANT... IT'S JUST SEX,
THAT'S IT, UNDERSTAND?
I SWEAR, IT'S JUST SEX, OK? ALEXIA, OK
LISTENING TO ME?
LOOK, LOOK, I'LL STAY 15 MINUTES
THEN YOU EXPEL ME,
NO COMMITMENT. ALEXIA! It's...
♪GOD PROTECT ME FROM YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
♪GOD HELP ME FROM YOUR ANGER♪
♪GOD MAKE ME IMMUNIZED FROM YOUR POISON♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR END♪
♪GOD PROTECT ME FROM YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
♪GOD HELP ME FROM YOUR ANGER♪
♪GOD MAKE ME IMMUNIZED FROM YOUR POISON♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR END♪
♪GOD GOD GO WITH ME♪
♪GOD SUPPORT ME♪
♪GOD LIFT ME UP♪
♪GOD GIVE ME STRENGTH♪
♪GOD FORGIVE ME FOR WANTING TO♪
♪GOD SAVE ME♪
♪AND KEEP IT FROM YOU♪
♪GOD GOD GO WITH ME♪
♪GOD SUPPORT ME♪
♪GOD LIFT ME UP♪
♪GOD GIVE ME STRENGTH♪
♪GOD FORGIVE ME FOR WANTING TO♪
♪GOD SAVE ME AND♪
♪AND KEEP IT FROM YOU♪
[DOOR CLOSE]
[CAR ENGINE]
♪GOD FORGIVE ME FOR WANTING TO♪
♪GOD SAVE ME♪
♪AND KEEP IT FROM YOU♪
♪GOD FORBID ME♪
♪KEEP IT FROM YOU♪
[SILENCE]
[WOMAN] TAKE YOUR BREATH THERE
IN THE BIG BELLY. THAT'S IT...
[KNOCKING ON GLASS]
[WOMAN] THIS, INSPIRING...
[ALEXIA] [WHISPERING] WHAT IS IT?
THAT?
[CRUCIBLE] WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DOING HERE?
[ALEXIA] WHAT ARE YOU
[CRUCIBLE] ARE YOU PREGNANT?
[ALEXIA] [WHISPERING]
PSYCHOPATH,
YOU'RE FOLLOWING ME, I'M GOING TO
CALL THE POLICE.
[CRUCIBLE] ANSWER, YOU ARE
PREGNANT?
[ALEXIA] "SHUT UP!" SHUT UP! NO
I HAVE NOTHING TO TALK ABOUT
FROM MY LIFE TO YOU. ONLY
THIS WAS WHAT WE NEEDED NOW,
I TALK ABOUT MY LIFE TO YOU!
[CRUCIBLE] A MONTH AGO, I WILL
TO BED WITH A WOMAN
AND NOW I FIND OUT SHE IS
PREGNANT.
[ALEXIA] WHO'S PREGNANT?
[WHISPERING] I'M NOT PREGNANT.
[CADINHO] WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE
THEN?
[ALEXIA] NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS!
GET OUT OF HERE, PREGO, GET OUT OF HERE!
[CRUCIBLE] AH... SWEAR ON YOUR LIFE
OF THE SON
WHAT'S NOT IN YOUR BELLY?
[ALEXIA] I HAVE NOTHING, NO
I HAVE NO CHILDREN
HERE IN MY BELLY, SO
I WON'T HAVE TO DO IT
NO OATH, OK? NOW, DO IT
A FAVOR FOR ME?
OH, BUT WHY AM I
TALKING ABOUT THESE THINGS TO YOU...
[CRUCIBLE] LOOK, BECAUSE...
IF, BY CHANCE,
YOU ARE PREGNANT WITH ME, YOU
I WOULD NEED TO KNOW
OF A GENETIC DISEASE
HEREDITARY OF MY FAMILY...
A HORRIBLE THING.
[SIGH] WHEW, BUT SINCE YOU DIDN'T
ARE YOU PREGNANT WITH ME?
NOT ANYONE, THANKS, THEN,
BIG KISS.
[STEPS]
[ALEXIA] CRUCIBLE... CRUCIBLE!
CRUCIBLE... CRUCIBLE. FOR.
WAIT FOR ME, LISTEN. WHAT A STORY
IS THIS A DISEASE?
YOU EVEN SAID YOU WERE CHAMPION OF
ROWING AT COLLEGE.
[CADINHO] ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT ME?
NOW?
[ALEXIA] NO, I'M FUCKED UP
FOR YOU.
OH MY GOD, IT'S A PROBLEM
CONGENITAL HEART,
RIGHT, TRUE?
[CRUCIBLE] IT STARTS IN THE HEART,
BUT THEN IT SPREADS
IN THE WHOLE BODY.
[ALEXIA] I KNEW IT. [SIGH] MY
GOD I KNEW IT,
IT CAN ONLY BE PUNISHMENT, MY GOD
HEAVEN. TELL ME THE TRUTH,
THIS STORY OF THE DISEASE. SPEAKS. IS
TRUE?
[CRUITLING] OK. THAT'S A LIE.
[ALEXIA] AH... LIAR! YOU
HE'S A BASTARD!
[CRUCIBLE] AND YOU? AND YOU?
YOU... YOU'RE WORSE THAN
A MAN HUNTER, YOU ARE
A... A SEMEN COLLECTOR,
IT'S NOT THAT?
[ALEXIA] I DIDN'T WANT ANYTHING
LIKE YOU.
[CRUCIBLE] WELL, NO,
JUST HAVE A CHILD WITH ME, RIGHT?
[ALEXIA] IT WASN'T EVEN FOR YOU
GET TO KNOW.
[CADINHO] NOW I KNOW, SO WHAT?
♪Ouch Ouch, Ouch Ouch, Ouch Ouch♪
♪THIS IS HOW YOU KILL DADDY♪
♪Ouch, Ouch Ouch♪
♪WHAT A DELICIOUS MOUTH♪
♪I WANT MORE♪
♪Ouch Ouch, Ouch Ouch, Ouch Ouch♪
♪THIS IS HOW YOU KILL DADDY♪
♪Ouch, Ouch Ouch♪
♪YOU SMELL SO GOOD♪
[TYPHOON] MOTHER, LOOK HERE, OH. I WANT
THAT THE WHOLE FAMILY
FROM MONALISA BE WELL TREATED,
DID YOU UNDERSTAND?
[MURICY] SURE, IMAGINE.
[TYPHOON] IS IT CLEAR?
[MURICY] SUPER, IMAGINE.
[MONALISA] [LAUGHTER] DONA MURICY,
TRY A SMALL PIE HERE
WHAT I DID, PROVE IT HERE.
[MURICY] BUT CALM DOWN, YOU SIT DOWN,
TALK TO PEOPLE.
MY SON HIRED WAITERS
TO SERVE.
[MONALISA] BUT I DON'T
I CAN STAND STILL,
I GET NERVOUS.
[IVANA] YOU CAN GET USED TO IT,
HEIN, MONALISA.
NOW YOU WILL HAVE LIFE OF
MADAM.
[MONALISA] IMAGINE... THEN, YOU KNOW
THE DAY I WILL BE A MADAME,
PEOPLE? I'M NOT GOING TO BE A MADAME
NEVER. NEVER! WHO WEEDED IT
IN THE FARM IN PARAÍBA, IT'S NOT POSSIBLE
FROM SITTING AND GROWING
ON THE COUCH, NO, I LIKE IT.
[MURICY] IS IT TRUE THAT YOU
DO THEY EAT LIZARDS IN THE NORTHEAST?
[LELECO] OH, BUT STOP
IMPLY, MURICY!
[MURICY] IT'S NOT A PISS,
AND TRUTH.
[DÉA] [STUTTERING] LOOK HERE,
DONA MURICY. WE STILL DON'T
DID YOU EAT A CALANGO, DIDN'T YOU SEE? BUT
LADY, KNOW THAT A FRIED ANT IS
MY DAUGHTER, IT COULD BE A PITEL.
[IVANA] OMG!
[MURICY] SO, SEE? I DON'T
DID I TELL YOU? YES... I KNEW IT
THAT YOU EAT ANIMALS
LITTLE ONE THERE.
[MONALISA] [CLEARING]
[CARMINHA] IF SOMEONE FALLS HERE
IT'S CERTAIN DEATH.
[URBAN AMBIENCE]
[CARMINHA] OH!
[MAX] MAN, STOP IT,
FOR GOD'S SAKE...
[CARMINHA] EXCELLENT SCENARIO,
MAX, EXCELLENT.
[MAX] YES, BUT YOU'RE GOING TO EXAGGERATE
DO THIS SCENE AGAIN,
THEN I REALLY FALL, FOR REAL,
I WANT TO SEE.
[CARMINHA] LEAVE IT TO ME... LEAVE IT TO ME
WITH ME, ONE OF THESE TIMES
PARAIBADA MUST ALREADY BE ALL THERE
IN THE HOUSE OF THE TYPHOON.
[MAX] FOR ME YOU'RE PAYING
A CRAZY GIRL TAKING RISKS
THAT MONEY THAT THE TYPHOON WAS GOING TO GIVE YOU
GIVE...
[CARMINHA] WHO WANTS MORE OF
LIFE HAS TO BE RISKED, MAX,
WHAT IS THIS? LEARN TO DREAM BIG,
FACE!
NOW, GET READY. GET READY
PRO INTERPRETING SHOW.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TALK]
[DÉA] LOOK... LOOK WHAT I
I BROUGHT IT. LOOK HERE. MONALISA,
HERE IS THE VEIL THAT YOUR GRANDMOTHER
USED ​​AT HER WEDDING
AND THAT YOU WILL USE IN YOURS.
[TALK]
[LELECO] LOOK HERE, LADY
DÉA, THIS WEDDING IS GOING TO BE
FROM BALACOBACO! BECAUSE, LOOK,
IT WILL RAIN PETALS
IN PINK, BUFFET FOR 500 PEOPLE AND
SHOW WITH A WELL-KNOWN SINGER.
[MONALISA] PEOPLE, WHAT A THING
BEAUTIFUL! ALL EMBROIDERED, LOOK!
OH, AUNT, THANK YOU.
[IVANA] SLOWLY WITH THE PILLOW,
HEIN, DAD, BECAUSE MONEY
YOU DON'T ACCEPT DISREGARD, HUH!
[LELECO] OH, IVANA IS A HAND
CLOSED, THIS ONE CONTROLS
THE FAMILY MONEY.
[MURICY] DOES IT AND DOES IT VERY WELL, IF
IF SHE DIDN'T CONTROL
FAMILY MONEY, NOT TYPHOON
I WAS SO WELL DONE
HOW IS HE TODAY, RIGHT, SONY?
[MONALISA] LOOK, YOU KNOW WHAT I
I THINK, DONA MURICY, SINCERELY,
700 PEOPLE IS A LOT OF PEOPLE, I
I DON'T EVEN KNOW 700 PEOPLE!
[TALK]
[MURICY] YOU DON'T KNOW, MY
LOVE, BUT LOOK,
THERE IS THE DIVINE BOARD, THERE
CLUB, HAS PEOPLE FROM THE NEIGHBORHOOD,
JUST THEN IT GAVE ABOUT 300
PEOPLE.
[IVANA] AND THESE PEOPLE, BY CHANCE,
DOES HE CALL YOU FOR SOMETHING, MOM?
[MURICY] THEY ARE VERY
NICE TO ME, IVANA!
[IVANA] OH, MOTHER, A BUNCH OF
EGG ASS, RIGHT?
JUST BECAUSE YOU BECAME A MOTHER
FAMOUS PLAYER.
[MURICY] DO YOU WANT TO SPEAK TO YOURSELF?
LIFE STOP PUTTING ME DOWN
DOWN? WHAT'S THIS, DEAR? I
I HAVE MY OWN CHARISMA
GUYS.
[IVANA] AH, THESE PEOPLE DON'T EVEN
THEY LOOKED AT YOUR FACE BEFORE
FOR HIM TO BECOME FAMOUS!
[MURICY] WHAT WHAT, MY DAUGHTER.
I GO OUT ON THE STREET
IT'S AN EVENT.
[IVANA] I'M WITH MONALISA,
200 PEOPLE IS A GOOD SIZE!
[MONALISA] PEOPLE, PEOPLE, OH,
LET ME SAY SOMETHING,
QUICKLY, I WANTED TO GET ONE UP
TOAST! EVERYONE HERE WITH ME,
A TOAST!
[TALK]
[MONALISA] [SHOUTING] WAITER!
[MONALISA] TAKE THESE, TAKE THESE
TWO, ​​MINE IS MISSING.
[LELECO] GO ON.
[TYPHOON] GIVE ME ONE.
[LELECO] GAVE.
[MONALISA] I WANTED TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT
THAT I WANT TO TALK ABOUT SOME
WORDS TOO. IT'S... EVERYONE
DO YOU KNOW THAT MY ENGAGEMENT WITH
TYPHOON TOOK A LONG TIME TO LEAVE.
[TALK]
[MONALISA] HE IN EUROPE, I
HERE, WE HAD TO HAVE
PATIENCE. [LAUGHTER] RIGHT, BUT I
I MEAN THAT...
[MONALISA] IT WAS WORTH THE WAIT.
[OLENKA] MY GOD, IT'S LOVE,
MY PEOPLE!
[LAUGHTER]
[MONALISA] AND THAT TODAY IS A
VERY SPECIAL MOMENT
IN MY LIFE,
AND I HAVE A VERY BIG NEWS
IMPORTANT TO GIVE. [LAUGHTER]
[TALK]
[JANAÍNA] YOU TYPHOON, YOU
TYPHOON, IT IS...
IT'S A GIRL NAME CARMINHA IN
TELEPHONE.
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA? ASK HER
CALL YOU IN A MOMENT.
[JANAÍNA] NO, NO. SHE SAID
THAT IS URGENT AND
IT SEEMS LIKE SHE'S DESPERATE.
[MONALISA] IT'S NOT THAT YOU TALK TO ME
"LEAVE IT",
I WANT TO FIND THE WORD OF
HEIGHT...
[TYPHOON] IT'S... PEOPLE, I... I
I'LL GO OVER THERE FOR A MOMENT
AND I'LL BE BACK.
[MONALISA] BUT WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
NOW?
[TYPHOON] I WILL ONLY SOLVE ONE
LITTLE BUSINESS. IT'S NOTHING, NO. NO
IT'S NOTHING, NO.
OH!... CLOSE IT.
[WOMAN] WHAT'S WRONG?
[MONALISA] I DON'T KNOW.
[TALK]
[MONALISA] AS I SAID,
WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT ANOTHER ONE
A LITTLE LITTLE.
[TALK]
[TYPHOON] HI, YOU CAN TALK.
[CARMINHA] TYPHOON, I'M SORRY
TO DISTURB.
I'M BOTHERING YOU, AREN'T I?
[TYPHOON] WE CANNOT TALK
ANOTHER TIME?
[CARMINHA] [CLUTTERED VOICE] NO,
I DON'T WANT TO TAKE UP YOUR TIME,
NO. I'M JUST CALLING YOU
TO TELL YOU THAT YOU ARE A
WONDERFUL PERSON,
A BEAUTIFUL PERSON.
LATELY, FROM THE THINGS THAT I
HAPPENED,
YOU WERE THE BEST OF THEM.
I'M CALLING YOU FOR ME
FIRE.
[TYPHOON] SAY GOODBYE? WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
GO?
[CARMINHA] [CLUTTERED VOICE] NO
IT MATTERS,
I DON'T WANT TO TAKE YOURS ANYMORE
TIME, YOU'RE SORRY, OK?
[TYPHOON] WAIT, WHAT'S UP?
HAPPENING?
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] I LOST THE
CONTROL,
I AM COMPLETELY
UNCONTROLLED.
WITHOUT MY GENESUS, I LOST MY
HEADING. OH!
[CRYING]
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] I DON'T
I CAN HOLD ON MORE.
I CAN'T STAND THE PAIN, MAN
GOD.
[CRYING]
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] MINE
WILLING...
IT'S DOING... CRAZY.
[TYPHOON] NO, WAIT, I
I'M GOING THERE.
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] NO
IT NEEDS.
[TYPHOON] I'M COMING. NO
DO NOTHING UNTIL I GET THERE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] THE SUCKER
IT'S COMING HERE.
[APPLAUSE]
[MAX] [SLOWLY]
SENSATIONAL.
[CARMINHA] YOU ALREADY KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO DO IT, DON'T YOU KNOW?
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[LELECO] LISTEN HERE, TYPHOON,
I...
[MURICY] WHAT IS THIS?
[LELECO] I DON'T KNOW, I WANT
KNOW. HE WENT TO THE BATHROOM,
AND THAT?
[WOMAN] HE WAS ALREADY SUPPOSED TO HAVE IT
RETURNED.
[MONALISA] OH MY GOD.
[SHOUTING] OH JANAINA! JANAINA,
GUYS, WHERE'S MY FIANCÉ?
YOU DISAPPEARED WITH HIM. FOR THE LOVE OF
GOD.
[JANAÍNA] HEY YOUR TYPHOON IS OUT.
[MONALISA] HOW DID IT COME OUT? HE
HE DIDN'T TELL ME ANYTHING.
[JANAÍNA] HE ASKED TO BE WARNED
THE LADY HE CAME DOWN HERE
BELOW TO BUY A WINE,
WHY WINE
THE THING HE OPENED WAS VINEGAR.
[IVANA] OH, THAT'S STRANGE,
PEOPLE.
[WOMAN] IT SEEMS TO ME THAT THE
YOUR FIANCÉ
ARE YOU PREPARING A SURPRISE FOR
YOU, DAUGHTER.
[MONALISA] NO, AUNT, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD
OF GOD.
OK... OK, SURPRISE,
I HAVE HAD A LOT OF SURPRISES
LATELY.
[MURICY] DIDN'T YOU SAY YOU WERE GOING
SAY SOMETHING IMPORTANT?
KEEP TALKING ABOUT IT FOR NOW.
[MONALISA] NO, NOTHING, NOTHING.
[LELECO] THAT "NOTHING, NOTHING. NOTHING,
NOTHING". WHAT, GOOD THING?
[MONALISA] OH, OH... LEAVE IT,
LET THE TYPHOON COME
WHAT I SAY, RIGHT? BETTER.
IN THE MEANTIME, LET'S DRINK THIS
CHAMPAGNE,
YOU KNOW, BEFORE IT GETS HOT.
[OLENKA] BECAUSE I CAN'T
STAY, YOU KNOW, RIGHT?
[IVANA] OH NO, OLENKA.
[OLENKA] I HAVE A SCHEME THERE.
I'M GOING TO SEE THE BOYS, OK?
[IVANA] OH, NO.
[OLENKA] THANK YOU. BYE, MY
GUYS, LOOK, KISSES!
[IVANA] GET OUT OF THE FRONT!
[OLENKA] NO, I'LL GO THIS WAY,
IT'S FASTER, GUYS.
[MAN] OK, BYE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA.
[CARMINHA] IT WASN'T FOR YOU
YOU CAME HERE, GO AWAY!
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA, CALM DOWN. LET'S GO
TO TALK.
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] STILL FOR
ABOVE I AM A COWARD.
I SHOULD HAVE BROKE UP WITH YOU ALREADY
THIS HAS BEEN A LONG TIME!
[TYPHOON] NO, NO, NO...
[CARMINHA] [SCREAM]
[TYPHOON] YOU'RE NOT A COWARD,
YOU WANT TO LIVE, CARMINHA!
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] I DON'T
WITH YOU.
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA, DO YOU WANT
TO LIVE.
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] ARE YOU
WRONG,
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE, I WANT
TO DIE.
I WANT TO FINISH
WITH THIS PAIN, MY GOD.
[TYPHOON] THIS PAIN WILL PASS,
CARMINHA. THIS PAIN WILL PASS!
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] HOW?
AS?
[TYPHOON] LOOK AT ME, LOOK AT ME
ME.
[CRYING]
[TYPHOON] I WILL HELP YOU. LOOK
FOR ME,
GIVE ME YOUR HAND, GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] GIVE ME YOUR HAND. GIVE ME YOUR
YOUR HAND.
[CARMINHA] WHAT FOR?
[CLUTTERED VOICE] THE WORLD DOES NOT
NEED A PERSON LIKE ME.
I AM USELESS.
[TYPHOON] DON'T SPEAK... YOU ARE A
WONDERFUL PERSON, CARMINHA.
DON'T SAY A THING
OF THESE.
[CARMINHA] YOU DON'T
DO YOU KNOW.
[TYPHOON] FOR THE LITTLE THAT I
I KNOW, I KNOW YOUR QUALITIES,
YOU ARE A WOMAN OF INTEGRITY,
YOU ARE A FAMILY WOMAN,
YOU WERE A GOOD WIFE,
YOU... YOU ARE SMART,
YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL, YOU ARE
LOVING, YOU HAVE LIFE
ENTIRELY AHEAD. YOU WILL
REBUILD YOUR LIFE
AND I WILL HELP YOU. GIVE ME A HAND.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
[CARMINHA] [GRUNT]
[TYPHOON] GIVE, GIVE, GIVE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] SORRY,
SORRY.
[CRYING]
[CARMINHA] I'M SORRY.
[TYPHOON] ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALL GOOD.
[MONALISA] JESUS ​​FROM HEAVEN, WHERE THE
HAS A TYPHOON COME IN? IT'S BEEN AN HOUR
AND A HALF THAT MAN LEFT AND NOT
BRING ME BACK THAT WINE.
[MURICY] AN IMPORTANT PERSON
SO, AS MY SON KNOWS,
IN HIS POSITION, HE SHOULD WALK
ALWAYS WITH PRIVATE SECURITY,
HE WILL ALWAYS BE A TARGET OF
KIDNAPPING, THAT'S THE TRUTH.
[LELECO] TURN THAT MOUTH AWAY!
[MURICY] I WON'T COME!
THE MOUTH IS MINE,
I GO WHEREVER I WANT!
[IVANA] CALM DOWN, GUYS! STOP IT!
YES, I MUST HAVE FLAT A TIRE,
ALREADY, ALREADY HE'S THERE.
[PHONE RINGING]
[TALK]
[IVANA] OH, IT MUST BE HIM.
[MONALISA] HELLO?
[MURICY] IS IT THE TYPHOON?
[MAX] PLEASE, MR. JORGE
ARAÚJO TYPHOON IS HERE?
[MONALISA] NO, HE DOESN'T
FIND, IT IS...
WHAT HAPPENED? WHO IS HERE?
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT... IT'S HIS BRIDE.
[MAX] THIS IS THE ONE SPEAKING HERE
MAJOR UBIRATAN SILVEIRA.
WE RECORD HERE A
OCCURRENCE,
A VEHICLE WITH THE LICENSE PLATE LNE-3152,
MUST BELONG TO YOUR FIANCÉ.
HERE ON DOMINGOS DE STREET
ALBUQUERQUE, AHEAD
TO NUMBER 736, HERE AT
GUADELOUPE.
[MONALISA] IN GUADELOUPE? BUT THE
WHAT HAPPENED
WITH HIS CAR?
[MAX] ACTUALLY, IT WAS NOTHING
SERIOUSLY, IT WAS AN ATTEMPT
FROM THEFT, THEY BROKE THE GLASS
DRIVER'S SIDE,
THAT'S IT.
[MONALISA] OK, BUT... AND MINE
GROOM? JORGE TUFÃO, PLAYER,
DO YOU KNOW HIM? IS HE THERE?
OK, THANK YOU.
[TALK]
[LELECO] DID YOU CRASH YOUR CAR?
[MONALISA] NO, NO, NOTHING LIKE THAT.
IT WAS AND... HIS CAR SUFFERED A
ATTEMPTED ROBBERY
AND WAS FOUND IN GUADELOUPE.
NOW I WANT TO KNOW,
WHAT HAPPENED? TYPHOON
I JUST CAME DOWN TO BUY
WINE, WHAT HIS CAR
ARE YOU DOING IN GUADELOUPE?
[MURICY] IN GUADELOUPE? THEY TOOK THE
MY SON! THEY KIDNAPPED HIM
MY SON! IVANA, FOR THE LOVE OF
GOD, YOU WILL PAY WHAT THEY
ASK FOR RESCUE...
[TALK]
[MONALISA] IT IS IN GUADELOUPE THE
APARTMENT THAT TYPHOON BOUGHT
AND LOANED IT TO THAT WIDOW, THAT'S WHERE,
IT'S THERE. OH... OH JANAÍNA!
[JANAINA] HERE.
[MURICY] WHICH WIDOW IS THIS?
[MONALISA] BY CHANCE, IT WAS A
SO MUCH CARMINHA
WHO CALLED TYPHOON AT THE TIME THAT
DID HE LEAVE?
[JANAINA] OH...
[MONALISA] SPEAK UP, WOMAN!
WAS IT CARMINHA?
[JANAINA] IT WAS.
[MONALISA] CARMINHA...
[LELECO] WHO IS THIS WOMAN?
WHO IS THIS WOMAN?
[WOMAN] WAIT, MONALISA, WHAT
I'M GOING WITH YOU.
[IVANA] WAIT, I'M GOING TOO,
WAIT...
[MURICY] PEOPLE, BUT WHO IS IT?
CARMINH?
[IVANA] AND I KNOW, MOTHER?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[SHATTERING GLASS]
[STEPS]
[TYPHOON] TAKE THIS WATER WITH
SUGAR AND THIS CALMING DRUG,
YOU NEED TO SLEEP, REST.
[CARMINHA] I'M SO
WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
I DISRUPTED YOUR LIFE TODAY,
WASN'T IT?
[TYPHOON] IT'S OK, IT WAS FOR
A GOOD CAUSE.
[CARMINHA] YOU ARE A SAINT.
A PERSON WHO DOES WHAT YOU DO
DID IT FOR A STRANGER,
FOR A POOR GIRL LIKE ME, IT CAN ONLY BE
TO BE CALLED A SAINT.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] YOU WILL NEVER GO AGAIN
BEING ALONE,
YOU WILL HAVE ME BY YOUR SIDE FOR
ALWAYS.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] WHO ARE YOU?
[TYPHOON] MONALISA.
[MONALISA] I DON'T BELIEVE THAT
YOU DID IT TO ME AGAIN.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY PACE♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK IT♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪