[SILENCE]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[BEGONIA] [CRYING] DADDY, OUR DADDY.
[NINA] [CRYING] HE DIDN'T SUFFER, BEGONIA,
IT ALL HAPPENED VERY FAST.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NINA] IT'S TIME TO TAKE A BIG TRIP.
[NINA] I'M GOING BACK TO BRAZIL.
[BEGONIA] DADDY JUST DIED
AND YOU'RE TELLING ME YOU'RE GOING TO BRAZIL?
I NEED YOU HERE, SISTER, THE FAMILY HAS TO STAY UNITED.
[NINA] SORRY... SORRY, BEGONIA IT WASN'T THE TIME
RIGHT TO TELL YOU THAT.
[BEGONIA] ARE YOU REALLY GOING TO BRAZIL?
[NINA] I DON'T KNOW, I'LL THINK ABOUT IT AND IF IT IS,
NO... IT'S NOTHING FOR NOW.
[BEGONIA] OF COURSE YOU WILL, NINA, AND IT'S FOR NOW, YES.
I KNOW YOU, YOU DECIDE EVERYTHING ALONE,
WHY ARE YOU LIKE THIS, HUH? YOU NEVER OPEN UP,
IT SEEMS LIKE HE DOESN'T TRUST ANYONE.
[NINA] IT'S NOT TRUE.
[BEGONIA] DADDY WAS RIGHT, YOU NEVER FORGOT THAT ONE
WOMAN, ONLY THINK ABOUT YOUR REVENGE,
NOW THAT DADDY IS GONE THERE IS NOTHING LEFT
THAT KEEPS YOU HERE, RIGHT? YOUR RELATIONSHIP WAS ONLY WITH HIM,
IT'S AS IF MERCEDES AND I ARE NOT PART OF YOUR FAMILY.
[NINA] YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU, BEGONIA.
[BEGONIA] MY MOTHER, SHE DIDN'T TREATS YOU LIKE A DAUGHTER,
SHE MADE A MISTAKE, BUT SHE'S DEAD.
NOW, MY FATHER HAS ALSO DIED AND YOU ARE GOING TO LEAVE ME!
[NINA] NO, I WILL NEVER LEAVE YOU.
[BEGONIA] STOP LYING, NINA!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NINA] BEGONIA!
[TYPHOON] [STUTTERING] WAIT.
[JORGINHO] [JUMBLE] YOU
IT'S NOT MY MOTHER. [LAUGHTER] IT'S NOT!
IT IS NOT!
[MURICY] HOW DO YOU DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
AT YOUR FATHER'S PARTY, YOU BRAT!
[LELECO] MURICY, DON'T ADD MORE WOOD TO THE FIRE.
[JORGINHO] [JUMBLE] BECAUSE I DON'T FEEL LIKE I BELONG
I DON'T FEEL ABOUT THIS FAMILY.
[DÉBORA] ENOUGH, ENOUGH, STOP!
[TYPHOON] MY SON, HOW IS IT
DO YOU DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT WITH YOUR MOTHER?
APOLOGIZE TO HER NOW.
[JORGINHO] [CRYING] I'M NOT HER SON, DAD,
SHE'S NOT MY MOTHER, DAD.
[TYPHOON] MY SON, DON'T SAY THAT. DON'T SAY THAT, MY SON.
[JORGINHO] [CRYING] FORGIVE, FATHER. FORGIVE. I'M SORRY.
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] HE HATES ME.
WHAT DID I DO TO DESERVE THIS...
[IVANA] MUSIC, MAESTRO!
MUSIC!
[MURICY] YES, PEOPLE, YES! THE PARTY ISN'T OVER.
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] THE PARTY IS OVER FOR ME.
[TYPHOON] SHIT, GO, GO, GO. LET'S GO IN.
I'M GOING TO MAKE YOU SOME MEAL, UNDERSTAND?
YOU TAKE A BATH. DON'T LOOK BACK, CARMINHA.
[DIOGENES] SEE? IT'S LIKE I ALWAYS SAY, ISN'T IT,
MONEY DOESN'T BRING HAPPINESS.
[SILAS] YES, YES, DIOGENES, THE BIGGER THE JUMP,
THE BIGGER THE FALL, RIGHT?
[DEBORAH] JORGINHO...
[VERÔNICA] WHERE DÉBORA WENT TO TIE UP THE DONKEY
HER! LOVE, THIS BOY IS CRAZY!
[CADINHO] ANOTHER ONE FOR DÉBORA'S COLLECTION,
OR DID YOU FORGET ABOUT YOUR DAUGHTER'S OTHER BOYFRIENDS, HUH?
THIS IS DELICIOUS.
[JORGINHO] [JUMBLE] SATISFIED NOW?
[LAUGHTER] YOU'RE THE ONE WHO INSISTED THAT I COME HERE.
[DÉBORA] YES, BUT I DIDN'T KNOW WHO YOU WERE
COMPLETELY CRAZY!
[JORGINHO] [JUMBLE] Yes,
BUT NOW THAT YOU KNOW...
[DÉBORA] STOP, JORGINHO. YOU'RE NOT GOING TO DRIVE,
YOU'RE COMPLETELY DRUNK!
[PANTING BREATHING]
[JORGINHO] I NEED TO GO SOMEWHERE,
I NEED SOMEONE.
[DÉBORA] BUT WHAT PLACE?
WHAT PERSON? TALK TO ME, OPEN UP TO ME!
[JORGINHO] [JUMBLE] I NEED TO BE ALONE.
[DÉBORA] WAIT! NO, STOP, JORGINHO!
JORGINHO, OPEN... OPEN THIS CAR, LET ME GO WITH YOU.
STOP, JORGINHO! JORGINHO!
[VEHICLE IN MOTION]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NINA] DADDY'S WAKE WILL BE TOMORROW THEN,
FROM EIGHT.
[MERCEDES] WAS BEGONIA USING DRUGS?
[NINA] I DON'T THINK SO.
WE DISCUSSED.
[MERCEDES] WHY DID THEY DISCUSS?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NINA] NONSENSE.
[NINA] DID YOU TALK TO THAT FRIEND OF YOURS?
FROM THE POLICE ABOUT THE BEGONIA?
[HECTOR] I SAID. THE POLICE ARE LOOKING FOR HER,
IT APPEARS THAT THE CAR WAS SEEN IN A FAVELA NEAR GODOY CRUZ.
[MERCEDES] WENT TO BUY DRUGS, IT CAN ONLY BE.
[NINA] AS IF EVERYTHING WE DO WASN'T ENOUGH
IT'S HAPPENING NOW, MORE OF THIS.
[HECTOR] LEAVE IT, I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO
WITH MY POLICE CONTACTS, HUM?
[MERCEDES] LET'S SEE IF SHE SHOWS UP TO THE WAKE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[HECTOR] WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO, MY LOVE?
WANT TO STAY HERE? WANT TO REST A LITTLE?
WANT TO COME TO MY HOUSE?
[NINA] IT MIGHT BE GOOD TO GET OUT OF HERE FOR A LITTLE BIT.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHERE JORGINHO WENT?
[DÉBORA] HE SAID HE WAS GOING TO VISIT SOMEONE,
BUT HE DIDN'T TELL ME WHO HE WAS.
[CRUCIBLE] OK, LOOK, GOOD NIGHT. LOOK, IF YOU NEED IT
SOMEHOW, WE'RE THERE, HUH?
[MURICY] THANK YOU.
[TYPHOON] SORRY FOR THE TUMBLER, THE CONFUSION.
[VERÔNICA] IMAGINE! WITH US THERE'S NO SUCH THINGS
NO, RIGHT, CRUCIBLE?
EH, NO, I JUST WANTED TO SAY GOODBYE TO YOUR WIFE.
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA IS... WITHDRAWN.
[VERÔNICA] OH, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
[CRUITLING] BUT, LOOK, I'M SURE EVERYTHING WILL WORK OUT FINE,
JORGINHO AND HIS WIFE WILL UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER
AND OUR CHILDREN ARE GOING TO GET MARRIED, AREN'T THEY?
AND DONA MURICY HERE WHO WAS MY SECOND MOTHER,
NOW YOU WILL OFFICIALLY JOIN THE FAMILY.
[KISS SNAP]
[MURICY] YOUR CRUCIBLE,
YOU'RE STILL MY BIG BABY. [LAUGHTER]
[CADINHO] LOOK, CONGRATULATIONS ON THE PARTY, HUH? HOW MANY GUESTS?
[MURICY] 400 SITTING.
[CADINHO] WOW! I'M GOING TO ASK FOR SOME MONEY SOON
LOANED TO YOU, HUH?
[MURICY] [LAUGHTER] IT SEEMS LIKE IT. I KNOW YOU'RE RICH,
YOU'RE A MILLIONAIRE. DID YOU EAT RIGHT?
[VERÔNICA] EVERYTHING WAS GREAT, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[CADINHO] VERY, VERY GOOD, ALTHOUGH I REALLY WANTED IT
IT WAS THE COD YOU MADE.
[MURICY] [LAUGHTER] I PROMISE YOU THAT I WILL DO IT AND I INVITE YOU,
I INVITE YOU.
[VERÔNICA] THANK YOU. LOVE, SHALL WE GO?
[CRUCIBLE] LET'S GO, LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
[MURICY] SORRY FOR ANYTHING, GUYS.
[TYPHOON] GOOD NIGHT.
[IVANA] COME ON, MAX, LET GO.
[LAUGHTER]
YOU'RE A GOOD DANCER I KNOW.
[MAX] YOU'RE REALLY GOING TO MAKE A MISTAKE FOR THIS, HUH, IVANA?
WE'LL BE THE LAST TO LEAVE THE DANCE FLOOR?
[IVANA] OH, I DON'T OWE ANYONE ANYTHING, SO WHAT?
I AM RICH! [LAUGHTER]
[MAX] LOW MOOD PARTY... THIS IS YOUR BROTHER'S FAULT, THE TYPHOON'S FAULT,
SEE? THERE IS NO FIRMNESS WITH JORGINHO. IF HE WERE MY SON,
I WANTED TO SEE IF HE WAS GOING TO DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
[IVANA] OH, MAX, STOP THINKING ABOUT JORGINHO.
YOU SHOULD BE WORRIED ABOUT OUR CHILDREN, HUH?
[LAUGHTER] THIS MONTH I'M GOING TO START TREATMENT.
[LAUGHTER] THE BABIES AND THE BABIES ARE COMING. [LAUGHTER] OH, OH, LOVE!
LOVE! LOVE! IF WE GET LUCK,
I'LL GET THREE AT ONCE.
[LAUGHTER] TOAST, LOVE, TOAST.
[MAX] BABY, BABY, CALM DOWN, IT'S OVER,
IT'S OVER, CALM DOWN, PST...
[VEHICLE IN MOTION]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[JORGINHO] MOTHER LUCINDA!
[JORGINHO] MOTHER!
[DOG BARKING]
[JORGINHO] MOTHER.
[LUCINDA] JORGINHO.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[JORGINHO] OH MOTHER.
[LUCINDA] WHAT HAPPENED, JORGINHO?
[JORGINHO] OH MOM, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO INVITE ME IN, ARE YOU?
[LUCINDA] WHAT'S UP, MY SON, YOU'RE... YOU'RE DRUNK,
YOU'RE DRIVING DRUNK. WHAT'S GOING ON?
TELL ME, WHAT WAS IT?
[JORGINHO] I SHOULD NEVER HAVE LET THEM TAKE ME AWAY FROM HERE.
[SNIFLE] THEY COULDN'T HAVE TAKEN ME, THEY COULDN'T.
[LUCINDA] COME WITH ME, COME. COME WITH ME, COME.
COME WITH ME, SUPPORT ME HERE, GO, I'LL TAKE YOU, COME.
COME ON, LET'S GO INSIDE.
[HECTOR] GO BACK TO BED, LOVE. YOU ALMOST DIDN'T SLEEP.
[NINA] I BETTER TELL YOU RIGHT AWAY.
[HECTOR] "TALK ABOUT WHAT?"
[NINA] I'M COMING BACK TO BRAZIL, HECTOR.
[HECTOR] [LAUGHTER] WHAT DO YOU MEAN? YOU'RE GOING TO TRIP TO BRAZIL?
TAKE ME WITH YOU TO PRACTICE MY PORTUGUESE.
[NINA] IT'S NOT A TRIP.
[NINA] I'M MOVING THERE.
[NINA] I'M GOING TO LIVE THERE.
[HECTOR] WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[HECTOR] IS IT JUST ME OR ARE YOU BREAKING UP WITH ME?
[NINA] THAT'S IT, HECTOR. SORRY, BUT IT'S OVER.
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY PACE♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK IT♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[HECTOR] WHAT DO YOU MEAN "IT'S OVER"?
[HECTOR] UNTIL TWO MINUTES AGO WE WERE
IN LOVE, MAKING PLANS FOR THE FUTURE.
[HECTOR] YOU SLEPT HUGGING ME.
[NINA] I NEVER MADE PLANS FOR THE FUTURE WITH YOU, HECTOR.
OUR HISTORY HAS NO FUTURE, IT NEVER HAS.
BETTER TO END HERE.
[HECTOR] [LAUGHTER] YOU'RE OUT OF BREAK, THAT'S IT, IT CAN ONLY BE,
I DON'T BELIEVE A WORD YOU'RE SAYING.
[NINA] IT WILL BE BETTER FOR ME AND YOU.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NINA] WE'RE WASTING TIME ON EACH OTHER.
YOU WILL STILL FIND THE RIGHT PERSON FOR YOU.
[HECTOR] WAIT, WHO IS THIS PERSON TELLING ME?
THESE THINGS? IS IT NINA, MY GIRLFRIEND?
THE BOSS OF MY RESTAURANT? OR IS IT?
AN ALIEN WHO TOOK POSSESSION OF THIS BODY?
[NINA] I AM THAT PERSON, HECTOR,
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO DOESN'T KNOW ME PROPERLY.
[HECTOR] YOU'RE LYING, YOU LOVE ME, I KNOW.
[NINA] I DON'T LOVE YOU. I NEVER LOVED YOU.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NINA] THAT'S THE TRUTH.
[HECTOR] WHAT'S GOING ON IN THAT HEAD OF YOURS?
ARE YOU WANTING TO BURN ALL YOUR SHIPS, IS THAT IT?
END EVERYTHING WITH ME, NO CHANCE OF COMING BACK,
ARE YOU LEAVING THE RESTAURANT TOO?
[NINA] I'M GOING TO LIVE IN BRAZIL, HECTOR.
I'M GOING TO GET A JOB THERE.
[HECTOR] WHAT "VAS A HACER EN"
BRAZIL?
[NINA] I ALREADY TOLD YOU, I'M GOING TO GET A JOB THERE,
I ALREADY GOT A CONTACT.
[NINA] I DON'T BELONG TO THIS LAND, I NEVER HAVE.
NOW THAT MY FATHER IS DEAD, THERE IS NOTHING LEFT
LET ME BE TRAPPED HERE.
[HECTOR] "Y YOUR SISTERS"?
[NINA] I AM THE ADOPTED DAUGHTER, HECTOR.
MY LATE ADOPTIVE MOTHER ALWAYS MADE IT CLEAR
THAT I NEVER REALLY BELONGED TO THIS FAMILY.
[HECTOR] HOW "CAN" YOU BE SO COLD? AND YOUR PROFESSION?
YOUR FRIENDS?
[HECTOR] YOU'RE A SUCCESS AS A BOSS HERE, ARE YOU?
IN ARGENTINA. "Y JA ME QUEDO SOLO WITH MY RESTAURANT,
ALSO, NOW", HUH?
[NINA] "NADIE ES INSUSTITUIBLE".
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[HECTOR] YOU WANT TO PROVOKE MY ANGRY, DON'T YOU?
[HECTOR] GOT IT WRONG.
[HECTOR] "NO TE CREO EN UNA SOLA PALABRA DE LO ESTAS DICIENDO".
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NINA] "BUENO, IF YOU WANT, YOU CAN CONTINUE DENYING IT".
[NINA] BYE, HECTOR. "HOW HAPPY YOU ARE."
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[JORGINHO] I MISS RITA SO MUCH.
[JORGINHO] SHE NEVER GAVE THE NEWS?
[LUCINDA] NEVER GAVE ANY NEWS. SHE DISAPPEARED IN THE WORLD, RIGHT?
[JORGINHO] I SO WANTED TO SEE HER AGAIN.
SOMETIMES I FEEL LONG FOR THE PAST.
[STEPS]
[JORGINHO] IT'S A TIME WHEN WE LIVED HERE, IN MY LIFE,
RUNNING HERE AND HERE.
[LUCINDA] WHAT'S THIS? STOP THE NONSENSE, THIS IS A GARBAGE DUMP.
HERE WE HAVE TO BE VERY STRONG, OTHERWISE WE WILL GET OVER SOON
SICK, IT DOESN'T LASTS LONG.
LISTEN HERE, BECAUSE YOU'RE GETTING INTO TROUBLE
WHERE DOESN'T IT EXIST? HAVE A BEAUTIFUL GIRLFRIEND,
FOOTBALL TALENT, YOUR LIFE IS WINNING.
GO BACK TO YOUR HOME AND YOUR FAMILY, THAT'S THE BEST THING THAT CAN BE
YOU HAVE TO DO IT, OK?
[JORGINHO] THAT FAMILY IS A LIE.
[JORGINHO] I FEEL IT'S NOT TRUE.
[JORGINHO] [SIGH]
TYPHOON IS A BIG GUY, YOU KNOW? BIG FATHER,
I HAVE NOTHING TO COMPLAIN ABOUT, BUT...
CARMINHA IS NO GOOD.
[LUCINDA] "NOT GOOD" WHY?
[JORGINHO] I DON'T KNOW WHY, I FEEL IT.
[JORGINHO] I DON'T KNOW HOW TO EXPLAIN.
[JORGINHO] IT MAY EVEN SEEME CRAZY WHAT I'M GOING TO SAY, BUT
IF I COULD, I WOULD TAKE MY FATHER AND MY SISTER AND TAKE THEM OUT OF THERE
FROM INSIDE, I TOOK IT OUT OF THAT HOUSE.
[JORGINHO] AND YOU ALSO KNOW THAT I NEVER UNDERSTOOD MYSELF
WITH HER, FROM THE BEGINNING.
[LUCINDA] YES, BUT SHE LIKES YOU. SHE LOVES YOU, WHAT'S THAT.
[JORGINHO] BUT I CAN'T LIKE HER.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[JORGINHO] I CAN'T.
[JORGINHO] MY MOTHER IS YOU.
[LUCINDA] [LAUGHTER] THANK YOU, MY SON, YOU TOO.
YES, I THINK THAT YOU WILL NEVER REALLY UNDERSTAND WITH
CARMINHA. BUT SHE ALWAYS TREATED YOU VERY WELL.
AND LOOK, SHE NEVER GAVE YOU A REASON TO DO SOMETHING BAD WITH HER.
GO THERE, GO AND AGREE WITH HER, GO. ASK FOR FORGIVENESS...
[JORGINHO] NO, AFTER WHAT I DID, THERE'S NO CLIMATE
TO GO BACK TO THAT HOUSE, I'LL GO SOMEWHERE ELSE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[JORGINHO] WHY DON'T YOU COME LIVE WITH ME?
[LUCINDA] IMAGINE, SON. IMAGINE, MY PLACE IS HERE,
WITH MY CHILDREN.
[SIGH] YES, THE WORLD OUT THERE IS NOT FOR ME, NO.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] CRAP OMELET, MY GOD.
JANAÍNA DOESN'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO DO THAT!
TYPHOON, I MEAN I'M REALLY LISTENING TO WHAT I
AM I LISTENING? ARE YOU TRYING TO TELL ME THAT WHAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY
AT OUR WEDDING PARTY, IT WASN'T THE WORST EMBARRASSMENT
FROM THE HISTORY OF THE NEIGHBORHOOD?
[TYPHOON] IT HAPPENS IN EVERY FAMILY, MY LOVE.
[CARMINHA] HOW DOES IT "HAPPEN IN ANY FAMILY?"
A SON BEATS HIS MOTHER IN FRONT OF 50 PHOTOGRAPHERS
AND 400 GUESTS? IT'S A COMMON THING, RIGHT, TYPHOON?
[RUNNING WATER FROM THE TAP]
[TYPHOON] MY LOVE, I'M GOING TO TALK TO HIM, OK?
NOT WHAT YOU WANT? I'LL TALK TO HIM,
HE WILL APOLOGIZE, AND EVERYTHING WILL GO BACK TO NORMAL.
[CARMINHA] BUT YOU DON'T EXIST.
MY GOD IN HEAVEN, YOU DON'T EXIST!
[TYPHOON] BUT NO...
[CARMINHA] SO YOU MEAN THAT,
IF JORGINHO APOLOGIZES TO ME,
IS EVERYTHING OK? IS EVERYTHING GREAT?
[TYPHOON] ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
[CARMINHA] YOU WILL CALL THEM
50 PHOTOGRAPHERS
WHEN HE APOLOGIZED TO ME?
[TYPHOON] OH MY GOD.
[CARMINHA] YOU KEEP COVERING THE SUN WITH A SIEVE,
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO! JORGINHO IS A SERIOUS PROBLEM
THAT WE HAVE. HE HATES ME!
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT DID I DO TO DESERVE THIS, SEE? WHAT DID I DO?
[TYPHOON] LOOK HERE, STOP THE DRAMA, OK? STOP THE DRAMA.
HE DOESN'T HATE YOU AT ALL. DO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT IS, MY LOVE? YOUTH.
[CARMINHA] WHAT "YOUTH?"
[TYPHOON] Yes.
[CARMINHA] LEFT ADOLESCENCE A LONG TIME AGO,
HE IS A MAN, BUT HE IS AN UNBALANCED MAN. WHY?
THERE IS NO LIMIT! AND IT'S YOUR FAULT. OF COURSE IT'S YOUR FAULT.
HE HAD HIS PASSION ON THE BOY'S HEAD HIS WHOLE LIFE.
JORGINHO IS A LOSER! OF COURSE HE HAS NO JUDGMENT,
OF COURSE, THERE NEVER WERE LIMITS.
[TYPHOON] JORGINHO HAS TALENT, WRITE WHAT I'M TELLING YOU:
HE WILL HAVE A BRILLIANT CAREER IN FOOTBALL...
[CARMINHA] NOTHING WILL HAPPEN! IF IT CONTINUES LIKE THIS,
YOU WILL SPEND THE REST OF YOUR LIFE SITTING ON THE RESERVE BENCH
FROM DIVINO FUTEBOL CLUBE, THIS IS WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO IT.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] YOU BETTER HAVE A SERIOUS TALK WITH HIM.
I WANT TO SEE YOU BECOME A FATHER! I WANT TO SEE YOU BECOME A MAN!
[TOGETHER] "PADRE NUESTRO QUE ESTÁS EN LO CIELOS,
HALLOWED BE THY NAME".
[MAN] "MAY MARTIN REST ETERNALLY
"BY THE SIDE OF OUR CREATOR"
[NINA] [SNIFLE]
[MAN] "EN NOMBRE DEL PADRE DEL HIJO Y DEL ESPIRITU SANTO..."
[BEGONIA] AMEN!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[BEGONIA] "IN THE NAME OF THE SON"? AND OF THE DAUGHTERS, FATHER?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[BEGONIA] ARE YOU NOT GOING TO TALK ABOUT YOUR DAUGHTERS?
[CRYING] WHERE'S MY DADDY, NINA?
WHERE'S MY DADDY? GET HIM OUT OF HERE!
[NINA] CALM DOWN, BEGONIA! CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN,
WE'LL HAVE TO ACCEPT IT.
[BEGONIA] SHUT UP, NINA, IT'S NOT TRUE!
[MERCEDES] BEGONIA, BEHAVE, TALK SOFTLY!
[BEGONIA] LEAVE ME, MERCEDES!
I SAY WHAT I WANT!
IF I WANT TO SHOUT HERE I WILL SHOUT!
[MERCEDES] COME ON, NINA, GET HER OUT OF HERE.
[NINA] [WHISPERING] CALM DOWN. CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN!
[BEGONIA] [CRYING] NINA, YOU'RE GOING AWAY,
DADDY IS GOING AWAY, I'M GOING TO BE ALONE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NINA] I'LL COME TO SEE YOU, I PROMISE YOU.
[BEGONIA] [VOICE OVERWHELMED] YOU'RE LYING,
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW ABOUT ANYONE ANYMORE. GO AWAY, GO, NINA!
GO! I WANT TO BE ALONE!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NINA] BEGONIA!
[NINA] BEGONIA. BEGONIA, CALM DOWN, BEGONIA! [SIGH]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[HORN]
[NINA] STOP THAT CAR, BEGONIA.
[BEGONIA] I WON'T STOP, NINA! WHY DID YOU COME IN HERE, HUH?
[NINA] [SHOUTING] STOP THIS CAR, I'M IN CHARGE!
[BEGONIA] YOU DON'T RULE ME!
[NINA] [SCREAMING] BE CAREFUL!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[BEGONIA] GET OUT, NINA! GET OUT, NINA!
LET GO!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NINA] WHAT'S THIS BEGONIA?
[BEGONIA] IT DOESN'T MATTER.
[NINA] YOU CAN BE ARRESTED. SPEAK UP!
[BEGONIA] IS ECSTASY.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[BEGONIA] WHAT ARE YOU DOING, NINA? STOP!
[NINA] I'M A FIRST OFFENDER. YOU'VE BEEN ARRESTED BEFORE,
IF YOU GET IN JAIL AGAIN, YOU'RE GOING TO STAY THERE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MAN] "QUE TIENE EN LA MANO, SEÑORITA? EN LA MANO! HUH?
[MAN] "GET OUT OF THE CAR, PLEASE."
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MAN] FOLLOW "NUESTRA"
PATROL.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MAN] DOCUMENT, PLEASE,
[JORGINHO] SPEAK, FATHER.
[TYPHOON] ARE YOU OK?
[JORGINHO] OK... I DON'T THINK IT'S ANY USE
I APOLOGIZE FOR YESTERDAY, RIGHT?
[TYPHOON] NO, IT'S NO USE. YOU HAVE TO APOLOGIZE
FOR YOUR MOTHER FIRST.
[JORGINHO] SHE'S NOT MY MOTHER.
[TYPHOON] MY GOD IN HEAVEN, STOP IT, JORGINHO.
SHE'S YOUR MOTHER, OF COURSE SHE'S A MOTHER, BOY.
[JORGINHO] I ONLY KNOW ONE THING, DAD, I'M NOT GOING TO THAT HOUSE
GO BACK, NO, I'M GOING SOMEWHERE ELSE, I'M GOING TO DÉBORA'S HOUSE.
[TYPHOON] YES, AFTER THE MESS YOU MADE WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
I DOUBT SHE WILL OPEN THE DOOR FOR YOU.
[JORGINHO] IT MAY BE, BUT I'M NOT GOING BACK TO THAT HOUSE
NO MORE, I'M GOING SOMEWHERE ELSE.
[TYPHOON] MY SON, TELL ME ONE THING: WHERE DID YOU GO?
AT NIGHT? TELL THE TRUTH!
[JORGINHO] I WENT TO THE DUMP.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[JORGINHO] TO MOTHER LUCINDA'S HOUSE.
[TYPHOON] YOU END MY PARTY, DRIVE DRUNK
AND ARE YOU GOING TO SLEEP IN THE DUMP? I SPENT THE NIGHT AWAKE THINKING ABOUT YOU.
DO YOU WANT TO WORRY ME TO DEATH?
[JORGINHO] OF COURSE NOT...
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[JORGINHO] YOU KNOW WHAT? I WON'T GIVE YOU ANY MORE WORK,
I'M GOING... I'M GOING TO DISAPPEAR FOR A WHILE, I'M GOING TO DISAPPEAR.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS, MY SON?
PEOPLE KEEP TELLING ME THAT THE PROBLEMS THAT HAPPEN
WITH YOU, IN REALITY, THE PROBLEM IS MINE, UNDERSTAND?
I'M THE ONE TO BLAME BECAUSE I KEEP RUNNING MY HAND ON YOU
HEAD. WHAT CAN I DO? LET'S GO.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[JORGINHO] WHERE TO?
[TYPHOON] COMES.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] MY SON, YOU'RE LUCKY. THIS APARTMENT
HERE JUST LEASED.
[JORGINHO] BUT I DIDN'T WANT TO GIVE YOU ANY MORE WORK,
NO, DAD. MAN, I WOULD STAY ANYWHERE.
A SLAB HIT THERE IN DIVINO AND I WAS ALREADY FINE.
[TYPHOON] MAN, SON, STAY HERE IN IPANEMA, UNDERSTAND?
YOU'RE CLOSE TO YOUR GIRLFRIEND, GO THERE, TAKE A DIVE,
WALK ON THE SIDEWALK.
[JORGINHO] MAN, ARE YOU SURE YOU'LL RELEASE ME?
HERE IN THE SOUTH ZONE? YOU DON'T KNOW ANYONE HERE, DAD.
THERE ARE ONLY SOMEBODY HERE.
[TYPHOON] ARE YOU GOING TO REFUSE MY OFFER?
[JORGINHO] NO, NO. NO WAY, I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
THANKS!
[TYPHOON] NOW, I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING. THIS SOUP WILL NOT
LEAVE FOR FREE, NO. WILL YOU HAVE TO PROMISE ME SOMETHING?
YOU WILL FOCUS ON YOUR CAREER.
[JORGINHO] MAN, TELL THE REAL THING, RIGHT, DAD. YOU MUST...
IT MUST BE VERY HARD FOR YOU TO KNOW THAT AT MY AGE
YOU HAD BEEN CALLED UP FOR THE NATIONAL TEAM, YOU WERE THROWING IT AWAY
OF THE COUNTRY AND... AND I'M A RESERVE OF THE DIVINE FOOTBALL CLUB, RIGHT?
[TYPHOON] JORGINHO, JORGINHO, PAY ATTENTION:
YOU CAN BE A GREAT SOCCER PLAYER IF YOU WANT TO.
YOU HAVE TO WANT IT...
[JORGINHO] NO, I DON'T HAVE YOUR TALENT, NO, FATHER.
[TYPHOON] YES, THERE IS. YES, THERE IS, MY SON. THERE IS EVEN MORE THAN THAT,
THIS ISN'T A TALK ABOUT A PROUD FATHER, NO. NOW, YOU ARE
TRIPING YOU? YOU HAVE TO CONCENTRATE YOU HAVE TO HAVE
DISCIPLINE. DO YOU THINK YOU CAN PLAY WELL BY SLEEPING IN LATE?
DRINKING EVERY DAY, MY SON, WHAT'S HAPPENING
IN YOUR HEAD?
[JORGINHO] A LOT OF THINGS HURT. I FEEL VERY LOST.
[TYPHOON] SO, TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THIS OPPORTUNITY THAT YOUR FATHER
IT'S GIVING YOU THE WAY TO ORGANIZE YOUR HEAD, UNDERSTAND?
ORGANIZE YOUR FEELINGS LIVE A MORE BALANCED LIFE,
MORE QUIET.
[JORGINHO] YOU CAN BELIEVE IT.
[TYPHOON] SUDDENLY IT WILL BE EVEN BETTER FOR YOU TO STAY A LITTLE FAR AWAY
OF US. LEARNING TO TAKE CARE OF A HOUSE. YOU ARE ALWAYS FIGHTING
WITH YOUR MOTHER, SUDDENLY IT WILL BE BETTER FOR EVERYONE,
MY SON.
[JORGINHO] CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING VERY SERIOUS, DAD?
[TYPHOON] MAY.
[JORGINHO] ARE YOU HAPPY?
[TYPHOON] MY SON, PEOPLE ARE NOT HAPPY ALL THE TIME.
[JORGINHO] SOMETIMES I THINK THAT, IF YOU HAD GOT ​​MARRIED
WITH MONALISA, WE WOULD BE MUCH HAPPIER.
[TYPHOON] DON'T SAY THAT, DON'T SAY THAT. DON'T TALK ABOUT CARMINHA,
BECAUSE IF IT WASN'T FOR HER, YOU WOULDN'T BE HERE,
YOU WERE NOT MY SON. WHAT'S UP WITH YOU TWO,
WHY DO YOU FIGHT SO MUCH? WHAT DID SHE DO TO YOU, MY SON.
[JORGINHO] DID NOTHING, DID NOTHING. I DON'T KNOW HOW TO EXPLAIN.
[TYPHOON] SO, DO YOUR FATHER A FAVOR...
[TYPHOON] ASK HER FOR FORGIVENESS. DO YOU UNDERSTAND? FORGIVE, FORGIVE,
FORGIVE... YOU WILL FEEL LIGHTER IF YOU DON'T DO THIS
FOR YOU. TRUST ME, YOU NEED TO DO IT FOR YOUR MOTHER,
DO IT FOR ME, I'M THE ONE ASKING YOU.
[JORGINHO] BEAUTY.
OK, I'LL DO IT.
[TYPHOON] I LOVE YOU, MAN.
[JORGINHO] I LOVE YOU TOO, DAD.
[STEPS]
[JINGLING OF KEYS]
[NINA] HECTOR?
[HECTOR] DON'T WORRY, NINA, EVERYTHING WILL BE OK. HUM?
[MAN] MISS NINA GARCIA.
"CONSIDERATION" TO MR HECTOR,
"FALL" RELEASED.
"BUT" THERE IS NO "ONE"
SECOND TIME.
[NINA] HECTOR, I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO THANK YOU.
[HECTOR] I KNOW A WAY. STAYING HERE, WITH ME.
[NINA] LET'S NOT START ALL OVER AGAIN. BYE.
[HECTOR] DON'T DO THIS TO ME, NINA... [SIGH]
DO YOU HAVE MONEY?
[NINA] I HAVE, OF COURSE I HAVE.
I'VE BEEN WORKING FOR A LONG TIME, I'VE SAVED UP.
[HECTOR] I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S MAKING YOU GO TO BRAZIL.
"YA SÉ... YA I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU DON'T WANT TO TELL ME, BUT...
YO IF YOU UNA" TIME "YOU WILL CHANGE YOUR IDEA".
ALREADY "NO VOY" WILL BE HERE WAITING FOR YOU.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MARTIN] I AM YOUR FATHER, YOUR LIFE IS HERE,
YOU ARE NINA, MY BELOVED DAUGHTER,
THE BEST CHEF I KNOW, HUH?
THAT HURT, SCARED, DESPERATE GIRL
THAT I TOOK OUT OF THAT PILE OF TRASH NO LONGER EXISTS!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] IF YOU APOLOGIZE, I CAN EVEN APOLOGIZE TO YOU
SAVE ME FROM WHAT I'M THINKING ABOUT DOING TO YOU.
APOLOGIZE. APOLOGIZE!
[SPIT]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] LEAVE IT, I'LL SEND YOU TO A REALLY COOL PLACE.
[BIRD SINGING]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[NINA] CARMEN LÚCIA MOREIRA DE SOUZA, YOUR PARTY IS GOING TO END.
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[LELECO] [DISTANT VOICE] I NEVER GAVE YOU A REASON TO BE SUSPICIOUS!
[MURICY] [DISTANT VOICE] OH, ENOUGH, ENOUGH! SHUT UP,
LELECO, SHUT UP. YOUR REPUTATION AS A STALLION, YOU KNOW, COMES
SINCE THE TIMES THE DEAD SEA WAS STILL SICK!
[LELECO] [LAUGHTER]
[MURICY] YOU WILL NOT ENTER THIS CONTEST, PERIOD.
[CARMINHA] [GASP] MY DIVINE HOLY SPIRIT,
BUT WHAT IS THIS, A HAUNTING IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT?
[ÁGATA] I'M SORRY, MOM, I DIDN'T MEAN TO SCARE YOU.
[CARMINHA] WHAT DO YOU HAVE IN YOUR HAND?
[AGATE] NOTHING, NO.
[CARMINHA] LIKE "NOTHING"? SHOW ME!
ICE CREAM, AGATE?
FIVE THOUSAND CALORIES... DO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT REPRESENTS?
YOU'RE GOING TO BECOME A LITTLE BUZZER LIKE YOUR AUNT.
BUT SHE HAS PERSONALITY AND CHARISMA, YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE THAT.
[AGATE] I'M GOING TO THROW IT AWAY.
[CARMINHA] THEN GIVE ME THIS. YOU'RE GOING TO LAY DOWN,
I ALREADY SAID I DON'T WANT YOU AWAKE AFTER 10PM,
THAT RUINS THE SKIN. YOU WANT TO BECOME A LITTLE MONSTER, DON'T YOU?
IT GOES TO SLEEP!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] OK, OLENKA, YOU CAN HIRE ME
TWO MORE HAIRDRESSERS, OK, DEAR?
OK. OK, LOVE, WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT TOMORROW, OK?
IN THE STRAIGHTENING GIRL CONTEST. OK, KISS THEN, BYE!
OH DADDY! I'M SORRY FOR SO MANY PHONE CALLS, DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
IT'S THAT THE BABY HERE
"NOT FOR TABAIÁ!
BUT NOW NOBODY WANTS TO PLAY"!
[MAX] "BINCA"? BUT "BINCA",
BABY? "HOLA IS THERE THIS BINCA"?
[IVANA] OXE, BUT IT'S ALMOST OVER
THREE WEEKS WE HAVEN'T DONE... TICKLE EACH OTHER!
[MAX] BUT THE BABY MUST BE VERY TIRED OF WORKING
IN THE COMPETITION. LET'S GO TO SLEEP, SHALL WE?
[IVANA] NO! OH! I WILL DO IT
CUCKOO! HUM! OH! "I WANT TO MAKE A FUNNY CUCKOO"!
OH, I MISS "BLINDING THE GANGOLA" SO MUCH!
[LAUGHTER] "DI ESCOLEGA, DI TLEPA-TLEPA"!
[MAX] [LAUGHTER] I FELT LIKE IT, DIDN'T I, BABY? BUT I THINK IT'S BETTER
BABY GO TO SLEEP EARLY TO WAKE UP IN A GOOD MOOD TOMORROW,
BECAUSE THERE IS NO NEED TO PRODUCE THIS COMPETITION,
AND I DON'T WANT TO HURT ANYONE IN ANY WAY. WHAT DOES DADDY
ARE YOU GOING TO DO IT? DADDY IS GOING TO PREPARE TWO DROPS FOR THE BABY TO SLEEP
A NICE SLEEP
"DROPLET", OK?
[IVANA] [STUTTERING] AND THEN... THEN, JUST GIVE A LITTLE DROP, GO ON,
DAD, SO WE CAN MAKE A LITTLE CABIN
BEFORE YOU FALL ASLEEP!
[MAX] BUT OF COURSE, MY BABY!
DADDY "PLEASE" TWO DROPS TO MAKE THE WATER LIKE THIS
VERY SWEET, "DROPY".
[IVANA] HUM! YAY, YAY!
[MAX] WELL DONE, BABY!
[IVANA] HUM! "DRIPY FINGER"!
[LAUGHTER] NOW COME, LITTLE CABIN! COME!
[MAX] DADDY IS GOING TO TAKE A QUICK BATH
WHEN YOU COME BACK, YOU'LL COME BACK SMELLING LIKE THE BABY, OK?
NOW, GO PLAY, GO.
[IVANA] OK, OK!
OH, COME BACK SO WE CAN SET UP THE TENT AND MAKE A LITTLE CABIN!
[MAX] "GO PLAYING, GO PLAYING, GO PLAYING",
MY BABY!
[IVANA] LITTLE CABIN! [LAUGHTER] OW!
[SNORING]
[CARMINHA] HUM! I THOUGHT YOU WON'T COME ANYMORE.
[MAX] I WAS IN SUCH A MESS YOU HAVE NO IDEA!
[CARMINHA] GIVE HER A LION, I'LL GIVE IT TO TUFOON.
[MAX] OOPS! AND YOU THINK I DON'T GIVE, NO? BUT NOT TODAY
I WAS "IPELATIVE", I WAS CRAZY, I HAD TO GIVE IT
A DOSE OF HORSE FOR HER OF TRANQUILIZER.
[CARMINHA] I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW! THE WORST WAS
WHAT I WENT THROUGH WITH JORGINHO, YOU SAW, RIGHT?
[MAX] DON'T EVEN SAY IT, DON'T SAY I FELT SORRY FOR YOU.
HE TREATED YOU LIKE A DOG, HE EVEN CALLED ME AN IDIOT,
THAT BOY.
[CARMINHA] WHERE ARE WE?
DID YOU WRONG WITH THAT KID, MAX? WHERE? THE KID HATES ME.
AND I WAS THE ONE WHO TOOK HIM OUT OF THAT GARBAGE, FROM THAT SEWER,
TO HAVE THE LIFE OF A KING IN THIS PALACE!
I GIVE REAL AFFECTION, WHAT ELSE DOES HE WANT?
AND IT'S THE TYPHOON'S FAULT, THAT DEAD FLY TOO,
AN IDIOT WHO HAS NO PULSE, DOESN'T KNOW HOW TO EDUCATE.
[MAX] STOP, STOP, STOP IT'S YOUR FAULT TOO
YOU RUN YOUR HAND ON HIS HEAD ALL THE TIME, OK?
[CARMINHA] DON'T YOU COME TOO, NO, MAX, PLEASE!
[MAX] OH CARMINHA! EVERYONE KNOWS YOU'RE IN LOVE
FOR THIS KID! THE MORE HE MALTREATS YOU,
BUT YOU SLUT HIS ASSHOLE!
[CARMINHA] YES, YOU'LL SEE
WHAT IS BAD BLOOD, RIGHT?
[MAX] Yeah, maybe! LEAVE IT
YOU KID WITH ME. I'LL FIX THIS KID IN THREE MOMENTS.
SPEAKING OF WHICH, WHERE IS IT? WHERE IS IT?
[CARMINHA] I DON'T KNOW, TUFÃO SAID HE WAS AT A FRIEND'S HOUSE.
IT MUST BE NOTHING, IT MUST BE NOTHING, IT'S LYING. IT'S ALWAYS COVERING UP
THE MAN, I'M SURE.
[MAX] SEE? SEE?
PAY ATTENTION, THAT'S IT, IT'S THE LACK OF LIMITS!
THERE IS NO LIMIT!
MISEDUCATE THE KID, UNDERSTAND?
IT'S THIS UNFORTUNATE LITTLE FAMILY FROM QUINTA, DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
THERE ARE ONLY IGNORANT PEOPLE. NOW TELL ME, WHY,
WHO NEEDS THESE BILLIONS IN THE BANK? TELL ME.
A COOLER PROGRAM FOR THIS GUY IS TO PUT ON A SANDAL,
GO WITH HIS DADDY TO EAT A CAT BARBECUE,
DRINK BEER, WITH THOSE GUYS LIKE SILAS AND DIÓGENES.
THE CAR HE BOUGHT IN THE GARAGE, ZERO MILE,
CRACKLING INSIDE THE GARAGE, BUT THE GUY LIKES TO GO OUT
WITH THAT CRAP OLD TRUCK!
THAT'S WHAT HE LIKES, HE LIKES LIVING IN THE S... IN THE SUBURB,
HE WANTS THE SUBURB, THE SUBURB IS THE BEST FOR HIM
WORLDLY THING, BECAUSE IF THIS MONEY IS WITH ME, LOVE!
[LAUGHTER] DO YOU KNOW WHERE I WOULD BE? I WOULD BE IN CALIFORNIA,
IN MIAMI, IN IBIZA, HAVING A LOT OF FUN!
[CARMINHA] YES, BUT YOU DON'T HAVE THE MONEY, MAN, IT'S NOT!
AND YOU'RE NOT THE TYPHOON! YOU'RE BETTER THAN HIM. [LAUGHTER]
[MAX] RIGHT, AND... AND WHAT ADVANTAGE DO YOU THINK IS
WHAT AM I GETTING OUT OF THIS? TELL ME! THE JABURANGA
DON'T GIVE ME ANOTHER PENNY, I'M BROKE, I HAVE NO MONEY
NONE! CARMINHA, PAY ATTENTION, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD.
LET'S ACT, LET'S STRIKE THIS ROULETTE.
[CARMINHA] MAX, HERE YOU COME COMPLAINING AGAIN!
BEFORE COMPLAINING, TAKE A LOOK AT THE PALACE
THAT WE ARE LIVING AND REMEMBER WHERE WE CAME FROM!
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A STRIKE AT ROULETTE, YES, BUT CALM DOWN!
CALM DOWN, JUST HAVE A LITTLE PATIENCE. A LITTLE.
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
[CARMINHA] VERY LITTLE...
[MAX] STOP IT, STOP...
STOP. WE AGREED THAT WE WON'T DO ANYTHING
HERE AT HOME. WE... THIS WEEK, WE'RE GOING THERE...
STOP IT. WE'RE GOING TO...
[CARMINHA] YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE RIGHT.
NOW, KEEP WORKING OUT, OK? KEEP WORKING OUT AND I'LL HOLD YOU HARMLESS
WITH INTEREST THIS WEEK.
[NINA] IT WILL BE GOOD FOR YOU TO SPEND SOME TIME HERE,
TREAT YOURSELF, DETOXIFY.
[BEGONIA] I KNOW, NINA.
YOU DON'T NEED TO CONVINCE ME.
[STEPS]
[MERCEDES] LOOK THERE'S THE DIRECTOR.
I'LL TALK TO HIM SO YOU CAN BE TREATED WELL, OK?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[BEGONIA] I DON'T... I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY TO YOU.
IF IT WASN'T FOR YOU, I WOULD BE IN JAIL,
I WOULD SPEND A LONG TIME IN JAIL.
NINA... MY WHOLE LIFE HAS BEEN LIKE THIS.
YOU ALWAYS SAVING ME.
MY GUARDIAN ANGEL.
[NINA] [LAUGHTER] I WAS LUCKY THAT HECTOR TOOK ME OUT
FROM THE CHAIN.
[SNIFLE] SEE.
LIFE IS GIVING YOU THIS CHANCE, IT DOESN'T THROW IT AWAY.
[BEGONIA] THEN, STAY CLOSE TO ME.
I NEED YOU, NINA.
LET ME GO TO BRAZIL WITH YOU, I'LL HELP YOU WITH WHATEVER YOU WANT.
[NINA] BEGONIA, YOU NEED TO STAY, YOU NEED TO GET TREATMENT.
[BEGONIA] YOU TOO, NINA. YOU'RE JUST LIKE ME.
WHAT ARE YOU WASTING YOUR WHOLE LIFE FOR?
BECAUSE OF REVENGE?
IS THIS YOUR DRUG?
AND ME, NINA? AND MERCEDES? WE LOVE YOU.
AND HECTOR? HE LOVES YOU, YOU LOVE HIM TOO.
[NINA] IT WASN'T LOVE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[BEGONIA] YOU DON'T LOVE ANYONE THEN.
THE ONLY THING THAT MATTERS TO YOU IS THIS HATE YOU HAVE INSIDE.
DAD WAS RIGHT, NINA.
YOU ARE A WOUNDED BIRD, THERE IS NO WAY OUT.
[NINA] OH, BEGONIA, GIVE ME A BREAK, COME ON.
[BEGONIA] NINA, GO AWAY, GO. LEAVE ME HERE ALONE.
HEY NURSE, GIVE ME A CALMING DRUG, COME ON.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] [LAUGHTER] OH HOW DELICIOUS!
[EXTENDED] HUM...
WE'VE BEEN HERE ALL MORNING, YOU KNOW?
IT SEEMS LIKE THERE'S SOMETHING LIKE A TASTE OF FORBIDDEN THINGS.
[SILAS] OH MY LOVE, LOOK. IF I CAME TO LIVE HERE
WITH YOU, WE WOULD BE ABLE TO DO SOMETHING ALL THE TIME...
[MONALISA] NO, WAIT. IT'S NO LONGER FUNNY.
IT NOW LOSES ITS FUN, BECAUSE IT BECAME A COMMONPLACE.
IT'S NOT FUNNY, COME ON, ENOUGH, IT'S OVER.
[SILAS] FOR THE LOVE OF GOD...
[MONALISA] NO, YOU LOST, YOU CUT IT.
CUT THE CLIMATE.
[SILAS] CUT HOW?
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, WE'RE JUST FINISHED,
ARE YOU ALREADY SENDING ME AWAY?
[MONALISA] Yes.
[SILAS] MY GOD IN HEAVEN.
WHY CAN'T I COME LIVE HERE WITH YOU? HUH?
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE ONLY INTERESTED IN MY BODY.
LOOK HERE, I'M NOT A MAN
"ABJECT", NO.
[MONALISA] WHAT AN "ABJECT" MAN, SILAS?
WHAT A MAN... OBJECT MAN.
[SILAS] THAT'S RIGHT, SEE HOW YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW. THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK I AM, OK?
[MONALISA] I THINK NOTHING, I DON'T THINK ANYTHING.
I JUST DON'T WANT A MAN CONTROLLING MY REMOTE CONTROL
FROM MY TV, THAT'S ALL. I'M THE ONE WHO CHOOSES THE CHANNELS HERE.
COME ON, PUT ON THAT SHIRT, GO.
[SILAS] WAKE UP, MONALISA.
IT'S EIGHT YEARS OF RELATIONSHIP, EIGHT YEARS.
I'M TIRED OF THIS, I WANT TO MARRY YOU.
[MONALISA] BUT, MY LOVE, IN A WINNING TEAM
DON'T MOVE, UNDERSTAND? DON'T MOVE. COME ON, WEAR THIS ONE...
[SILAS] WHICH TEAM IS WINNING?
[LAUGHTER] AND MY TEAM IS WINNING?
[MONALISA] WHAT, YOU'RE NOT WINNING?
[SILAS] MY TEAM IS WINNING
WHERE, MONALISA?
[MONALISA] WHAT'S YOUR TEAM LIKE?
SO, SILAS?
[SILAS] MY TEAM IS IN THE LAST PLACE
A LONG TIME AGO, A LONG TIME AGO.
[MONALISA] WHAT IS THIS?
[SILAS] LOOK HERE, I'M THE ONE WHO HAS TO COOK
AT HOME, I HAVE TO WASH MY UNDERWEAR,
I'M THE ONE WHO HAS TO...
[MONALISA] OH! WAIT THEN,
CALM DOWN. CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN. NOW I UNDERSTAND.
IF YOU WANT BED, TABLE AND BATH, MY LOVE,
HIRE A CLEANER. ARE YOU CRAZY?
OR, MY LOVE, YOU CAN ALSO MARRY A LITTLE WOMAN
ANYWAY, GO BACK TO MOMMY'S HOUSE, BIG BABY.
OH! PUT ON THOSE SHOES.
[SILAS] MONALISA,
SOMETIMES I THINK YOU STILL LIKE TYPHOON
AND NOT FROM ME, YOU KNOW?
[MONALISA] ME, HUH!
I BELIEVE, GOD FORBID ME!
LOOK, I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING:
THE TYPHOON IS A PAST.
A DEAD AND BURIED PAST. AND LOOK WHAT ELSE,
ENOUGH ABOUT THIS. COME ON, LETS GO.
[SILAS] NO. NO, THAT'S NOT ENOUGH. THE CONVERSATION IS NOT OVER, NO.
THE CONVERSATION IS NOT OVER, WOMAN. LET'S TALK...
IT'S NOT OVER, NO. LET'S TALK OVER COFFEE...
[MONALISA] NOTHING OF THAT. GO, GO, GO, GO.
[SILAS] NONE OF THAT WHAT? WE'RE GOING TO HAVE BREAKFAST
AND WE'RE GOING TO TALK ABOUT IT.
[IRAN] OH, NO. WAIT, MOM.
ARE YOU GOING TO WAIT FOR ME AT THE DOOR? CALM DOWN.
[SILAS] NO, IT'S NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU, NO, IRAN.
THIS HOLLY GIRL IS SENDING ME AWAY AGAIN,
THAT'S IT. OK, I'M GOING TO GO SO... BYE... BYE.
[MONALISA] BYE... BYE. GONE. KISS.
[DOOR CLOSE]
[STEPS]
[IRAN] MORNING, DEAL WITH SILAS.
[MONALISA] OH, MY SON. MEN TREAT THEMSELVES LIKE THIS, HUH!
[IRAN] IT'S BAD, HUH? IF A WOMAN TREATS ME LIKE THIS,
I'M NEVER COMING BACK.
[MONALISA] MY SON, WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU, MY SON?
YOU'RE DOWN.
[IRAN] I AM.
[MONALISA] MY SON, YOU'RE SO SKINNY, POOR THING.
THESE WOMEN ARE SUCKING YOUR BLOOD, RIGHT? OH MY FATHER.
DO YOU WANT TO EAT SOMETHING? DO YOU WANT A SANDWICH? I'LL MAKE IT.
[IRAN] BUT THE TRUTH IS I'M HANGOVER
UNTIL NOW, CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
[MONALISA] SO, HOW WAS THE CAFONAS PARTY THERE?
[IRAN] MOTHER, YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
WHAT A MISTAKE, MOM. JORGINHO GOT CRAZY, TOOK ALL THEM,
HE MADE A BIG MISTAKE, HE EVEN FIGHTED WITH HIS MOTHER.
[MONALISA] [LAUGHTER] BUT, MY SON, I UNDERSTAND,
WITH THAT JARARACA MOTHER HE HAS.
[LELECO] OH, HERE, IF YOU LEAVE THIS... THESE WOMEN WILL SIT DOWN
ON TOP OF US, HUH. WHERE HAVE YOU EVER SEEN A FEMALE JURY?
TO ELECT A STRAIGHT GIRL? LISTEN, TELL YOUR MOTHER,
THAT THE JURY WILL BE COMPOSED OF MEN, REAL MEN,
ME, DIOGENES, SILAS AND ADAUTO.
[TYPHOON] OH FATHER, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO PUT ME IN THE MIDDLE OF ANOTHER FIGHT,
NO, DO YOU UNDERSTAND? I'M PUTTING YOU AS THE PRESIDENT OF THE JURY.
AND ALSO, IF THE MONALISA ALLOWS YOU. NOW, YOU HAVE TO BEHAVE YOURSELVES,
YOU HAVE TO HAVE ETHICS, YOU HAVE TO JUDGE ABOVE ALL
PERSONAL INTEREST.
[DIOGENES] CALM DOWN, WE'RE GOING TO BE TOTALLY IMPARTIAL.
[SILAS] AND TRANSPARENT, RIGHT. HERE. OH ADAUTO,
YOU WON'T SAY ANYTHING, RIGHT?
[ADAUTO] I AM AGAINST IT, I THINK THAT THE PERSON SHOULD DO THIS
THE JUDGMENT HERE IS MURICY AND IVANA, THAT YOU...
YOU'RE GOING TO... TO...
[TOGETHER] DISTORT!
[ADAUTO] YES, YOU'RE GOING TO MESS UP THE BUSINESS,
AND A STRAIGHTENER GIRL IS NOT... IT'S A BEAUTY CONTEST,
IT'S NOT A WOMAN'S "SERVE-SERVE", NO.
[DIOGENES] "IXI"!
[LELECO] ADAUTO, ARE YOU A FAGGOT?
[ADAUTO] WHAT'S THIS, LELECO?
[DIOGENES] OH, POOR BOY.
[SILAS] HEY, HEY, STOP, STOP, STOP! HEY GUYS, LET'S KEEP IT GOING
THE LEVEL. LET'S KEEP THE LEVEL OF THIS HERE, BOY. LOOK HERE,
OH, PROVOLONE, A SKEWER HERE, ON THE HOUSE.
[TYPHOON] HEY, HEY, VALENTINE! BRING ME ONE OF THOSE CHICKEN WINGS
OR IS IT TOO MUCH TO ASK OF YOU?
[SILAS] OH, VALENTIM, CAN'T YOU HEAR THE TYPHOON, BOY?
[VALENTIM] OF COURSE I HEARD IT, RIGHT, SILAS. CHAMPION HERE
DON'T ASK, THE CHAMPION IS IN CHARGE. THAT'S WHY I'M GOING.
[DIOGENES] HEY!
[SILAS] ADAUTO, COME HERE, ADAUTO. DON'T GET INTO THIS
NO PIRA, ADULTO.
[CARMINHA] AND YOUR HUSBAND, IVANA?
[IVANA] HE WENT TO THE COMPANY EARLY... OW! I HAVE TO GO,
I'M LATE. HE'S TAKING CARE OF THE MARKETING CAMPAIGN
FROM OUR STRAIGHTENER GIRL CONTEST.
[MURICY] OH! WAIT, WAIT, IVANA! OH, IVANA,
I HAVE SOMETHING SO IMPORTANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
[IVANA] OK, KEEP TALKING.
[MURICY] IVANA,
FOR GOD'S SAKE!
[IVANA] SPEAK, SPEAK.
[MURICY] IVANA, LISTEN, MY DAUGHTER. YOU ARE A PERSON WHO
YOU HAVE AN ACTIVE VOICE WITHIN THAT FIRM OF OUR, RIGHT, DEAR?
[IVANA] OF COURSE.
[MURICY] AND THE FIRM IS A FIRM
FAMILY. IS IT OR ISN'T IT, CARMINHA?
[CARMINHA] MORE OR LESS.
[MURICY] AH, MORE OR LESS, SHE'S JEALOUS...
[CARMINHA] MY COFFEE, ZEZÉ!
[MURICY] IT SO HAPPENS THAT I HEARD THAT LELECO WANTS
BE THE PRESIDENT OF THE JURY OF THE CHAPINHA GIRL! AND WANT TO TAKE IT
THOSE FRIENDS ALL THERE BAR ALL TO BE JURY TOGETHER
WITH HIM. PEOPLE, DON'T YOU THINK IT'S ANYTHING WORTH IT? FOR THE LOVE OF GOD,
PEOPLE, THIS DOESN'T LOOK WELL! THIS DOESN'T LOOK WELL FOR OUR FAMILY,
FOR OUR FIRM, THAT BUNCH OF GUYS JUDGING THAT MOUNTAIN
OF A HOT WOMAN! WHAT IS THIS? I THINK THAT IT IS JUST, DIGNIFIED,
I WOULD LIKE TO BE THE JURY PRESIDENT, RIGHT?
[IVANA] THAT'S RIGHT, MOM. I'M GOING TO LAUNCH YOUR CANDIDACY,
BUT MONALISA WILL HAVE TO APPROVE, RIGHT?
[MURICY] WHY DOES MONALISA HAVE TO APPROVE?
[IVANA] WELL, BECAUSE SHE OWNS HALF THE COMPANY, MOM.
BY THE WAY, YOU DON'T WANT TO BE PART OF THIS JURY EITHER,
NO, CARMINHA?
[CARMINHA] NO, THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
I WILL PASS. IF I CAN AVOID ANY CONTACT FROM ME
AND MY FAMILY WITH THAT AMORAL LITTLE WOMAN,
SO MUCH BETTER.
[IVANA] OH, HONESTLY,
CARMINHA, I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU'RE SO MUCH ANNOYED ABOUT MONALISA.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM? WHAT DID SHE DO WRONG?
[CARMINHA] WHAT DID SHE DO WRONG? THAT WOMAN
IS A CANCER IN OUR COMMUNITY. A WOMAN WHO CARRIES
A WASTED LIFE, SINGLE MOTHER, CONCUBINA.
SHE HAS BEEN LIVING WITH THAT MAN FOR YEARS.
[IVANA] SHE'S DATING SILAS! SHE DOESN'T WANT TO MARRY HIM,
SHE'S HAPPY LIKE THIS. WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
[CARMINHA] IVANA, PLEASE, HUH. IT'S VERY MODERN.
I REALLY ADMIRE YOU, A FAMILY WOMAN SPEAKING LIKE THIS!
[MURICY] DO YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS, THIS IS ALREADY INFLUENCE
FROM THAT MESSALINA, DID YOU KNOW?
[IVANA] LOOK HERE, I'M GOING TO WORK, I HAVE
MORE TO DO. YOU CAN SPEND THE WHOLE DAY THERE TALKING
OF OTHER PEOPLE'S LIVES, OK?
[MURICY] WAIT AREA. OH IVANA,
IVANA. IVANA! IVANA!
[IVANA] YOU WILL BE THE PRESIDENT OF THE JURY.
[M URICY] BUT IT'S ONE THING... LOOK, DID YOU SEE HOW IT IS?
THIS GIRL? SHE'S WANTING TO CONFRONT ME, THIS GIRL.
[CARMINHA] SHE REPEATS WHAT SHE HEARS FROM THE OTHER'S MOUTH.
IVANA'S PLACE IS HERE, LIKE ANY FAMILY WOMAN!
BUT IF MONALISA DIDN'T CREATE PROBLEMS FOR MY TYPHOON, RIGHT,
IVANA DIDN'T NEED TO LEAVE HOME EVERY DAY TO GO TO WORK.
[MURICY] YOU'RE COMPLETELY RIGHT, MY DAUGHTER-IN-LAW,
YOU'RE TOTALLY RIGHT, SEE. MOST OF THE PROBLEMS IN THIS
HOUSE, IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF THIS AMORAL WOMAN!
[MAX] HOW DO I SEE THIS? REASONING, THINKING,
HOW HAVE WE BEEN RUNNING THE GIRL WITH STRAIGHT HAIR CONTEST FOR TEN YEARS?
WHAT HAS TO HAPPEN? YOU ASK, I ANSWER.
WE HAVE TO INNOVATE, TRANSFORM, WHAT?
REPAGINATE, PERFECT. HOW IS THIS GOING TO HAPPEN?
TAKING A STRIKE AT ROULETTE.
[LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] COME HERE, DO YOU REMEMBER THE FIRST STRAIGHT GIRL?
[MONALISA] OF COURSE, I WAS THE FIRST STRAIGHT-HAIRED GIRL.
EVERYTHING OK, TYPHOON?
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[TYPHOON] THE LAST TIME WE SAW EACH OTHER WAS IN...
AT THE BEGINNING OF THE YEAR, RIGHT? WHEN WE RUNNED OVER
THERE AT SILAS' BAR.
[MONALISA] WAS IT? I DON'T REMEMBER, REFRESH MY MEMORY.
[TYPHOON] YOUR FOOT WAS BROKEN.
[MONALISA] OH, OKAY, IT'S TRUE. I TWISTED MY ANKLE ONE DAY
AFTER MY BIRTHDAY.
[LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] [LAUGHTER] REMEMBER, RIGHT?
[MONALISA] COME HERE, LET'S GET TO THE POINT, WHICH IS THE COMPETITION
FROM A STRAIGHTENER GIRL.
[TYPHOON] YOU'RE... YOU'RE FINE, MONALISA, YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
[MONALISA] THANK YOU. WELL, SO, ANY IDEAS GUYS?
ANY IDEAS FOR THE CONTEST?
[IVANA] WELL, MAX WOULD LIKE TO SAY A FEW WORDS.
[MAX] PLEASE, EXCUSE ME. WELL, WHAT'S MY
IDEA, OK? MY IDEA IS THIS: ASSOCIATE THE IMAGE
FROM THE TYPHOON TO THE STRAIGHTENER GIRL. WHY? BECAUSE EVERYONE
YOU ALREADY KNOW THAT TYPHOON IS A PARTNER IN THE BUSINESS.
[TYPHOON] [SIGH]
[MAX] SO WHAT DO I DO? ME, AS AN IMAGE CONSULTANT
MY BELOVED, MY GREAT STAR, HOW DO I DEFEND HIM?
ASSOCIATING. I THINK TYPHOON WILL ADD TO THE BRAND AND THE BRAND
WILL ADD TO IT. UNDERSTAND? AND I TELL YOU, AND SO,
I HAVE PROOF. FOR EXAMPLE, I HAVE THIS HERE,
I HAVE SEVERAL THINGS...
[DARKSON] YOU, KITTY, YOU, KITTY! YOU, MISS, YOU,
MY LADY! LITTLE PRINCESSES AND BIG BOOTS! YOU, WHO HAVE THE SKIN
THE COLOR OF JABUTICABA, OR YOU, WITH HAIR AS GOLD AS HONEY!
YOU WILL BE EVEN MORE AWESOME AFTER COMING HERE
IN "ELEGANCE. DIOGENES, WOMEN'S FASHIONS". WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
FIND EVERYTHING! THAT BLOUSE, THOSE SHORTS
TIGHT, THAT TOP, THAT LITTLE BUSTY, WHAT WILL DO
MEN MOAN WHEN YOU PASS BY, MY PRINCESS.
[ÁGATA] LOOK AT DARKSON, HE'S NOT THE MOST CUTE GUY
OF THE WORLD?
[JANAÍNA] I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A BIB AS A GIFT.
COME, AGATA, COME. WE'RE LATE, I HAVE SO MUCH TO DO
TO DO. NO, NO, NO, NO, NO. NO TALKING, NO TALKING.
♪I WANT TO SEE♪
♪YOU RUNNING AFTER ME♪
♪WHEN I LOOKED FOR YOU♪
♪YOU DIDN'T EVEN CALL ME♪
[DARKSON] YOU, POWERFUL! YOU WHO ARE ABLE TO MAKE A WAVE WITH
EVERYONE, JUST BECAUSE THEY LOOK LIKE A TELEVISION ARTIST,
COULD YOU GIVE ME A BREAK, PLEASE?
[SUELEN] WAIT SITTING DOWN, YOU DROOLING DUMBASS.
[DARKSON] THE LINE MOVES, HUH, DAUGHTER? JUST BE CAREFUL.
[DIOGENES] MRS SUELEN!
[SUELEN] HI!
[DIOGENES] IS THIS TIME TO REPORT TO WORK?
[SUELEN] HERE IS THE MEDICAL CERTIFICATE, ROTAVIRUS, UNTIL YESTERDAY.
[DIOGENES] I KNOW, I KNOW. TONSILLITIS ONE WEEK, DENGUE THE NEXT,
ROTAVIRUS IN THE OTHER ONE. LOOK, I AM AMAZED THAT YOU ARE
SO, SO, SO HEALTHY, AREN'T YOU? YOU'RE ALMOST
WHAT A MIRACLE OF MEDICINE.
[SUELEN] DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS, MR. DIOGENES?
I AM EXPOSED TO MILLIONS OF MICROBES WORKING
IN YOUR STORE, YOU UNDERSTAND? THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE, A LOT OF PEOPLE COMING AND GOING. YOU KNOW?
THESE PEOPLE WITHOUT VACCINES. IT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
[DIOGENES] I UNDERSTAND, I UNDERSTAND. NOW YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
ONE THING: GO INSIDE, PUT ON YOUR UNIFORM AND COME AND ASSIST
TO CUSTOMERS! BECAUSE OTHERWISE, THIS MICROBE HERE WILL END
WITH YOU!
♪I WANT TO SEE♪
[WOMAN] HI, GIRL?
♪NOW I WANT TO SEE♪
[WOMAN] GIRL?
[SUELEN] ARE YOU NERVOUS? CAN'T YOU WAIT A SECOND, NO?
[WOMAN] OK, THAT'S OK.
[SUELEN] SPEAK, NOW I'VE LOST CONCENTRATION.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
[WOMAN] DO YOU KNOW THOSE LEGGINGS THAT ARE IN THE WINDOW?
[SUELEN] THERE ARE 20 LEGGINGS IN THE SHOWCASE.
[WOMAN] IT'S A LITTLE PRINT, LIKE THIS, WITH A LOW WAIST.
[SUELEN] FOR YOU? [LAUGHTER]
ARE YOU KIDDING, RIGHT?
YOU'LL LOOK LIKE A CIRCUS ELEPHANT IN THOSE LEGGINGS.
[WOMAN] YOU RUDE!
[SUELEN] BEAUTIFUL.
[JESSICA] OH SUELEN, YOU'RE ALREADY ON THE BALL SEVEN,
IF DIÓGENES CAUGHT YOU TREATING A CLIENT LIKE THIS, YOU'D BE OUT ON THE STREET.
[SUELEN] I DON'T CARE, JESSICA. MY HEAD IS ANOTHER ONE,
MY DAUGHTER. WHAT IF LIFE CHANGES TOMORROW, HUM?
WANT TO BET HOW MUCH I'LL WIN THAT GIRL CONTEST
FLAT IRON? THIS IS MY BODY AND THE TRACK IS OURS, MY LOVE.
[MONALISA] WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, MAX, LET ME UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S IT LIKE? IT'S A GIRL, WITH HER BREAST OUT,
DOING JIGSAWY WITH A SOCCER BALL, IS THAT IT?
[MAX] [EXTENDED] PERFECT!
IT'S SIMPLY GENIUS,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT? HUH? WHO'S GOING TO FORGET THIS?
THIS YEAR? NOBODY, PEOPLE!
[MONALISA] WANT TO KNOW WHAT I THINK? FANTASTIC, I LOVED IT!
[LAUGHTER] I LOVED IT!
[TYPHOON] OH MAX! MAX, THE PEOPLE AT HOME ARE GOING TO SCREAM, HUH?
[MONALISA] AH, THEIR PROBLEM, RIGHT? I THINK THAT, NOW, WE
YOU HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT WHO WILL BE THE PRESIDENT OF THE JURY.
[IVANA] SO, MOM ASKED TO BE.
[TYPHOON] DAD WANTED IT TOO.
[MONALISA] NO, THEN, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT. I DON'T WANT TO
I'M GETTING INVOLVED, BUT WHEN I'M ALREADY GETTING INVOLVED, YOU TELL DONA MURICY,
IVANA, I DEMANDED THAT THE PRESIDENT OF THE JURY BE
YOUR LELECO, OKAY? WELL, GUYS, SO THAT'S IT, RIGHT?
THE MEETING IS OVER.
[IVANA] Yes.
[MAX] PERFECT, GREAT.
[IVANA] WELL, I'M GOING TO MY CLASSROOM AND LATER
COME OVER THERE SO WE CAN TALK ABOUT THOSE OTHER SUBJECTS.
[MONALISA] I'M GOING DOWN, I'M GOING TO THE SALON REALLY QUICKLY,
I'LL SEE YOU SOON, OK?
[IVANA] BYE ​​BABY, SEE YOU LATER AT HOME!
[STEPS]
[TYPHOON] MONALISA! MONALISA.
[TYPHOON] I MISSED... YOU NOT GOING THERE, IN MY...
MY WEDDING PARTY, UNDERSTAND?
[MONALISA] OH YES. [MOANS] I KNOW I LOST THE BIG ONE
HISTORY OF THE NEIGHBORHOOD SHACK.
[LAUGHTER] SORRY.
[TYPHOON] WHY BE AGGRESSIVE LIKE THIS? HUH?
[MONALISA] DO YOU KNOW THE DAY I'M GOING TO YOUR WIFE'S HOUSE?
FROM THAT BLACK WIDOW? NEVER!
IT'S ENOUGH WHAT THIS SNEAKY ONE SAYS ABOUT ME OUT THERE...
[TYPHOON] SHE IS NOT SILLY.
MAN, STOP BEING HARD, WE ARE PARTNERS
IN A STOP THAT WORKED OUT, YOU UNDERSTAND?
I OWE YOU SO MUCH, MONALISA.
[MONALISA] SO IF YOU ARE SO GRATEFUL TO ME,
SELL ME YOUR SHARE. I WANT TO LIVE FREE OF YOU!
[TYPHOON] I WILL NOT SELL MY SHARE,
I WILL NOT SELL, I ALREADY SAID I WILL NOT SELL.
[TYPHOON] I AM A PERSON WHO FEELS LONGING
FROM OUR CONVERSATIONS, UNDERSTAND?
WE HAD SUCH A GOOD CHAT, MAN.
[MONALISA] YES, BUT DO IT.
BECAUSE THESE CONVERSATIONS ARE OVER.
OUR RELATIONSHIP, NOW, IS AND WILL ALWAYS BE, YOUR TYPHOON,
STRICTLY COMMERCIAL.
OUR CPFs, THEY ARE FRIENDS, WE ARE NOT.
FORGET ME, ERASE MY NAME FROM YOUR NOTEBOOK,
BECAUSE I ALREADY SCRATCHED YOURS 12 YEARS AGO.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MAX] AND SO, SHEILINHA, I WAS THINKING, HAVE YOU ALREADY... ALREADY WALKED?
BY BOAT EVER, DEAR?
[SHEILA] NO, NEVER.
[MAX] OH, I HAVE A FRIEND OF MINE,
HE HAS A BEAUTIFUL DOUBLE DECK BOAT.
YOU WILL BE SURPRISED, I...
[TYPHOON] WHAT'S UP, MAX.
[TYPHOON] COME ON?
[MAX] AND THEN YOU CAN LEAVE EVERYTHING TIDY
AND WE'LL TALK LATER. THANK YOU, SHEILA!
[TYPHOON] MAX, IT'S MY IMPRESSION
OR ARE YOU HITTING SHEILA?
[MAX] WHAT'S UP? NO, FOR... WHAT'S THIS?
I WAS TALKING ABOUT BOATS, YOU KNOW I LOVE THEM...
[TYPHOON] PAY ATTENTION, UNDERSTAND?
YOU'RE MARRIED TO MY SISTER, YOU LIVE UNDER MY ROOF.
IF I FOUND OUT THAT YOU'RE CHEATING ON MY SISTER
WITH ANYONE, I'LL KILL YOU, HUH?
[MAX] LOOK HERE, TYPHOON, YOU'RE CRAZY. WHEN YOU TALK
WITH THIS MONALISA, YOU'RE SPITTING OUT WASPS.
YOU'RE GOING CRAZY ANYWAY. WHAT'S THIS?
♪I SAW♪
♪WHEN YOU SAW ME♪
♪YOUR EYES♪
♪THEY LANDED ON MINE♪
♪IN A SUBTLE SHIVER♪
♪I SAW IT... THAT'S IT♪
♪I NOTICED♪
♪YOU TOOK ME OUT TO DANCE♪
♪WITHOUT EVER LEAVING THE PLACE♪
♪WITHOUT PUTTING♪
♪FEET ON THE GROUND♪
♪NO MUSIC TO ACCOMPANY♪
[DÉBORA] OH, MARGARIDO APPEARED.
[JORGINHO] I CALLED YOU ALL DAY, DIDN'T YOU SEE?
[DÉBORA] [LAUGHTER] THAT'S A LOT OF CONSIDERATION ON YOUR PART, RIGHT?
AS IF I HADN'T BEEN UP ALL NIGHT,
AFTER YOU ABANDONED ME AT YOUR PARENTS' PARTY.
[JORGINHO] I WAS PISSED, YOU KNOW.
FORGIVE ME, LET'S TALK...
[DÉBORA] "LET'S TALK"? TALK FOR WHAT?
YOU DON'T TRUST ME, YOU'RE FULL OF SECRETS.
[JORGINHO] OF COURSE I TRUST YOU.
I LOVE YOU, I NEED YOU...
[DÉBORA] OH YES, DO YOU NEED IT? DO YOU NEED IT? BECAUSE I THINK NOT.
HE SPENT THE WHOLE NIGHT OUT, NOBODY KNOWS, NOBODY SAW.
FOR EXAMPLE, WHO WERE YOU WITH? WHERE WERE YOU? I DON'T EVEN KNOW...
[JORGINHO] DO YOU THINK I WAS OUT NIGHT, THEN? JUST FOR A JOKE?
[DÉBORA] I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
[JORGINHO] SOMETIMES I DON'T KNOW EITHER.
THINGS ARE DIFFICULT...
[DÉBORA] THERE, YOU SEE, YOU SEE? "THE THING"...
[JORGINHO] WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
[DÉBORA] I DON'T KNOW WHAT THIS IS. YOU WANT TO KNOW, JORGINHO?
STAY THERE ALONE WITH YOUR LITTLE SECRETS.
♪YOUR EYES SEARCHED MINE♪
♪THE SAME FEBRILE SIN♪
♪I SAW... YES, I NOTICED♪
♪YOU TOOK ALL THE AIR OUT OF ME♪
♪SO I COULD BREATHE♪
♪I KNOW NOBODY NOTICED♪
♪IT WAS JUST YOU AND ME♪
[DÉBORA] HUM, OKAY. I KNOW
THAT I CANNOT RESIST YOU, BUT NOW OR WE
TALK OR I'M LEAVING.
[JORGINHO] OK, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO KNOW?
[SHEET RUSTLESS]
[JORGINHO] [EXTENDED] HUM!
[DÉBORA] [LAUGHTER] STOP.
[JORGINHO] [SIGH]
[DÉBORA] WHERE DID YOU GO AFTER THE PARTY?
[JORGINHO] I WENT TO THE DUMP.
[DÉBORA] WHAT DO YOU MEAN, WHAT IS THIS TALK?
WHAT WERE YOU DOING IN THE DUMP?
[JORGINHO] I'M FROM THERE, I CAME FROM THE GARBAGE.
[DÉBORA] WHAT DO YOU MEAN, JORGINHO?
[JORGINHO] WHEN MY FATHER AND CARMINHA ADOPTED ME
I COLLECTED TRASH IN THE LANDFILL, IN THE DUMP.
[DÉBORA] AND WHY DID YOU NEVER TELL ME THIS?
[JORGINHO] AH. [LAUGHTER] SHAMEFUL, RIGHT? MY SPONSOR
FROM THE SOUTH ZONE, LITTLE PRINCESS, DATING A GARBAGE BOY?
ALSO BECAUSE DOWN ON THE GROUND I HAVE ANOTHER FAMILY, SO,
AS IF IT WERE A SECRET IDENTITY.
EVERYONE THERE KNOWS ME AS POTATO.
[LAUGHTER]
[DÉBORA] NICE TO MEET YOU, BATATA.
[JORGINHO] NOW YOU CAN SAY YOU KNOW ME, HUH?
[DÉBORA] [LAUGHTER] NOW?
[KISS SNAP]
[JORGINHO] LET ME SHOW YOU SOMETHING HERE. OH. [SIGH]
[WALLET HANDLING]
[DÉBORA] WHAT PHOTO IS THIS?
[JORGINHO] THIS IS MY WEDDING PHOTO.
NO, I WAS ALREADY MARRIED BEFORE I MET YOU.
[DEBORAH] AH.
[JORGINHO] I MARRIED RITA WHEN I WAS 12 YEARS OLD.
[DÉBORA] AND WHERE IS SHE?
[JORGINHO] DISAPPEARED, I NEVER HEARD OF HER AGAIN.
[DÉBORA] AND ARE YOU STILL IN LOVE WITH MISS RITA?
[JORGINHO] OH, YOU'RE JEALOUS!
[DÉBORA] LOOK AT YOU.
[JORGINHO] STOP IT, YOU'RE JEALOUS!
[DÉBORA] STOP, WHAT?
[JORGINHO] NO, RITA WAS ADOPTED, SHE WENT TO LIVE OUTSIDE THE COUNTRY.
I WILL NEVER SEE IT AGAIN. DID YOU LIKE IT?
[DÉBORA] I THINK IT'S GOOD.
[JORGINHO] ARE YOU MORE CALM?
[KISS SNAP]
[NINA] [SIGH] THIS BRAZILIAN AIR.
[NINA] THANK YOU.
[NINA] LET'S GO TO COPACABANA, PLEASE.
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪