[SILENCE]
[POTATO] COME ON, COME WITH ME.
[RITA] I'M NOT GOING.
[POTATO] YOU MUST BE STARVING.
[RITA] GO AWAY.
[POTATO] IF YOU STAY THERE, YOU'LL GET SICK.
[RITA] AND WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO DO WITH THIS?
YOU ARE NOTHING MINE.
[POTATO] YES I AM, I AM YOUR FRIEND. TRUST ME.
I'LL TAKE YOU TO A NICE PLACE,
BETTER THAN THE HOUSE OF THE NILE.
I ALSO RUN AWAY FROM THERE.
[RAIN]
[POTATO] COME, GIVE ME YOUR HAND. COME.
[CRYING]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[KISS SNAP]
[TYPHOON] WAIT... WAIT... WAIT...
[CARMINHA] WAS IT GENÉSIO WHO SENT YOU HERE?
[TYPHOON] I HAVE... I HAVE A BRIDE. I HAVE...
[CARMINHA] YOU... OH MY GOD, YOU'RE AN ANGEL.
IT WAS GENÉSIO WHO SENT YOU HERE.
[TYPHOON] DON'T DO THAT, DON'T DO THAT.
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE IT WAS HIM.
[TYPHOON] MY GOD IN HEAVEN...
[CARMINHA] I WILL LIVE,
GENÉSIO, I WILL LIVE. I WILL LIVE.
OF COURSE I WILL LIVE. I PROMISE YOU,
I WILL NEVER THINK ABOUT CRAZY THINGS AGAIN, GENÉSIO. OF COURSE.
OF COURSE, MY LOVE. OF COURSE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[TELEVISION IN THE BACKGROUND]
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪KNOW US WELL♪
♪NEITHER THE SAME NOR DIFFERENT♪
♪IT'S NOT BEFORE OR AFTER♪
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪IT'S WHAT WE FEEL♪
♪NEITHER GUILTY OR INNOCENT♪
♪IN THIS STORY OF US TWO♪
[TYPHOON] THIS SHOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED.
[CARMINHA] NO, YOU SHOULDN'T.
[RAIN]
[CARMINHA] MY GOD IN HEAVEN, WHAT DID I DO?
[TYPHOON] I'M ENGAGED. MY BRIDE MUST BE WAITING FOR ME,
I HAVE TO GO AWAY.
[STEPS]
[CARMINHA] I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY TO YOU.
[RAIN]
[TYPHOON] I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY EITHER.
[CARMINHA] I'M SO EMBARRASSED, YOU KNOW?
I'M SORRY, OK?
I DON'T KNOW WHERE MY HEAD WAS,
I THINK I'M GOING CRAZY.
IT'S JUST THAT, FOR A SECOND...
IT'S AS IF YOU WERE THE GENESIO,
AS IF MY GENESUS HAD COME BACK TO ME.
[RAIN]
[CARMINHA] I'M REALLY CRAZY, I'M REALLY CRAZY.
[TYPHOON] I THINK I'M GOING CRAZY TOO,
BECAUSE I'M ABOUT TO GET MARRIED.
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE, OF COURSE.
[TYPHOON] YOU KNOW THAT.
[CARMINHA] I KNOW. OF COURSE.
[TYPHOON] THEN. FOR ALL PURPOSES,
THIS NEVER HAPPENED. OK?
[CARMINHA] NO, YOU CAN REMAIN CALM.
NOBODY WILL KNOW, FROM ME,
NOBODY WILL EVER KNOW ANYTHING.
[TYPHOON] ARE YOU GOING TO BE OKAY?
[CARMINHA] DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME, NO.
[TYPHOON] WHEN DO YOU HAVE TO DELIVER THIS HOUSE?
[CARMINHA] NEXT WEEK, BUT FORGET ABOUT IT.
[TYPHOON] NO, NO, I WANT YOU TO STAY IN AN APARTMENT OF MINE
WHICH IS EMPTY, UNTIL WE FIND YOU A HOUSE.
[CARMINHA] NO, NO, FORGET ABOUT IT, FORGET ABOUT IT.
[TYPHOON] ACCEPTING THIS HOUSE WOULD BE A FAVOR YOU ARE DOING ME.
[CARMINHA] WE'LL THINK ABOUT IT LATER.
NOW, GO AWAY, GO AWAY, PLEASE,
I DON'T WANT TO KEEP YOU HERE ANYMORE.
[STEPS]
[CARMINHA] I'M SORRY, OK?
I'M SORRY.
[RAIN]
[CARMINHA] "ACCEPTING THIS HOUSE WOULD BE A FAVOR
THAT YOU WOULD BE DOING TO ME."
LEAVE ME, I'LL DO YOU THIS FAVOR,
IDIOT. FOOL. [LAUGHTER]
[RITA] IS THIS YOUR HOUSE?
[POTATO] IT'S MOTHER LUCINDA'S HOUSE. THAT'S WHERE I LIVE.
[RITA] A BEAUTIFUL HOUSE.
[POTATO] I KNOW. MOTHER LUCINDA BUILT THIS HOUSE
WITH THE THINGS WE COLLECT FROM THE GARBAGE.
SHE IS THE BEST PERSON IN THE WORLD.
I WILL FIND A WAY FOR YOU TO LIVE WITH US.
[RITA] ARE WE NOT GOING TO COME IN?
[POTATO] THERE ARE TWO CHILDREN IN THE HOUSE,
MOTHER LUCINDA SAYS SHE DOESN'T HAVE SPACE FOR ANY OF THEM ANYMORE.
[RITA] I GOT YOU IN TROUBLE, DIDN'T I?
[POTATO] OH, STOP THE NONSENSE, I'LL FIX EVERYTHING.
YOU'LL SEE.
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO STAY THERE WHILE I TALK TO MOTHER LUCINDA.
I'LL GET YOU SOME FOOD, HERE WE GO.
[LUCINDA] HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING AWAKE
ALL WET, BOY?
[POTATO] NO, IT'S JUST...
I'M JUST HUNGRY.
[LUCINDA] WHAT WHAT
ARE YOU UP TO IT?
[POTATO] NO, I'M NOT GETTING READY
NOTHING, MOMMY.
[LUCINDA] THEN GO TO LIE DOWN, GO.
TAKE OFF THOSE CLOTHES, BOY, YOU HAVE TO WAKE UP EARLY TOMORROW.
[POTATO] I'LL TAKE IT OUT NOW.
[POTATO] YOU MUST BE STARVING.
[POTATO] BUT FIRST CHANGE THOSE CLOTHES,
IF NOT YOU'LL GET THE FLU. I'LL TURN TO THE SIDE.
[POTATO] OK, I'LL TURN TO THE SIDE AND KEEP MY EYES CLOSED.
[RITA] IT CAN TURN.
[POTATO] [LAUGHTER]
[RITA] WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING AT, FOOL?
[POTATO] YOU LOOK LIKE EMERSON, MY FRIEND.
[RITA] HUM... FUNNY.
[RITA] AM I GOING TO HAVE TO STAY HIDDEN HERE?
[POTATO] JUST A LITTLE BIT. UNTIL I EXCHANGE AN IDEAS WITH MOTHER.
[RITA] THANK YOU.
[POTATO] BUT THERE IS ONLY ONE THING
MOTHER LUCINDA SAYS THAT IT IS FORBIDDEN HERE TO BE SAD.
SLEEP WELL. IF YOU NEED ANYTHING, I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
[CARMINHA] I CALLED YOUR CELL PHONE
TEN THOUSAND TIMES AND YOU DON'T ANSWER, RIGHT?
[MAX] I GAVE YOU A LITTLE SLAPPING, DIDN'T I, DEAR?
[CARMINHA] CARMINHA SCORED A GOAL, ONE TO ZERO FOR US.
[MAX] WHAT'S UP? DID YOU MANAGE TO GET THE GUY TO BED?
[CARMINHA] [LAUGHTER] IT WAS A HARD TIME, BUT I DID IT.
[MAX] AH, CUTE.
[LAUGHTER] THAT'S COOL.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO LIKE? CELEBRATE THIS WITH YOU,
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
[CARMINHA] ARE YOU JEALOUS?
DIDN'T I SAY I HAD A GAME WITH THE GUY, HUH?
[MAX] WHAT "GAME" WHAT? WHAT "GAME"? DON'T TRAVEL,
CARMINHA, THE GUY IS ENGAGED, DO YOU THINK HE'LL DROP HER OFF?
IS HIS FIANCE GOING TO STAY WITH YOU?
[CARMINHA] SHE WON'T DISMISS, BUT SHE WILL REPORT THAT SHE HAD SEX
WITH ME AND THE TWO OF THEM WILL FIGHT, HOW MUCH DO YOU WANT TO BET?
[THUNDER]
[MONALISA] YOU CAN ORDER DINNER, BECAUSE I ALREADY ATE ALL OF IT
IN THESE HOURS I WAITED WAITING FOR YOU.
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, SORRY.
[MONALISA] "SORRY",
OKAY, WHAT'S THE EXCUSE? I'M PAYING TO SEE.
[TYPHOON] THE WOMAN WENT CRAZY, THE WOMAN SAID SHE WAS GOING TO KILL HERSELF,
UNDERSTAND? I COULDN'T LEAVE, I WAS SCARED
HER DOING SOMETHING CRAZY. I'M ALREADY DEAD
BEHIND MY BACK, IMAGINE A SECOND DEATH.
[MONALISA] WHAT'S THAT SMELL? DID YOU DRINK IT, TYPHOON?
[TYPHOON] I HAD A LITTLE WHISKEY.
[MONALISA] YOU DRANK BEER... YOU...
YOU SAY, YOU SMELL LIKE A WOMAN!
DID YOU HAVE SEX WITH THIS WOMAN, TYPHOON?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY PACE♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK IT♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[MONALISA] TYPHOON, RESPOND!
GOT MUTE?
DID YOU HAVE SEX WITH THIS WOMAN?
[TYPHOON] NO, OF COURSE NOT.
[MONALISA] YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO LIE. I SEE IT,
IT'S WRITTEN ON YOUR FOREHEAD THAT YOU HAD SEX WITH THIS WOMAN!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS HAPPENED,
OK? BECAUSE SHE... SHE ASKED ME TO LAY DOWN ON THE SIDE
HER, WHERE HER HUSBAND LAY,
BECAUSE SHE WAS AFRAID OF BEING ALONE.
[MONALISA] NO, NO, NO! SPARSE ME THE DETAILS,
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD. I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
YOU KNOW? IT'S GOOD FOR ME!
[TYPHOON] STOP, MONALISA!
I WAS DRUNK, I WAS CRAZY, YOU UNDERSTAND?
[MONALISA] WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN? THAT YOU DID A CHARITY,
IS THAT IT? YOU GOT DRUNK WITH WHISKEY AND GOT ​​THIS
WOMAN, FOR CHARITY, FOR GUILT OF HAVING RUN OVER HER HUSBAND?
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M HEARING THIS!
[TYPHOON] FORGIVE ME, FORGIVE ME, FORGIVE ME.
[MONALISA] "FORGIVEN ME"...
[VOICE OVERWHELMED] IT'S "FORGIVE ME",
THAT'S WHAT YOU HAVE TO SAY TO ME. YOU LEAVE ME HERE ALONE,
PLANTED, ON OUR ENGAGEMENT CELEBRATION NIGHT
AND YOU GET WITH A WOMAN. YOU TURN TO ME AND SAY:
"SORRY, FORGIVE ME", IS THAT IT?
[TYPHOON] MONALISA,
I HAVE NEVER DONE THIS AND I WILL NEVER DO IT AGAIN.
[MONALISA] YOU WON'T DO IT AGAIN, NO.
YOU WON'T DO IT AGAIN, DO YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE IT'S ALL OVER BETWEEN US!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, DON'T DO THAT. DON'T SAY THAT,
THAT YOU ARE THE WOMAN OF MY LIFE,
WE'LL STAY TOGETHER UNTIL WE GET OLD, UNDERSTAND?
IT'S NOT BECAUSE OF SOME STUPIDITY LIKE THIS THAT WE CAN SEPARATE!
[MONALISA] LOOK, MY FRIENDS FROM THE SALON,
THEY WERE RIGHT.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] THEY WERE RIGHT, DO YOU KNOW WHY?
FAME HAS GONE TO YOUR HEAD.
[VOICE OVERWHELMED] DO YOU THINK THAT
YOU ARE THE OWNER OF THE WORLD, WHICH YOU CAN NOW STEP ON
IN PEOPLE. I WAS BLIND, BUT I WAS BLIND WITH PASSION,
BUT NOW MY EYES ARE OPENING!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA... NO, THIS IS NOT HAPPENING.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, MONALISA?
[MONALISA] WHERE DO YOU THINK I'M GOING?
I'M LEAVING!
[TYPHOON] I'LL GO WITH YOU.
[MONALISA] NO, YOU WON'T. YOU'LL STAY HERE ALONE,
IN YOUR "TOP EXECUTIVE SUITE KING SIZE"!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, DON'T DO THIS TO ME, MONALISA.
[MONALISA] NO, IT'S NO PROBLEM.
IF YOU FEEL LONELY, YOU CAN CALL A WIDOW WHO IS DOWN
OF LOSING HER HUSBAND, BECAUSE AFTER ALL,
THIS IS YOUR SPECIALTY NOW,
GRAVEYARD CATCHMAN! [SIGH]
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪KNOW US WELL♪
♪NEITHER THE SAME NOR DIFFERENT♪
♪IT'S NOT BEFORE OR AFTER♪
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪IT'S WHAT WE FEEL♪
♪NEITHER GUILTY OR INNOCENT♪
♪IN THIS STORY OF US TWO♪
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪IT'S NOT A WORK OF CHANCE♪
♪IT'S A PLAN DESIGNED♪
♪ SIMPLE THING TO UNDERSTAND ♪
[TYPHOON] MONALISA! GET IN THE CAR, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD!
[WOMAN] GUYS, IT'S THE TYPHOON!
[MONALISA] WANT IT FOR YOURSELF?
[LAUGHTER] YOU CAN. TAKE HER TO SEE THE SUITE,
SHE WILL LOVE IT.
[TYPHOON] MONALISA! MONA...
♪FOR YOU♪
♪FAR FROM YOU♪
♪MY HEART IS LOST♪
♪THE WORLD IS DIVIDED♪
[CHILD] PASS ME A... A FORK.
[CHILD] THERE.
[LUCINDA] LOOK AT THE CAKE
RAIN COMING OUT!
[CHRIES OF CELEBRATION]
[CHILD] I DID IT!
[LUCINDA] WOW, LOOK AT THIS,
SLEEPING BEAUTY WOKE UP! WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU'RE ALWAYS THE FIRST ONE TO GET UP TO MAKE COFFEE
IN THE MORNING.
[POTATO] I DIDN'T SLEEP RIGHT, NO,
IT WAS... IT WAS VERY HOT.
[LUCINDA] WELL, BUT EMERSON DIDN'T FIND A NICE FAN,
THIS WEEK, IN THE TRASH? HUH? IT'S ALREADY SPOILED?
[POTATO] NO. IT'S... I DON'T KNOW, MOM, I JUST SLEPT A LITTLE MORE.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
[LUCINDA] NO,
SLEPT A LITTLE MORE, BECAUSE, RIGHT?
HE ARRIVED LATE, ALL WET, IN THE MIDDLE OF THE RAIN.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[POTATO] I... I FIXED THE ROOF OF THE CHICKEN COOP,
THAT THE CHICKENS WERE GETTING WET IN THE STORM.
[LUCINDA] THE CHICKENS, HUH? [LAUGHTER]
OH, THERE'S VITAMIN IN THE FRIDGE,
OF AVOCADO.
[LUCINDA] SO, LET'S EAT, LET'S EAT!
LET'S THROW THINGS IN THE TRASH!
YOU DON'T MISS OUT ON BREAKFAST, NO, YOU SEE?
WE'RE WAITING FOR YOU OUT HERE, OK?
AND HEY, THERE'S A RAIN CAKE, I JUST MADE IT.
LET'S GO. GOT, GOT, GOT, GOT THE GLOVES? WHERE ARE THEM?
SO NOW WE GO. [LAUGHTER]
LET ME SEE.
OH... HELLO! WHO DO YOU WANT TO TALK TO?
[LAUGHTER] GIVE HIM THIS ONE, PUT THE LITTLE BIRD INSIDE, LOOK.
WELL, SINCE THERE'S NO BIRD, PUT THE FEATHER, PUT IT HERE.
HEY! [LAUGHTER] OH, GUYS, LOOK WHAT I FOUND HERE.
OH... HERE, BETHANY, OH, BETHANY, WHAT I FOUND HERE.
OH, BETANIA, I FOUND A MIRROR, IT'S ALL INTACT.
[BETÂNIA] [LAUGHTER] WOW, THIS EXPERIMENT IS REALLY COOL.
[LUCINDA] [LAUGHTER] AH, THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL THING.
THE MIRROR IS ALL FULL AND CHIC, HUH? HUM... LOOK! [LAUGHTER]
[NILO] WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING TODAY?
COME ON, GIRL, FILL THE GARBAGE BAG. I WANT TO SEE, LET'S GET TO WORK.
AND THIS SHAMELESS GUY HERE, HUH? HARD FACE,
ARE YOU SLEEPING? GO GET SOME TRASH,
KID, GO PICK UP TRASH...
BECAUSE THIS THING DOESN'T...
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] OH! SO, IF IT WAS A SNAKE I WOULD HAVE BITE IT, HUH?
[NILO] AH, ALTHOUGH YOU MUST BE MISSING SOMETHING
SNAKE, ISN'T IT? BUT FOR THOSE WHO KEEP A RATTLESNAKE IN THEIR HOUSE,
DON'T BE SCARED OF ANYTHING.
[LUCINDA] OH, WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
[NILO] I'M TALKING ABOUT BATATA, HE'S PROTECTING THE NEW GIRL.
[LUCINDA] WHAT ARE YOU ACCUSING BATATA OF?
[NILO] AFTER HIDING MY NEW GIRL, SHE DISAPPEARED.
[LUCINDA] AH, BUT I DON'T DOUBT MUCH THAT YOU HAVE DONE IT
WITH HER WHAT YOU'VE ALREADY DONE WITH SO MANY OTHERS, RIGHT?
MAY THE POOR GIRL'S BODY APPEAR THERE IN THE MIDDLE OF THE TRASH.
NOW, DO YOU WANT TO ACCUSE BATATA?
[NILO] SHE IS SPECIAL, SHE IS A FINE EATER, SHE IS NOT ONE TO PLAY AROUND
NO OUT. SHE'S HERE, I KNOW, I FEEL,
BUT IF I KNOW THAT IT WAS BATATA WHO HID HER,
OUR DEAL OF NOT INTERFERING IN EACH OTHER'S LIVES
GO TO HELL, HUH?
FOR THE CUCUIA.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] POTATO! COME HERE, BOY. COME!
[LUCINDA] RUN!
[POTATO] WHAT'S UP?
[LUCINDA] OH BATATA, WHERE DID YOU HIDE THE GIRL FROM THE NILE?
[POTATO] BUT... WHAT GIRL, MOTHER?
[LUCINDA] OH, YOU KNOW VERY WELL WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT,
BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN COVERING UP FOR HER SINCE LAST NIGHT I KNOW.
[POTATO] OH, MOM, IT WAS NOTHING.
[LUCINDA] OH, WHAT'S THE FIRST LAW AT HOME, HUH?
[POTATO] NO SECRETS. ONE TRUSTS THE OTHER.
[LUCINDA] WHERE DID YOU HID THE GIRL? SPEAK.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RITA] POTATO?
[LUCINDA] COME. COME WITH ME, COME. COME.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] GO, GO, GO.
[LUCINDA] YOU CAN EAT AS MUCH AS YOU WANT,
BUT THEN YOU HAVE TO FIND YOUR OWN DIRECTION, OK?
[POTATO] NO, MOTHER LUCINDA, SHE HAS NOWHERE TO GO.
HER FATHER DIED, IT WAS JUST THE TWO OF THEM.
[LUCINDA] BUT, BATATA, YOU KNOW, NOT HERE...
POTATO, THERE'S NO ROOM FOR ANYONE ELSE. THERE ARE 12 MOUTHS TO EAT,
12 SON TO... GIVE MEDICINE, TO PUT ON CLOTHES, IT'S NOT POSSIBLE,
THERE ARE NO CONDITIONS, RIGHT?
[RITA] YOU'RE VERY GOOD, MOTHER LUCINDA, YOU CAN SEE IT IN YOUR EYES.
BUT THANKS ANYWAY. THANKS, BATATA.
[POTATO] SHE'S NOT GOING AWAY! IF SHE LEAVES, I'M GOING WITH HER.
[LUCINDA] OH, LET GO OF IT
"BRAVALRY",
ARE YOU WANTING TO SHOW OFF TO THE GIRL, HUH?
[POTATO] IF SHE GOES BACK TO THE NILE, SHE WILL DIE, OR MAYBE TURN
ANOTHER ONE OF THOSE DEMONS THERE.
[RITA] LEAVE IT, BATATA, I KNOW HOW TO FIND MYSELF,
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE ANY TROUBLE.
[RITA] DONA LUCINDA DOESN'T WANT TROUBLE WITH ME.
[POTATO] AH, SO THERE'S NO MORE NILO, THERE'S NOTHING ELSE.
I'M LEAVING HERE FROM THE DUMP. ME AND YOU, RIGHT, RITA?
LET'S GO TOGETHER.
[LUCINDA] WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
[POTATO] THAT'S RIGHT, MOTHER LUCINDA, IT'S DECIDED!
IF RITA CAN'T STAY HERE AT HOME, I'LL RUN AWAY WITH HER
AND WE'LL FIND A WAY TO GET AROUND.
I'M GOING TO GET MY STUFF AND I'LL BE BACK.
[LUCINDA] YOU'RE A HARD-HEADED LITTLE ONE, HUH?
[POTATO] BYE, MOTHER LUCINDA, ONE DAY I'LL COME TO VISIT YOU.
[LUCINDA] AND CAN I KNOW WHERE YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE LUNCH?
AND WHERE WILL YOU SLEEP?
[POTATO] OH, WE BEG FOR ALMS TO EAT, RITA, RITA?
[RITA] AND SLEEP UNDER THE AWNING.
[LUCINDA] ARE YOU TAKING A BLANKET? IF IT GETS COLD, YOU'LL CATCH A COLD
AND THERE WILL BE NOBODY TO TAKE SYRUP ON A SPOON, OK?
[POTATO] IF I DIE, I DIE.
[ALL] MOTHER LUCINDA, HE WILL STARVE TO DEATH, PLEASE,
DON'T LET IT. DON'T LET IT, MOTHER LUCINDA.
[LUCINDA] HEY BATATA, STOP THE DRAMA, BATATA, RITA IS STAYING!
RITA STAYS!
[LUCINDA] HEY! I'LL TELL YOU...
[CHRIES OF CELEBRATION]
[CHILD] YEAH, MAN! I KNEW IT!
I KNEW IT, MAN!
[OLENKA] MONALISA. WAKE UP. WAKE UP,
YOUR MAN IS DOWN THERE. HE HAS DARK CIRCLES FROM THE DAY BEFORE YESTERDAY,
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
[MONALISA] TELL HIM TO GO AWAY.
TELL THAT DONKEY NEVER TO SHOW UP AGAIN.
[OLENKA] ARE YOU SURE?
[MONALISA] I HAVE.
[OLENKA] OK, IF YOU DON'T WANT IT, THERE ARE SOMEONE WHO DOES.
[MAN] [DISTANT VOICE]
ATTENTION, ATTENTION, ATTENTION,
RESOUNDING THAT MISS MONALISA.
HER GROOM, THE MYTH OF THE DIVINE,
THE KING OF THE LAWNS, THE HERO OF OUR PEOPLE,
JOR-JOR-JOR-JORGE TYPHOON, ASK YOUR EXCELLENCY
LET HIM SHOW HIS GRACE! [LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, LOOK, I PROMISE IT'S THE LAST THING
I'M GOING TO ASK YOU IN LIFE, COME OUT HERE.
[TYPHOON] COME HERE AND LISTEN TO WHAT I HAVE TO SAY TO YOU.
DO YOU WANT ME TO KNEEL? THEN OKAY, I'M KNEELING
HERE IN FRONT OF EVERYONE.
[TYPHOON] I WANT TO ASK YOU, MY LOVE, TO COME OUT HERE
TO HEAR WHAT I HAVE TO SAY TO YOU.
[MONALISA] THIS IS THE PARROT IN FRONT OF MY PLACE
AT WORK? I'M GOING TO YOUR GAME TO MAKE A SCANDAL?
YOU'RE GOING TO SCARENTURE THE PARISH. PLEASE, CAN YOU PULL THIS CAR AWAY?
FROM HERE I HAVE NOTHING ELSE TO SAY TO YOU,
GET OUT OF MY LIFE!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, LISTEN TO ME.
[TYPHOON] I'M AN IDIOT, I ONLY DO STUPID THINGS.
NOW, YOU ARE THE BEST WOMAN IN THE WORLD. YOU ARE MY TALISMAN,
MY GUIDE, MY LUCKY FIG. I AM NOTHING WITHOUT YOU,
YOU ARE THE WOMAN OF MY LIFE.
[MONALISA] ENOUGH, TYPHOON, STOP IT!
[TYPHOON] NO, BECAUSE I AM LIKE THIS, I AM YOURS. THE BODY,
THE SOUL, THE HEART, TILL DEATH DO US PART.
AND I'M SURE, MY LOVE, THAT IF I'M WITHOUT YOU
I WILL DWIN UNTIL I DIE, I KNOW IT.
I'M ASKING YOU NOT TO LET THIS HAPPEN,
DON'T LET ME DIE.
[TYPHOON] FORGIVE ME.
♪THIS IS WHY I LIVE FOR YOU♪
[MONALISA] DON'T TALK TO ME LIKE THAT.
♪BECAUSE NOBODY HAS THE RIGHT♪
♪TELL US WHAT IS PERFECT♪
♪IN THIS STORY THAT IS♪
♪JUST THE TWO OF US♪
[TYPHOON] YOU WILL NOT REGRET IT,
YOU WILL BE THE MOST LOVED WOMAN IN THE WORLD.
[TYPHOON] COME WITH ME, WE WILL STAY TOGETHER FOREVER.
♪JUST THE TWO OF US♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[CONCEIÇÃO] CAN I TAKE THE PLATE OUT OF YOUR CRUCIBLE,
DONA VERONICA?
[VERÔNICA] LOVE, THE PLATE, THE CHAIR, THE CLOTHES IN THE CLOSET,
YOU CAN TAKE EVERYTHING THAT IS HIS AND GIVE IT TO THE FIRST CARTWORKER
THAT APPEARS IN FRONT. CLOWN!
[BELLING]
[VERÔNICA] OH, IT'S HIM! YOU'LL FALL FACE TO FACE AT THE DOOR,
I CHANGED THE LOCK. LOOK, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO LEAVE ME WITH THIS MAN
COME IN HERE, HUH, CONCEIÇÃO.
[CONCEIÇÃO] IT'S NOT YOUR CRUCIBLE, NO, DONA VERÔNICA,
IT'S FROM THE STORE, THEY CALLED THE RECEPTION INTERCOM.
[VERONICA] WHICH STORE?
[DOOR OPEN]
[WOMAN] GOOD AFTERNOON! THEY TOLD THESE DRESSES TO BE DELIVERED HERE.
[CONCEIÇÃO] CAN I SEND IT BACK, MADAME?
[VERÔNICA] YOU CAN! WAIT, LET ME IN JUST A LITTLE.
[VERÔNICA] IS IT FOR ME TO CHOOSE?
[WOMAN] NO, IT WAS ALL BOUGHT FOR YOU.
♪GOD PROTECT ME♪
♪OF YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME♪
♪OF YOUR BITTERNESS♪
[VERONICA] ONE THING IS TRUE,
CARLOS EDUARDO KNOWS MY TASTE.
♪GOD HELP ME♪
♪FROM YOUR ANGER♪
[VERÔNICA] I'LL PROVE IT.
♪OF YOUR POISON♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR END♪
♪GOD PROTECT ME♪
♪OF YOUR ENVY♪
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[VERÔNICA] ARE YOU THINKING YOU CAN BUY ME, CARLOS EDUARDO?
LOVE, I'M VERY EXPENSIVE, SEE? I'M NOT CHEAP, NO.
DO YOU REALLY THINK I'M GOING TO COME DOWN THERE TO FIND YOU?
AT THE RECEPTION?
[VERÔNICA] I DON'T WANT TO KNOW ANY SURPRISES, OK?
YOU TAKE THIS LITTLE SURPRISE OF YOURS AND GO DRINK SALT!
[VERÔNICA] SOMETIMES IN LIFE WE HAVE TO BE FIRM,
CONCEIÇÃO. I DON'T WANT TO KNOW ANY SURPRISES, I'M NOT LEAVING HERE.
♪GOD GOD GO WITH ME♪
♪GOD SUPPORT ME♪
♪GOD LIFT ME UP♪
♪GOD GIVE ME STRENGTH♪
[CADINHO] DO YOU WANT TO TEST DRIVE NOW OR LATER? HUM?
[CRUCIBLE] IT'S YOURS. COME IN, HUM?
[CRUITLING] HUM, OH, FOR YOU. HUH? DID YOU FEEL THE BENCH?
ITALIAN LEATHER. NEW CAR SMELL. HUH?
BE CAREFUL, IF YOU PRESS THE ACCELERATOR IT WILL FLY. [LAUGHTER]
[VERÔNICA] YOU'RE NO GOOD, CADINHO.
[CAR ENGINE]
[CRUITLING] [CLEARING] HOW WAS THE WEATHER THERE, CIÇA, HEAVY?
[CIÇA] DO YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW THE TRUTH, YOU LITTLE CRUCIFIX?
[CADINHO] WELL, LOOK, I'M GOING TO HAVE TO GO BACK TO BRASILIA.
TRY TO HELP VERÔ RELAX, OK?
PREPARE A BUBBLE BATH,
POUR THAT GLASS OF CHAMPAGNE
IN THE LATE AFTERNOON THAT SHE LIKES SO MUCH, OK?
LOOK HERE, LOOK, AT YOU.
[CRUITLING] A BONUS, OK?
THANK YOU, CIÇA.
[NOÊMIA] IT'S THE ULTIMATE! IT'S UNACCEPTABLE!
EVEN WHEN I WAS 18, I ONLY DATED HIPPIES,
I WAS STANDING IN THE RESTAURANT WAITING FOR SOMEONE!
[CIDA] DONA NOÊMIA, YOUR DUDU IS HERE.
[NOÊMIA] TELL THIS MAN THAT I WANT TO SEE HIM DEAD!
BY THE WAY, IF HE LEAVES THIS FOR A BETTER DAY,
I'M NOT EVEN GOING TO THE BURIAL.
[CIDA] DONA NOÊMIA, I THINK IT'S BETTER FOR YOU TO GO OUTSIDE,
HE'S IN AN AMBULANCE!
[NOÊMIA] [SCREAMING] DUDU! LET'S GO.
[NOÊMIA] DUDU! DUDU, WHAT HAPPENED, DUDU?
[MAN] WAS IN A CAR ACCIDENT, THERE WERE MANY BRUISES,
IT IS IMPORTANT THAT HE RESTS.
[NOÊMIA] MY GOD, WHAT MADNESS!
YOU'RE HERE ALL HURT AND I'M INSIDE ANGRY, CIDA.
[CADINHO] I TRIED TO COMMUNICATE IN THE HOSPITAL,
BUT I LOST MY SENSES.
[NOÊMIA] DOESN'T SPEAK, DOESN'T SPEAK, DOESN'T SPEAK.
PRESERVE YOURSELF, PRESERVE YOURSELF.
PREPARE SOME FOOD FOR MY LITTLE CHUCHUZINHO,
AN ANGEL'S HAIR WITH PESTO.
COME ON, CIDA, YOU CAN BRING HIM HERE, COME ON CIDA.
[MAN] GONE.
[CADINHO] REALLY GOOD, HUH? WOW.
HERE IT IS, LOOK, WAIT A LITTLE.
GREAT, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[MAN] OH, CHECK IF IT'S RIGHT.
[MAN] HEY.
[CRUCIBLE] WELL, THERE WERE NO 300
REAL?
[MAN] 350, RIGHT?
WHAT ABOUT THE ACTORS UNION FEE? HMM, I SAID, FAT.
[CRUITLING] OK, HERE IT IS.
[MURICY] I CAN'T BELIEVE WHAT I'M HEARING.
DID YOU COME BACK WITH THAT BANDACEIRA?
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, MY SON, GIVE UP ON THAT WOMAN,
LEAVE HER ALONE!
[TYPHOON] I LOVE MONALISA, MOMMY.
I AM TELLING YOU THAT I WILL MARRY MONALISA.
[MURICY] WITH SO MANY WOMEN IN THIS WORLD,
WHY DID THIS BOY CHOOSE THAT ONE?
BADLY DRESSED RETIRED?
[LELECO] YOU CHOSE YOUR WIFE VERY WELL,
MY SON, MONALISA IS A WOMAN OF VALUE.
[MURICY] YOU DON'T LISTEN, YOU DON'T LISTEN TO WHAT THIS OLD MAN SAYS
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND ANY OF THIS.
[LELECO] I DON'T UNDERSTAND ANY OF THIS?
WHAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND ABOUT THIS... OH, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY,
I REALLY DON'T UNDERSTAND ANY OF THIS, BECAUSE I MARRIED YOU.
[MURICY] OH, THANK GOD.
[IVANA] GUYS, STOP FIGHTING, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD.
[TYPHOON] LOOK HERE YOU TOO, SISTER,
I WANT THE MONALISM TO BE TREATED VERY WELL
FROM HERE ONWARDS IN HERE
AND I DON'T WANT TO HEAR THE WORD "CANGACEIRA" ANYMORE.
AND I'M GOING TO BECOME A MEMBER IN THE SALON SHE'S OPENING.
[MURICY] I'M TALKING, I'M TALKING.
SHE HASN'T EVEN STEPPED ON THE ALTAR YET
AND YOU'RE ALREADY REACHING YOUR POCKET.
[TYPHOON] MOM, FOR YOUR GOVERNMENT, SHE ONLY ACCEPTED ME
AS A PARTNER AFTER MUCH INSISTENCE.
I JUST WANT IT BECAUSE I THINK IT
THAT WILL BE A GOOD DEAL FOR ME, UNDERSTAND?
[IVANA] I THINK SO TOO. THAT'S IT, I SAID IT, MOM.
AND I SAY MORE, THIS STRAIGHTENING FORMULA THAT SHE INVENTED
IT'S A SHOW, I'M A CUSTOMER MYSELF.
SO, HEY, IT'S GOING TO MAKE US A LOT OF MONEY, HUH? TRUST ME.
[MURICY] THANK YOU SO MUCH, IVANA. I APPRECIATE IT.
I THROW IN THE TOWEL, RIGHT?
IT LOOKS LIKE THIS MARIA IS BEAUTIFUL.
IS IT OK "MARIA BONITA"?
IT SEEMS LIKE SHE HAS BEwitched YOU ALL, RIGHT?
[MURICY] AFTER YOU END UP WITH YOUR DONKEYS IN THE WATER,
DON'T SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU
THAT THIS HAIR SALON BUSINESS IS A SCAM.
IT'S A HOAX.
[IVANA] OH! SHE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT SHE'S TALKING ABOUT, GUYS.
[TYPHOON] PAY ATTENTION, SISTER, I STILL WANT IT
YOU'RE MY PARTNER, AREN'T YOU GOOD AT ACCOUNTING?
SO, I'M COMING IN WITH THE MONEY,
MONALISA WITH TALENT, AND YOU CLEAN THE HOUSE.
[IVANA] IT TOOK A WHILE, I'M IN.
[LELECO] AND WHERE DO I GO IN?
[IVANA] YOU, DAD, HOW ABOUT IF YOU STAY IN THE POOL KIT, HUH?
OVER THERE AT THE BAR. WHERE YOU NEVER LEFT, RIGHT? [LAUGHTER]
OH, DAD. SO, DID YOU LIKE IT?
THE STREET IS GREAT, LOOK, THERE'S A BUS STOP AT THE DOOR.
TELL ME IF THIS ISN'T THE IDEAL SPOT FOR US TO OPEN THE SALON?
[MONALISA] IVANA, YOU HIT IT RIGHT THE WAY.
[TYPHOON] HERE, OH, MY PRINCESS, I JUST DON'T WANT
LOSING MY WIFE TO WORK, HUH?
YOU HAVE TO BE HOME BY 6PM AT THE LATER, OK?
[MONALISA] LEAVE IT, OLENKA IS THERE TO RELIEVE ME.
SHE IS THE CO-PILOT OF THE SHOW, IS THAT IT OR ISN'T IT?
[OLENKA] YEAH, I CAN'T WAIT FOR THIS TO BE READY, HUH?
[CELEBRATING SHOUT]
[MONALISA] OH, WHAT EMOTION.
WILL NOBODY COME?
[IVANA] WHAT IS THIS?
[TYPHOON] OH MONALISA, TODAY IS THE FIRST DAY,
WHAT DO YOU WANT, A LINE AT THE DOOR? THAT'S TOO MUCH, RIGHT?
[IVANA] OH, AUNT ANARAÍ GUARANTEED ME
THAT FIVE MORE OF MY GYMNASTICS COLLEAGUES WERE COMING TOO.
[OLENKA] HEY, SISTER, I'M TALKING TO YOU, THIS SALON IS GOING TO BE A BIG HOUSE! [LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] Oh!
[MONALISA] AH! WELCOME!
ARE YOU OK, MRS. ZULEIDE?
LOOK, YOU'RE GOING TO GET A FREE STRAIGHTENING
SINCE YOU WERE MY FIRST CLIENT.
[OLENKA] [LAUGHTER] COME HERE, I'LL PREPARE YOUR HAIR NOW.
[TYPHOON] FOR FREE?
♪I CHERISH THE MOMENTS WITH YOU♪
♪RESPECTFULLY I SAY TO THEE♪
♪I'M AWARE THAT YOU'RE CHEATING♪
♪WHEN NO ONE MAKES♪
♪ME FEEL LIKE YOU DO♪
♪UPSIDE DOWN♪
♪BOY, YOU TURN ME♪
♪INSIDE OUT♪
[OLENKA] GREAT! VERY GOOD. LOOK OVER THERE. I'LL SHOW YOU BACK HERE,
LOOK. SEE? IT'S SMOOTH, HUH? IT'S GOING TO BE AWESOME.
TELL US ABOUT THE SALON.
[MONALISA] PLEASE, OH, THE TREATMENT, OK? CONTINUE AT HOME.
THANK YOU, LINDA.
[MONALISA] GO WITH GOD, OK?
[MONALISA] WHO'S NEXT?
[IVANA] THE GIRL ON THE LEFT.
GIRL, LOOK, I'M ALREADY GIVING OUT PASSWORDS.
[MONALISA] [LAUGHTER]
♪SITTIN' HERE EATIN' MY HEART♪
♪OUT WAITIN'♪
♪WAITIN' FOR SOME LOVE TO CALL♪
♪DIALED ABOUT A THOUSAND♪
♪NUMBERS LATELY♪
[IVANA] GUYS, DIDN'T I TELL YOU? HAIR STRAIGHTENING
IT'S A GOLD MINE. TAKE IT ALL IN AND VISIT IT, JUST IMAGINE
THE AMOUNT OF CURLY HAIR THERE IS STILL IN THE WORLD.
[IVANA] WAIT, WAIT, LET'S ORGANIZE THIS HERE,
IT IS ON A FIRST COME BASIS.
[OLENKA] AH!
♪GONNA HAVE SOME LOVE TONIGHT♪
♪HOT STUFF♪
♪I NEED♪
♪I WANT SOME HOT STUFF♪
[MONALISA] YOU CAN SAY, DOCTOR, IT'S SERIOUS, RIGHT? I KNOW IT IS,
BECAUSE I'M FEELING SO WEIRD, I KNOW IT'S COMING TO BOOM
AROUND THERE. MY FATHER, I'M READY, I JUST ASK YOU
ONE THING, DON'T ASK ME TO REST TODAY, BECAUSE TODAY
IT'S MY ENGAGEMENT PARTY, MY WHOLE FAMILY IS COMING
FROM PARAÍBA, I AM NOT ABLE TO STAY IN BED, NO.
[MAN] THIS IS A PERFECT DAY FOR YOU TO RECEIVE THE NEWS
THAT I HAVE TO GIVE YOU. YOU ARE PREGNANT, MONALISA.
[MONALISA] [LAUGHTER] PREGNANT? I... I'M... I'M PREGNANT?
[MONALISA] I HAVE A BREAST, DOCTOR?
AUNT DÉA, I MISS YOU SO MUCH! [LAUGHTER]
OH COUSIN HOSEAS, OH, HOW GOOD! OH JUNO, DID YOU HAVE A GOOD TRIP?
[JUNO] THIS IS TOO FAR, THE JOURNEY SEEMS LIKE IT NEVER ENDS
NEVER.
[MONALISA] WHY DIDN'T THEY ACCEPT THE PLANE TICKET?
WHAT DID I OFFER YOU?
[HOSEA] NEITHER I NOR JUNO WILL SET FOOT ON THAT ANIMAL
OF FLYING IRON.
[MONALISA] [LAUGHTER] AUNT DÉA, AUNT DÉA, I... I WANT TO TELL YOU
ONE THING. I WANT YOU TO BE THE FIRST TO KNOW.
I'M PREGNANT WITH THE TYPHOON!
[DÉA] HOW WONDERFUL, MY DAUGHTER!
[MONALISA] I FOUND OUT ABOUT THIS NOW, I DIDN'T EVEN TELL YOU
FOR HIM STILL. I'LL TELL HIM TODAY, AT THE PARTY.
AT TOAST TIME. [LAUGHTER]
[DÉA] MY OUR LADY, THIS PARTY IS GOING TO BE AN EMOTION,
MY DAUGHTER! HOW BEAUTIFUL!
[MAX] [GRUNTING] [LAUGHTER]
[CARMINHA] MARGARIDA APPEARED.
[MAX] WHAT'S UP, HOT?
[CARMINHA] WHERE DID YOU GO YESTERDAY?
[MAX] "WHAT DID I GET MYSELF INTO YESTERDAY", I WAS WORKING FOR YOU, MISS,
RIGHT? I MANAGED TO GO OUT WITH TYPHOON'S BRIDE'S FRIEND,
THE ONE WHO WORKS IN THE SALON. LOOK, WHAT'S THAT?
WHAT A VIEW! HIGH FLOOR, OH, KIDDIE, I LIKED THE APARTMENT
THAT THE IDIOT LOANED YOU...
[CARMINHA] THIS CRAP, MAX?
YOU'RE REALLY UNCONSCIOUS, RIGHT?
[MAX] OH, STOP THAT. THERE.
[CARMINHA] COME HERE, DON'T ASK ME HOW IT WAS
NOT THE DOCTOR, HUH?
[MAX] HUM...
[CARMINHA] DO YOU REMEMBER THAT I WENT TO THE DOCTOR YESTERDAY,
OR DID YOU FORGET?
[MAX] I REALLY FORGOT, WHY? IS THERE A PROBLEM?
[CARMINHA] THE PROBLEM IS... IT DEPENDS ON THE POINT OF VIEW.
[MAX] I DON'T UNDERSTAND, ARE YOU SICK?
[CARMINHA] I'M PREGNANT.
[MAX] PREGNANT... PREGNANT WITH ME?
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE IT'S YOURS, MAX.
[MAX] WHAT ELSE...
[CARMINHA] IT'S YOUR FAULT, FOR BEING LAZY TO USE A CONDOM.
AND IT WASN'T THE FIRST TIME.
[MAX] STOP IT... STOP IT, STOP IT! DON'T SAY IT LIKE THAT,
WOW, A CHILD IS COMING
FOR THE WORLD. OUR SON, WHAT A THING...
THIS TIME IT WILL BE DIFFERENT, THE FIRST TIME WE WERE
IN A BAD SHORT STORIES, NOT LIKE THIS,
WE'RE DOING WELL, MY LOVE.
[CARMINHA] THAT'S WELL DONE, MAX? WHAT ARE YOU REFERRING TO?
TO THE CARAMINGUÁ THAT GENÉSIO LEFT ME?
[MAX] WHAT THE FUCK, MAN? MAN, ME, HUH! AND THE HOUSE?
THE HOUSE THAT THE TYPHOON WILL GIVE YOU?
[CARMINHA] LITTLE DOWNTOWN HOUSE
MIXED INCOME, EVERYTHING MIXED.
[MAX] OH, HEY, CARMINHA, STOP THAT, MAN,
STOP YOUR DELUSION OF GREATNESS!
[CARMINHA] I DO HAVE DEVIATIONS OF GREATNESS AND I THANK YOU
TO MY DELUSION OF GREATNESS, THAT WE ARE NOT IN THE GARBAGE.
[MAX] COME HERE, TELL ME SOMETHING. WHEN WILL WE KNOW
IS IT A BOY OR A GIRL, HUH? HUM?
[CARMINHA] IT DOESN'T MATTER. I WOULD TAKE IT OFF FOR ME.
[CARMINHA] OH NO, THIS BABY CAME AT A GOOD TIME.
A CHILD WHO NEEDS A FATHER.
[MAX] YES, THAT'S RIGHT. AND DAD'S HERE, HUM?
[CARMINHA] WHAT THE FUCK, DAD, MAX? YOU, DAD? DAD IS THE ONE WHO PAYS
THE ACCOUNTS.
[MAX] NO, WAIT,
I DON'T BELIEVE IT. YOU WON'T SAY IT
THAT THIS SON IS FROM TUFOON, THAT THIS IS TOO MUCH FORCE,
CARMINHA. STOP IT!
[CARMINHA] STOP BEING STUPID,
MAX. I WILL DO MUCH BETTER.
[CARMINHA] I WILL SAY THAT THE SON IS GENÉSIO'S. IF A WIDOW
A HOUSE IS WORTH HOW MUCH IS THE COMPLETE PACKAGE NOT WORTH?
A LITTLE ORPHAN INSIDE THE WIDOW, HUH?
[CARMINHA] DID YOU DO YOUR PART? SAID IT, FIND OUT
ABOUT THE MONALISM WITH THAT WOMAN?
[MAX] THAT'S A DIFFERENT STORY, RIGHT? I'LL TELL YOU THE FOLLOWING.
[CARMINHA] HUM?
[MAX] IF I WERE YOU,
I LOST HOPE OF GETTING WITH THIS GUY, SEE?
THIS MONALISA IS FIXING UP
AN ENGAGEMENT PARTY AND HE SAID THAT PARAÍBADA
IT HAS ALREADY COME DOWN TO RIO DE JANEIRO.
[CARMINHA] ENGAGEMENT PARTY?
[CARMINHA] VERY INTERESTING.
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[CADINHO] HEY, ROSE, CALL VERÔNICA AND NOÊMIA
AND TELL THEM THAT THE TICKETS FOR NEW YEAR'S EVE
THEY'RE ALREADY BOUGHT, OK? THANK YOU.
[SIGH] THANK GOD IT'S ALREADY THE END OF THE YEAR, I'M EXHAUSTED.
[JIMMY] I DON'T UNDERSTAND, NO. ARE YOU GOING TO TRAVEL WITH BOTH OF THEM?
[CADINHO] NO, LUCKILY FOR ME, NOÊMIA ALWAYS LIKES TO PASS
NEW YEAR'S EVE ALONE MEDITATING IN A BUDDHIST TEMPLE IN NEPAL,
AND I'M GOING TO TAKE VERÔNICA TO A LITTLE RESORT IN THE MALDIVES.
[PHONE RINGING]
[ROSE] [ELECTRONIC VOICE]
DONA NOÊMIA ON LINE ONE.
[CRUITLING] [SIGH] HI, NONO. READY FOR NEPAL?
[NOÊMIA] WHAT NEPAL, CADINHO? HAVEN'T YOU READ THE NEWSPAPERS?
THERE WILL BE A MILLENNIUM BUG WHEN IT TURNS FROM 99 TO 00,
COMPUTER WILL MELT, AIRPORT WILL CLOSE,
EVEN TOLL GATEWAYS WILL BE A BLAST.
I WANT TO SPEND THIS NEW YEAR'S EVE HERE IN RIO,
YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO STAY TOO.
[CRUCIBLE] ME? I'M GOING, I'M GOING. I'M GOING TO STAY IN RIO,
OF COURSE, I'LL STAY IN RIO.
[NOÊMIA] THAT'S GREAT,
SO WE WILL BREAK THIS MILLENNIUM TOGETHER,
HUGGING WITH TOMÁS. WE CAN CALL IT, LIKE THAT,
ABOUT THREE FRIENDS, ONLY THE CLOSEST PEOPLE, RIGHT, DUDU?
[EXTENDED] OH! WHY DON'T WE RENT
A HOTEL SUITE IN COPA TO WATCH THE FIREWORKS?
WHAT DO YOU TELL ME?
[CRUCIBLE] HUM...
[PHONE RINGING]
[CRUCIBLE] JUST A MINUTE, LOVE, JUST A MINUTE.
[ROSE] [ELECTRONIC VOICE]
DONA VERÔNICA ON LINE TWO.
[CRUCIBLE] OH MY GOD.
HELLO? LOVE?
[VERÔNICA] WHAT'S UP, CADINHO?
BAGS READY FOR THE MALDIVES?
[VERÔNICA] WHAT DO YOU MEAN THE SECRETARY MADE A MISTAKE? CARLOS EDUARDO,
ARE YOU CRAZY? SPENDING NEW YEAR'S EVE IN RIO? LOVE, NO WAY!
[CADINHO] HEY, VERÔNICA, YOU HAVEN'T BEEN READING THE NEWSPAPERS, HAVE YOU?
THERE WILL BE THE MILLENNIUM BUG. THE PLANE WILL CRASH, THERE WILL BE FIRE
AT THE AIRPORT. NO, I KNOW WE AGREED, LOVE,
BUT I CHANGED MY MIND. IT'S FOR OUR FAMILY'S SAFETY,
UNDERSTAND? THINK CAREFULLY, LOOK, WE RENT, LIKE THIS,
A PRESIDENTIAL SUITE IN THE LUXURY HOTEL, CALL YOUR FRIENDS,
SEE THE FIREWORKS UP THERE. HUH? THINK ABOUT IT.
WAIT, WAIT, JUST A MINUTE,
LOVE, JUST... I HAVE TO SIGN SOME PAPERS HERE.
[CALENDAR] HELLO, NONO? DONE. SURE, I'LL BOOK A HOTEL,
LEAVE IT TO ME. IT'S GOING TO BE BEAUTIFUL, SEE? I LOVE YOU TOO, LOVE.
O... LOOK, DON'T FORGET TO GIVE THEM THE SYRUP I BOUGHT
FOR TOMÁS, OK? A KISS. I LOVE YOU TOO, NONO.
[CRUITING] VERÔ, THINK WITH LOVE, LOVE.
YES, IT'S GOING TO BE BEAUTIFUL. WE'LL SPEND NEW YEAR'S EVE IN BRAZIL
WITH OUR FRIENDS, OK? WE'LL TALK LATER.
ME, ME... WE'LL TALK LATER, I LOVE YOU, I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
BYE, BYE, BYE. JIMMY, YOU RESERVE
ALL THIS FOR ME.
[JIMMY] WAIT, ARE YOU SURE?
THAT YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TWO PARTIES WITH YOUR TWO WIVES
IN THE SAME HOTEL? HOLY SHIT, HOLY SHIT, YOU'RE GOING TO DIE FROM THIS.
[CRUITLING] YES, YES. I'M EXHAUSTED,
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE. TWO WOMEN, TWO FAMILIES.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I NEED?
[JIMMY] SOME ALONE TIME?
[CRUCIBLE] NO, A LOVER.
[ALEXIA] [EXTENDED] OH MY GOD IN HEAVEN,
WHAT IS THIS GUY DOING HERE?
[ALEXIA] HELLO?
[CADINHO] HI, ALEXIA? THIS IS CARLOS EDUARDO,
THAT GUY FROM THE OTHER NIGHT, FROM THE BAR...
[ALEXIA] I KNOW, I SEE YOU HERE ON THE INTERCOM.
[CRUCIBLE] AH! [LAUGHTER]
[CRUITLING] HI, HOW ARE YOU?
[THROAT CLEARING] WELL, I WAS PASSING BY HERE AND I THOUGHT,
SUDDENLY, I DON'T KNOW, PAY A VISIT, GO UP THERE,
HAVE A LITTLE COFFEE, RIGHT?
[ALEXIA] LISTEN, CARLOS EDUARDO, RIGHT?
I'M GOING TO BE VERY HONEST WITH YOU, CAFEZINHO
THAT WE BOTH HAD TO TAKE, WE ALREADY TOOK IT THAT NIGHT.
[CRUCIBLE] HOW?
[ALEXIA] YES, I AM A VERY INDEPENDENT WOMAN,
COMPLETELY DETACHED, AND, HONESTLY,
I DON'T USUALLY HAVE SEX TWICE WITH THE SAME MAN.
THE LAST THING I WANT IN MY LIFE,
IT'S A COMMITMENT, UNDERSTAND?
[CADINHO] I KNOW, BUT LOOK, IT'S EXACTLY WHAT I WANT.
LOOK, I... I SWEAR TO YOU, I WILL NOT GET INVOLVED EITHER.
I... I JUST WANT... IT'S JUST SEX, THAT'S ALL, UNDERSTAND?
I SWEAR, IT'S JUST SEX, OK? ALEXIA, ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
LOOK, LOOK, I STAY THERE FOR 15 MINUTES AND YOU THROW ME OUT,
NO COMMITMENT. ALEXIA! It's...
♪GOD PROTECT ME FROM YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
♪GOD HELP ME FROM YOUR ANGER♪
♪GOD IMMUNIZES ME FROM YOUR POISON♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR END♪
♪GOD PROTECT ME FROM YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
♪GOD HELP ME FROM YOUR ANGER♪
♪GOD IMMUNIZES ME FROM YOUR POISON♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR END♪
♪GOD GOD GO WITH ME♪
♪GOD SUPPORT ME♪
♪GOD LIFT ME UP♪
♪GOD GIVE ME STRENGTH♪
♪GOD FORGIVE ME FOR WANTING TO♪
♪GOD SAVE ME♪
♪AND KEEP IT FROM YOU♪
♪GOD GOD GO WITH ME♪
♪GOD SUPPORT ME♪
♪GOD LIFT ME UP♪
♪GOD GIVE ME STRENGTH♪
♪GOD FORGIVE ME FOR WANTING TO♪
♪GOD SAVE ME AND♪
♪AND KEEP IT FROM YOU♪
[DOOR CLOSE]
[CAR ENGINE]
♪GOD FORGIVE ME FOR WANTING TO♪
♪GOD SAVE ME♪
♪AND KEEP IT FROM YOU♪
♪GOD FORBID ME♪
♪KEEP IT FROM YOU♪
[SILENCE]
[WOMAN] TAKE YOUR BREATH IN YOUR BELLY. THAT'S IT...
[KNOCKING ON GLASS]
[WOMAN] THIS, INSPIRING...
[ALEXIA] [WHISPERING] WHAT IS THIS?
[CADINHO] WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
[ALEXIA] WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
[CRUCIBLE] ARE YOU PREGNANT?
[ALEXIA] [WHISPERING]
PSYCHOPATH,
YOU'RE FOLLOWING ME, I'M GOING TO CALL THE POLICE.
[CALMIN] ANSWER, ARE YOU PREGNANT?
[ALEXIA] "SHUT UP!" SHUT UP! I HAVE NO BUSINESS TO TALK ABOUT
FROM MY LIFE TO YOU. THAT'S ALL THAT'S MISSING NOW,
I TALK ABOUT MY LIFE TO YOU!
[CALENDAR] A MONTH AGO, I WENT TO BED WITH A WOMAN
AND NOW I FIND OUT SHE'S PREGNANT.
[ALEXIA] WHO'S PREGNANT?
[WHISPERING] I'M NOT PREGNANT.
[CADINHO] WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE THEN?
[ALEXIA] IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS!
GET OUT OF HERE, PREGO, GET OUT OF HERE!
[CRUCIBLE] AH... SWEAR ON YOUR SON'S LIFE
WHAT'S NOT IN YOUR BELLY?
[ALEXIA] I HAVE NOTHING, I HAVE NO CHILDREN
HERE IN MY BELLY, SO I WON'T HAVE TO DO IT
NO OATH, OK? NOW, DO ME A FAVOR?
OH, BUT WHY AM I TALKING ABOUT THESE THINGS TO YOU...
[CRUCIBLE] LOOK, BECAUSE... IF, BY CHANCE,
IF YOU WERE PREGNANT WITH ME, YOU WOULD NEED TO KNOW
FROM A HEREDITARY GENETIC DISEASE IN MY FAMILY...
A HORRIBLE THING.
[SIGH] WHEW, BUT SINCE YOU'RE NOT PREGNANT WITH ME
NOT FROM ANYONE, THANKS, THEN, BIG KISS.
[STEPS]
[ALEXIA] CRUCIBLE... CRUCIBLE!
CRUCIBLE... CRUCIBLE. FOR.
WAIT FOR ME, LISTEN. WHAT IS THIS STORY ABOUT ILLNESS?
YOU EVEN SAID YOU WERE A ROWING CHAMPION AT COLLEGE.
[CADINHO] ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT ME NOW?
[ALEXIA] NO, I DON'T GIVE A FUCK ABOUT YOU.
OH MY GOD, IT'S A CONGENITAL HEART PROBLEM,
RIGHT, TRUE?
[CRUCIBLE] IT STARTS IN THE HEART, BUT THEN IT SPREADS
IN THE WHOLE BODY.
[ALEXIA] I KNEW IT. [SIGH] OH MY GOD, I KNEW IT,
IT CAN ONLY BE PUNISHMENT, MY GOD IN HEAVEN. TELL ME THE TRUTH,
THIS STORY ABOUT THE DISEASE. SPEAKS. IS IT TRUE?
[CRUITLING] OK. THAT'S A LIE.
[ALEXIA] AH... LIAR! YOU'RE A SCOUNDREL!
[CRUCIBLE] AND YOU? AND YOU? YOU... YOU'RE WORSE THAN
A MAN HUNTER, YOU'RE A... A SEMEN COLLECTOR,
IT'S NOT THAT?
[ALEXIA] I DIDN'T WANT ANYTHING
LIKE YOU.
[CRUCIBLE] WELL, NO,
JUST HAVE A CHILD WITH ME, RIGHT?
[ALEXIA] YOU WERE NOT EVEN SUPPOSED TO KNOW.
[CADINHO] NOW I KNOW, SO WHAT?
♪Ouch Ouch, Ouch Ouch, Ouch Ouch♪
♪THIS IS HOW YOU KILL DADDY♪
♪Ouch, Ouch Ouch♪
♪WHAT A DELICIOUS MOUTH♪
♪I WANT MORE♪
♪Ouch Ouch, Ouch Ouch, Ouch Ouch♪
♪THIS IS HOW YOU KILL DADDY♪
♪Ouch, Ouch Ouch♪
♪YOU SMELL SO GOOD♪
[TYPHOON] MOTHER, LOOK HERE, I WANT THE WHOLE FAMILY
FROM MONALISA BE TREATED WELL, UNDERSTAND?
[MURICY] SURE, IMAGINE.
[TYPHOON] IS IT CLEAR?
[MURICY] SUPER, IMAGINE.
[MONALISA] [LAUGHTER] DONA MURICY, TRY A SMALL PIE HERE
WHAT I DID, PROVE IT HERE.
[MURICY] BUT CALM DOWN, YOU SIT DOWN, TALK TO PEOPLE.
MY SON HIRED WAITERS TO SERVE.
[MONALISA] BUT I CAN'T STAY STILL,
I GET NERVOUS.
[IVANA] YOU CAN GET USED TO IT, HUH, MONALISA.
NOW YOU WILL HAVE THE LIFE OF A MADAME.
[MONALISA] IMAGINE... THEN, YOU KNOW THE DAY I WILL BE A MADAME,
PEOPLE? I WILL NEVER BE A MADAME. NEVER! WHO WEEDED IT?
IN THE FARM IN PARAÍBA, YOU CANNOT STILL SIT AND GET MOLD
ON THE COUCH, NO, I LIKE IT.
[MURICY] IS IT TRUE THAT YOU GUYS UP IN THE NORTHEAST EAT LIZARDS?
[LELECO] OH, BUT STOP PICKING, MURICY!
[MURICY] IT'S NOT A PISS, IT'S THE TRUTH.
[DÉA] [STUTTERING] LOOK HERE, DONA MURICY. WE STILL HAVEN'T
YOU ATE A CALIPER, DIDN'T YOU SEE? BUT YOU KNOW THAT A FRIED ANT IS A FRIED ANT,
MY DAUGHTER, IT COULD BE A PITEL.
[IVANA] OMG!
[MURICY] SO, SEE? DIDN'T I TELL YOU? YES... I KNEW IT
YOU EAT LITTLE ANIMALS THERE.
[MONALISA] [CLEARING]
[CARMINHA] IF SOMEONE FALLS HERE IT'S SURE DEATH.
[URBAN AMBIENCE]
[CARMINHA] OH!
[MAX] MAN, STOP IT,
FOR GOD'S SAKE...
[CARMINHA] EXCELLENT SCENARIO,
MAX, EXCELLENT.
[MAX] YES, BUT YOU'RE GOING TO EXAGGERATE DOING THAT SCENE AGAIN,
THEN I'LL REALLY FALL, I REALLY WANT TO SEE.
[CARMINHA] LEAVE IT TO ME... LEAVE IT TO ME, ONE TIME OR THEN
PARAIBADA MUST ALREADY BE ALL THERE AT THE TUFÃO HOUSE.
[MAX] FOR ME YOU'RE PLAYING LIKE A CRAZY GUY AND TAKING RISKS
THAT MONEY THAT THE TYPHOON WAS GOING TO GIVE YOU...
[CARMINHA] THOSE WHO WANTS MORE FROM LIFE HAVE TO TAKE RISKS, MAX,
WHAT'S THIS? LEARN TO DREAM BIG, MAN!
NOW, GET READY. GET READY FOR THE ACTING SHOW.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TALK]
[DÉA] LOOK... LOOK WHAT I BROUGHT. LOOK HERE. MONALISA,
HERE IS THE VEIL YOUR GRANDMOTHER WORN AT HER WEDDING
AND THAT YOU WILL USE IN YOURS.
[TALK]
[LELECO] LOOK HERE, OH DONA DÉA, THIS WEDDING IS GOING TO BE
FROM BALACOBACO! BECAUSE, LOOK, THERE WILL BE A RAIN OF PETALS
IN PINK, BUFFET FOR 500 PEOPLE AND SHOW WITH A WELL-KNOWN SINGER.
[MONALISA] GUYS, WHAT A BEAUTIFUL THING! ALL EMBROIDERED, LOOK!
OH, AUNT, THANK YOU.
[IVANA] SLOW DOWN WITH THE SANDOR, HUH, DADDY, BECAUSE OF MONEY
YOU DON'T ACCEPT DISREGARD, HUH!
[LELECO] OH, IVANA IS A TIGHT FIST, THAT ONE IS IN CONTROL
THE FAMILY MONEY.
[MURICY] DOES IT AND DOES IT VERY WELL, IF IT WERE NOT FOR HER TO CONTROL IT
THE FAMILY'S MONEY, TUFÃO WASN'T DOING SO WELL
HOW IS HE TODAY, RIGHT, SONY?
[MONALISA] LOOK, YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK, DONA MURICY, HONESTLY,
700 PEOPLE IS A LOT OF PEOPLE, I DON'T EVEN KNOW 700 PEOPLE!
[TALK]
[MURICY] YOU DON'T KNOW, MY LOVE, BUT LOOK,
THERE IS THE DIVINO BOARD, THERE IS THE CLUB, THERE ARE PEOPLE FROM THE NEIGHBORHOOD,
JUST THEN IT GAVE ABOUT 300
PEOPLE.
[IVANA] AND DO THESE PEOPLE, BY CHANCE, CALL YOU FOR SOMETHING, MOTHER?
[MURICY] THEY ARE VERY NICE TO ME, IVANA!
[IVANA] OH, MOM, A BUNCH OF ASSHOLE, RIGHT?
JUST BECAUSE YOU BECAME THE FAMOUS PLAYER'S MOTHER.
[MURICY] DO YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT YOUR LIFE STOP PUTTING ME IN FULL
DOWN? WHAT'S THIS, DEAR? I HAVE MY OWN CHARISMA
GUYS.
[IVANA] AH, THESE PEOPLE DIDN'T EVEN LOOK AT YOUR FACE BEFORE
FOR HIM TO BECOME FAMOUS!
[MURICY] WHAT, MY DAUGHTER. I GO OUT ON THE STREET
IT'S AN EVENT.
[IVANA] I'M WITH MONALISA,
200 PEOPLE IS A GOOD SIZE!
[MONALISA] PEOPLE, PEOPLE, LET ME SAY SOMETHING,
QUICKLY, I WANTED TO RAISE A TOAST! EVERYONE HERE WITH ME,
A TOAST!
[TALK]
[MONALISA] [SHOUTING] WAITER!
[MONALISA] HERE, TAKE THESE TWO, I'M MISSING MINE.
[LELECO] GO ON.
[TYPHOON] GIVE ME ONE.
[LELECO] GAVE.
[MONALISA] I WANTED TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT
I WANT TO SAY A FEW WORDS TOO. IT'S... EVERYONE
YOU KNOW THAT MY ENGAGEMENT WITH TYPHOON TOOK A LONG TIME TO COME OUT.
[TALK]
[MONALISA] HE'S IN EUROPE, ME HERE, WE HAD TO HAVE
PATIENCE. [LAUGHTER] RIGHT, BUT I MEAN THAT...
[MONALISA] IT WAS WORTH THE WAIT.
[OLENKA] MY GOD, IT'S LOVE, MY PEOPLE!
[LAUGHTER]
[MONALISA] AND TODAY IS A VERY SPECIAL MOMENT
IN MY LIFE,
AND I HAVE SOME VERY IMPORTANT NEWS TO GIVE. [LAUGHTER]
[TALK]
[JANAÍNA] YOUR TYPHOON, YOUR TYPHOON, IT'S...
IT'S A GIRL NAME CARMINHA ON THE PHONE.
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA? ASK HER TO CALL YOU IN A LITTLE WHILE.
[JANAÍNA] NO, NO. SHE SAID IT WAS URGENT AND
IT SEEMS LIKE SHE'S DESPERATE.
[MONALISA] IT'S NOT THAT YOU TALK TO ME
"LEAVE IT",
I WANT TO FIND THE WORD OF HEIGHT...
[TYPHOON] IT'S... GUYS, I... I'LL GO OVER THERE FOR A MOMENT
AND I'LL BE BACK.
[MONALISA] BUT WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
NOW?
[TYPHOON] I WILL ONLY SOLVE ONE
LITTLE BUSINESS. IT'S NOTHING, NO. IT'S NOTHING, NO.
OH!... CLOSE IT.
[WOMAN] WHAT'S WRONG?
[MONALISA] I DON'T KNOW.
[TALK]
[MONALISA] AS I SAID,
WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT A LITTLE LONGER.
[TALK]
[TYPHOON] HI, YOU CAN TALK.
[CARMINHA] TYPHOON, SORRY TO BOTHER YOU.
I'M BOTHERING YOU, AREN'T I?
[TYPHOON] CAN'T WE TALK ANOTHER TIME?
[CARMINHA] [CLEAR VOICE] NO, I DON'T WANT TO TAKE UP YOUR TIME,
NO. I'M JUST CALLING YOU
TO TELL YOU THAT YOU ARE A WONDERFUL PERSON,
A BEAUTIFUL PERSON.
LATELY, FROM THE THINGS THAT HAPPENED TO ME,
YOU WERE THE BEST OF THEM.
I'M CALLING YOU TO SAY GOODBYE.
[TYPHOON] SAY GOODBYE? WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[CARMINHA] [CLUTTERED VOICE] IT DOESN'T MATTER,
I DON'T WANT TO TAKE UP YOUR TIME ANYMORE, YOU'RE FORGIVE, OK?
[TYPHOON] WAIT, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] I LOST CONTROL,
I'M COMPLETELY OUT OF CONTROL.
WITHOUT MY GENESUS, I LOST MY WAY. OH!
[CRYING]
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
I CAN'T STAND THE PAIN, MY GOD.
[CRYING]
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] MY WILL...
IT'S DOING... CRAZY.
[TYPHOON] NO, WAIT, I'M COMING THERE.
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] NO NEED.
[TYPHOON] I'M COMING. DON'T DO ANYTHING UNTIL I ARRIVE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] THE IDIOT IS COMING HERE.
[APPLAUSE]
[MAX] [SLOWLY]
SENSATIONAL.
[CARMINHA] YOU ALREADY KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO DO, DON'T YOU?
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[LELECO] LISTEN HERE, TYPHOON, I...
[MURICY] WHAT IS THIS?
[LELECO] I DON'T KNOW, I WANT TO KNOW. HE WENT TO THE BATHROOM,
AND THAT?
[WOMAN] HE SHOULD HAVE COME BACK BY NOW.
[MONALISA] OH MY GOD.
[SHOUTING] HEY JANAINA! JANAINA, GUYS, WHERE'S MY FIANCÉ?
YOU DISAPPEARED WITH HIM. FOR THE LOVE OF GOD.
[JANAÍNA] HEY YOUR TYPHOON IS OUT.
[MONALISA] HOW DID YOU LEAVE? HE DIDN'T TELL ME ANYTHING.
[JANAÍNA] HE ASKED ME TO LET YOU KNOW THAT HE CAME DOWN HERE
BELOW TO BUY A WINE, BECAUSE WINE
THE THING HE OPENED WAS VINEGAR.
[IVANA] OH, THIS IS STRANGE, GUYS.
[WOMAN] IT SEEMS TO ME THAT YOUR FIANCE
HE'S PREPARING A SURPRISE FOR YOU, DAUGHTER.
[MONALISA] NO, AUNT, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD.
OK... OK, SURPRISE,
I'VE BEEN HAVING A LOT OF SURPRISES LATELY.
[MURICY] DIDN'T YOU SAY YOU WERE GOING TO SAY SOMETHING IMPORTANT?
KEEP TALKING ABOUT IT FOR NOW.
[MONALISA] NO, NOTHING, NOTHING.
[LELECO] THAT "NOTHING, NOTHING. NOTHING, NOTHING". HELLO, GOOD STUFF?
[MONALISA] AH, OH... LET IT, LET THE TYPHOON COME
WHAT I SAY, RIGHT? BETTER.
IN THE MEANTIME, LET'S DRINK THIS CHAMPAGNE,
YOU KNOW, BEFORE IT GETS HOT.
[OLENKA] BECAUSE I CAN'T STAY, YOU KNOW, RIGHT?
[IVANA] OH NO, OLENKA.
[OLENKA] I HAVE A SCHEME THERE. I'M GOING TO SEE THE BOYS, OK?
[IVANA] OH, NO.
[OLENKA] THANK YOU. BYE, MY PEOPLE, LOOK, KISSES!
[IVANA] GET OUT OF THE FRONT!
[OLENKA] NO, I'LL GO THIS WAY, IT'S FASTER, GUYS.
[MAN] OK, BYE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA.
[CARMINHA] YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE COME HERE, GO AWAY!
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA, CALM DOWN. LET'S TALK.
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] ON TOP OF THAT I'M A COWARD.
I SHOULD HAVE ENDED THIS A LONG TIME AGO!
[TYPHOON] NO, NO, NO...
[CARMINHA] [SCREAM]
[TYPHOON] YOU'RE NOT A COWARD,
YOU WANT TO LIVE, CARMINHA!
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] I CAN'T DO IT.
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA, YOU WANT TO LIVE.
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] YOU'RE WRONG,
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE, I WANT TO DIE.
I WANT TO END THIS PAIN, MY GOD.
[TYPHOON] THIS PAIN WILL PASS, CARMINHA. THIS PAIN WILL PASS!
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] HOW? HOW?
[TYPHOON] LOOK AT ME, LOOK AT ME.
[CRYING]
[TYPHOON] I WILL HELP YOU. LOOK AT ME,
GIVE ME YOUR HAND, GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] GIVE ME YOUR HAND. GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
[CARMINHA] WHAT FOR?
[VOICE OVERWHELMED] THE WORLD DOESN'T NEED A PERSON LIKE ME.
I AM USELESS.
[TYPHOON] DON'T SPEAK... YOU'RE A WONDERFUL PERSON, CARMINHA.
DON'T SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
[CARMINHA] YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
[TYPHOON] FROM WHAT LITTLE I KNOW, I KNOW YOUR QUALITIES,
YOU ARE A WOMAN OF INTEGRITY, YOU ARE A FAMILY WOMAN,
YOU WERE A GOOD WIFE, YOU... YOU ARE SMART,
YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL, YOU ARE LOVING, YOU HAVE LIFE
ENTIRELY AHEAD OF YOU. YOU WILL REBUILD YOUR LIFE
AND I WILL HELP YOU. GIVE ME YOUR HAND. GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
[CARMINHA] [GRUNT]
[TYPHOON] GIVE, GIVE, GIVE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] [CRYING] SORRY, SORRY.
[CRYING]
[CARMINHA] I'M SORRY.
[TYPHOON] ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
[MONALISA] JESUS ​​IN HEAVEN, WHERE DID THE TYPHOON GO? IT'S BEEN AN HOUR
AND HALF THAT MAN LEFT AND DOESN'T COME BACK TO ME WITH THAT WINE.
[MURICY] AN IMPORTANT PERSON LIKE MY SON, YOU KNOW,
IN HIS POSITION, HE SHOULD ALWAYS WALK WITH PRIVATE SECURITY,
HE WILL ALWAYS BE A TARGET OF KIDNAPPING, THAT'S THE TRUTH.
[LELECO] TURN THAT MOUTH AWAY!
[MURICY] I WON'T COME!
THE MOUTH IS MINE,
I GO WHEREVER I WANT!
[IVANA] CALM DOWN, GUYS! STOP IT, YOU MUST HAVE A FLAT TIRE,
ALREADY, ALREADY HE'S THERE.
[PHONE RINGING]
[TALK]
[IVANA] OH, IT MUST BE HIM.
[MONALISA] HELLO?
[MURICY] IS IT THE TYPHOON?
[MAX] PLEASE, IS MR. JORGE ARAÚJO TUFÃO HERE?
[MONALISA] NO, HE'S NOT THERE, HE'S...
WHAT HAPPENED? THIS IS HIS BRIDE SPEAKING.
[MAX] THIS IS MAJOR UBIRATAN SILVEIRA SPEAKING HERE.
WE RECORD AN OCCURRENCE HERE,
A VEHICLE WITH THE PLATE LNE-3152 MUST BELONG TO YOUR FIANCÉ.
HERE ON DOMINGOS DE ALBUQUERQUE STREET, IN FRONT OF
TO NUMBER 736, HERE IN GUADELOUPE.
[MONALISA] IN GUADELOUPE? BUT WHAT HAPPENED
WITH HIS CAR?
[MAX] IN FACT, IT WAS NOTHING SERIOUS, IT WAS AN ATTEMPT
THEFT, THEY BROKEN THE SIDE GLASS ON THE DRIVER'S SIDE,
THAT'S IT.
[MONALISA] OK, BUT... WHAT ABOUT MY FIANCÉ? JORGE TUFÃO, PLAYER,
DO YOU KNOW HIM? IS HE THERE?
OK, THANK YOU.
[TALK]
[LELECO] DID YOU CRASH YOUR CAR?
[MONALISA] NO, NO, NOTHING LIKE THAT.
IT WAS AND... HIS CAR WAS SUFFERED BY AN ATTEMPTED ROBBERY
AND IT WAS FOUND IN GUADELOUPE. NOW I WANT TO KNOW,
WHAT HAPPENED? TYPHOON CAME DOWN JUST TO BUY
WINE, WHAT IS HIS CAR DOING IN GUADELOUPE?
[MURICY] IN GUADALUPE? THEY TOOK MY SON! THEY KIDNAPPED HIM
MY SON! IVANA, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, YOU WILL PAY WHAT THEY
ASK FOR RESCUE...
[TALK]
[MONALISA] IT'S IN GUADALUPE THE APARTMENT THAT TYPHOON BOUGHT
AND HE LOANED IT TO THAT WIDOW, IT'S THERE, IT'S THERE. OH... OH JANAÍNA!
[JANAINA] HERE.
[MURICY] WHICH WIDOW IS THIS?
[MONALISA] BY CHANCE, IT WAS SOMEONE CERTAINLY CARMINHA
WHO CALLED TYPHOON WHEN HE LEFT?
[JANAINA] OH...
[MONALISA] SPEAK UP, WOMAN!
WAS IT CARMINHA?
[JANAINA] IT WAS.
[MONALISA] CARMINHA...
[LELECO] WHO IS THIS WOMAN? WHO IS THIS WOMAN?
[WOMAN] WAIT, MONALISA, I'M GOING WITH YOU.
[IVANA] WAIT, I'M GOING TOO, WAIT...
[MURICY] PEOPLE, BUT WHO IS CARMINHA?
[IVANA] AND I KNOW, MOTHER?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[SHATTERING GLASS]
[STEPS]
[TYPHOON] TAKE THIS SUGAR WATER AND THIS SOOTHING DRINKS,
YOU NEED TO SLEEP, REST.
[CARMINHA] I'M SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
I MESSED UP YOUR LIFE TODAY, DIDN'T I?
[TYPHOON] IT'S OK, IT WAS FOR A GOOD CAUSE.
[CARMINHA] YOU ARE A SAINT.
A PERSON WHO DOES WHAT YOU DID FOR A STRANGER,
FOR A POOR THING LIKE ME, HE CAN ONLY BE CALLED A SAINT.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] YOU WILL NEVER BE ALONE AGAIN,
YOU WILL HAVE ME BY YOUR SIDE FOREVER.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] WHO ARE YOU?
[TYPHOON] MONALISA.
[MONALISA] I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DID THIS TO ME AGAIN.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY PACE♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK IT♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪