[SILENCE]
[MONALISA] I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DID THIS TO ME AGAIN!
YOU BASTARD, SON OF A MARE!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, I DID NOTHING, I SWEAR.
I CAME HERE BECAUSE SHE WANTED TO KILL HERSELF.
[MONALISA] DO YOU WANT ME TO BELIEVE IN THIS AGAIN?
THE FIRST TIME YOU WENT TO BED WITH HER AND NOW WHY DIDN'T YOU?
WHY DIDN'T YOU WANT TO?
[TYPHOON] I SWEAR!
[SLAP]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] ALL MY RELATIVES IN MY HOUSE FOR OURS
ENGAGEMENT AND YOU HERE. WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU WANT TO HUMILIATE ME IN FRONT OF MY RELATIVES, IS THAT IT?
DO YOU WANT TO END MY RACE? MY GOD IN HEAVEN!
[CRYING] WHAT MAKES A PERSON DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
[CARMINHA] IT'S NOT THAT, PLEASE. I WAS DESPERATE,
THE TYPHOON CAME TO MY RESCUE, IT WAS A HUMANITARIAN GESTURE, THAT'S ALL.
[MONALISA] GOING TO BED WITH HIM WAS A HUMANITARIAN GESTURE
YOURS TOO?
[CARMINHA] PLEASE CALM DOWN,
I DON'T WANT TO CAUSE PROBLEMS FOR YOUR FIANCE.
HE DOESN'T DESERVE IT, YOUR GROOM IS A SAINT.
[MONALISA] AND SANTINHO THERE BY CHANCE HAS ALREADY TOLD YOU IT WAS HIM
WHO RAN OVER YOUR HUSBAND?
[TYPHOON] MONALISA.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] IS THIS TRUE, TYPHOON?
[TYPHOON] THIS IS NOT HAPPENING. THIS IS NOT HAPPENING.
HOW CAN YOU DO THIS TO ME?
[CARMINHA] MY GOD! SO IT'S TRUE? THAT'S WHY YOU'RE TO BLAME?
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA, I WAS GOING TO TELL YOU EVERYTHING. HUM.
[CARMINHA] YOU DIDN'T KNOW GENÉSIO, MY GOD IN HEAVEN!
YOU'VE BEEN LIING ALL THE TIME!
[TYPHOON] IT WAS... IT WAS... IT WAS THE ONLY WAY I FOUND
TO GET CLOSER TO YOU.
[MONALISA] GOODBYE, TYPHOON.
[TYPHOON] MONALISA!
[MONALISA] I'M TAKING IT OFF
MY FIELD TEAM, STAY THERE, BECAUSE YOU STILL HAVE A LOT
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT WITH YOUR FRIEND.
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, MONALISA!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] GOD!
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA...
[CARMINHA] OH, NO.
[TYPHOON] GENÉSIO THREW HIMSELF
IN FRONT OF MY CAR, I WASN'T TO BLAME.
I CALLED THE AMBULANCE, BUT HE WAS ALREADY DEAD.
[CARMINHA] YOU CALLED THE AMBULANCE, YES,
YOU CALLED THE AMBULANCE, BUT THEN YOU RAN AWAY.
[TYPHOON] I... I CALLED THE AMBULANCE,
BUT HE WAS ALREADY DEAD, I HAD NOTHING TO DO THERE.
[CARMINHA] GET OUT OF HERE!
GET OUT OF HERE!
GO AFTER YOUR BRIDE!
[TYPHOON] IF YOU WANT TO HAND ME OVER TO THE POLICE,
I'LL UNDERSTAND, HUH?
[CARMINHA] GET OUT OF HERE.
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA, LISTEN TO ME...
[CARMINHA] GET OUT!
[CLUTTERED VOICE] GET OUT! GET OUT! GET OUT!
[CRYING]
[CARMINHA] [CLUTTERED VOICE] GET OUT!
GET OUT!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CRYING]
[MONALISA] STOP, STOP.
[MONALISA] [VOICE OVERWHELMED] STOP THERE. LET'S GO.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] [SCREAMING] MONALISA!
[TIRE SINGING]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LAUGHTER]
[CARMINHA] THE BOSS IS STILL TIED TO ME.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THE DONKEY FROM PARAÍBA ENDED UP WITH
TO SAY HERE, THE HEIGHT OF PERFECTION.
[MAX] WHAT?
[CARMINHA] THAT THE TYPHOON RAN OVER
GENÉSIO, HAS DELIVERED THE GROOM, MY LOVE.
[MAX] [GASP] WHAT A SHACK.
[CARMINHA] YOU NEEDED TO SEE
MY FACE. "WHAT? YOU CALLED AN AMBULANCE,
BUT THEN HE RAN AWAY? GO AWAY FROM HERE, PLEASE,
GET OUT OF HERE". [MOANS] MY LOVE...
THE ENGAGEMENT IS OVER, DIDN'T I SAY IT WOULD WORK OUT?
[MAX] YES, STOP IT, CARMINHA,
NOBODY ENDS A RELATIONSHIP LIKE THIS, AFTER SO MANY YEARS,
BECAUSE OF A BUSINESS LIKE THAT, NO.
[CARMINHA] IT DOES END, STOP BEING NEGATIVE.
AFTERWARDS, WHO'S GOING TO GET A JERK LIKE THAT PARAÍBA,
HAVING A BIG WOMAN LIKE ME?
[MAX] YEAH, NOTHING, THERE. HUM. THAT WOMAN IS NOT ONE TO PLAY AROUND
OUT, NO, HUH, DUDE?
[CARMINHA] YES, ARE YOU GOING TO PROVOKE?
PROVOKE, GO. PROVOKE.
[MAX] I'M GOING TO PROVOKE YOU LIKE THIS,
OH, OK? LIKE THIS, OK? HUM?
[MURICY] SO THE ENGAGEMENT IS OVER, RIGHT, PEOPLE? IT'S OBVIOUS, RIGHT?
[LELECO] TURN YOUR MOUTH AWAY, MURICY, PLEASE.
MONALISA LIKES OUR SON, SHE'S A GOOD GIRL.
[IVANA] I'M WITH DAD. EVEN IF IT WERE NOT FOR HER,
MY BROTHER HADN'T GOT TO WHERE HE HAS.
[MURICY] THAT'S NOT TRUE.
[IVANA] OH, OF COURSE IT IS, MOTHER,
WHY LIE? NOBODY HERE IN YOUR HOUSE EVER BELIEVED IT
THAT TYPHOON WOULD HAVE A CAREER IN FOOTBALL, SHE WOULDN'T,
ALWAYS BELIEVED, SUPPORTED, INCLUDING,
YOU WAITED FOR YEARS FOR HIM TO COME BACK FROM EUROPE, DIDN'T YOU?
[MURICY] DO YOU WANT TO TELL YOUR DAUGHTER TO STOP ANNOYING ME?
[LELECO] WELL, IT'S THE PURE TRUTH.
[MURICY] OH REALLY? IT'S VERY EASY FOR YOU TO SAY THAT, RIGHT?
IT'S VERY EASY. WHILE HE WAS THERE IN THE BAR DRINKING THE BEER
HIM, PLAYING POOL, I... I WAS SUPPORTING THE FAMILY
OVER THERE IN THE CENTRAL, SELLING UMBRELLAS UNDERNEATH
FROM A TENT. IF IT WASN'T FOR ME, TYPHOON WOULD HAVE DIED!
[LELECO] THIS IS ALSO THE PURE TRUTH.
[MURICY] OH WELL, I'M GLAD YOU RECOGNIZE IT.
[MONALISA] GRANDPA JUNO, COUSIN OSEIAS, AUNT DÉA, COME ON.
[DÉA] WHAT HAPPENED, MY DAUGHTER?
[MONALISA] MY ENGAGEMENT WITH TYPHOON IS OVER, COME ON!
[MURICY] DIDN'T I SAY? [LAUGHTER]
[MONALISA] ARE YOU HAPPY, DONA MURICY, THAT YOU
WON'T YOU HAVE TO SEE MY PARAÍBA FACE ANYMORE?
[LELECO] CALM DOWN, MONALISA, PLEASE CALM DOWN, YOU WON'T TAKE IT
NO ATTITUDE WITH A HOT HEAD.
[DÉA] I'VE GOT YOUR LELECO, QUIET, MY DAUGHTER!
[IVANA] YES, AT LEAST EXPLAIN WHAT HAPPENED!
[TYPHOON] MONALISA, I SWEAR ON MY SOUL IT DIDN'T HAPPEN
NOTHING WITH THAT WOMAN.
[LELECO] WHAT WOMAN?
[MONALISA] THE LITTLE WIDOW HE HAS AN AFFAIR WITH! COUSIN OSEIAS,
THIS GUY LEFT ME STRANDED HERE IN MY NIGHT
ENGAGED AND WENT TO BED WITH ANOTHER WOMAN!
[HOSEIAS] I'M GOING TO BEAT THIS GUY!
[TYPHOON] WAIT, OH ASSASSIN, WAIT.
[LELECO] JUST A MINUTE, JUST A MINUTE, LET'S NOT GO FOR IGNORANCE
NOT SO! MY SON, IS THAT TRUE?
[TYPHOON] VERY COMPLICATED STORY, FATHER.
I RUN OVER THIS WOMAN'S HUSBAND AND HE'S DEAD.
[MURICY] MY GOD, WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL US THIS?
FOR US, MY SON?
[TYPHOON] HE DIED IN MY ARMS, SAYING THIS GIRL'S NAME
WOMAN. I WANT TO HELP THIS WOMAN,
BECAUSE SHE IS A WIDOW BECAUSE OF ME.
[MONALISA] AND YOU NEEDED TO HAVE GONE TO BED WITH HER?
[TYPHOON] MY GOD IN HEAVEN, THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT, MONALISA,
I SAID IT WOULDN'T HAPPEN AGAIN. FOR THE LOVE OF GOD,
SHE... LOOK, SHE SAID SHE WAS GOING TO KILL HERSELF, THAT'S WHY
I WENT THERE, NOTHING HAPPENED!
[MONALISA] OK, AND YOU EXPECT ME TO BELIEVE THAT?
[TYPHOON] AND WHY DID YOU SAY THAT I KILLED HER HUSBAND?
[MURICY] DID YOU SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
MY GOD, BUT THIS WOMAN IS A TRAITOR.
[IVANA] NOW THIS WOMAN CAN SEND MY BROTHER TO JAIL.
[MONALISA] SORRY! [CRYING]
BUT IT'S BECAUSE I DIDN'T STOP TO
THOUGHT, I WAS OUT OF MY MIND.
BUT ANYWAY, IT'S OVER, TYPHOON!
[TYPHOON] IT'S NOT OVER. IT'S NOT OVER, WE'RE GOING TO
WE WILL STILL BE HAPPY, GET MARRIED,
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU, UNDERSTAND?
[MONALISA] DON'T GO, BECAUSE I DON'T LOVE YOU ANYMORE. [SNIFLE]
[TYPHOON] LIE.
[MONALISA] [SLOWLY] I DON'T LOVE YOU ANYMORE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] COME ON.
[MURICY] LET HER GO,
LET HER GO, GO AWAY, GO AWAY! THIS WOMAN IS A
TRAITOR, YOU DESERVE MUCH BETTER THAN THIS WOMAN.
[TYPHOON] MOM, SHUT UP, LET ME THINK.
[MURICY] NO, THINK ABOUT IT, THERE'S NO PROBLEM AT ALL, THINK ABOUT IT,
MY SON, GO THINK. THANK GOD!
[COUGH]
[LUCINDA] OH MY DAUGHTER.
[RITA] TAKE THIS, IT'S A SHOT AND A DROP FOR THE FLU, OK?
MOTHER LUCINDA? LOOK, IT'S LEMON, HONEY AND GARLIC BOX TEA.
[LUCINDA] OH MY GOD, BUT YOU REALLY ARE A GENIUS,
RIGHT, LISTEN HERE, DO YOU KNOW IF THERE'S FOOD FOR LUNCH?
[RITA] DON'T WORRY, MOMMY, YESTERDAY WE
I RAISED SOME MONEY FROM THE TRASH AND WE WENT TO SHOPPING. THE HOUSE IS FULL
OF FOOD. OH, I'LL EVEN MAKE THAT PIE YOU LIKE.
[LUCINDA] OH MY GOD, LOOK, BEFORE I COULDN'T
I WOULD NOT EVEN GET SICK OR THE HOUSE WOULD COME DOWN. YOU ARE MINE
CO-PILOT, SHE IS THE VICE-PRESIDENT OF THE FIRM. I OWE THIS TO
BATATA, RIGHT, HE'S THE ONE WHO INSISTED THAT YOU STAY HERE, DIDN'T HE?
[LAUGHTER]
[RITA] I'M GOING TO PREPARE THE PIE DOUGH, OK?
[LUCINDA] NO, YOU WON'T. TELL BETÂNIA THAT I SENT YOU.
SHE MAKES LUNCH, OK? TODAY IS SUNDAY... GO HAVE FUN
LITTLE, TAKE THE POTATO AND GO PLAY AROUND.
[RITA] BUT BETÂNIA DOESN'T KNOW HOW TO COOK.
[LUCINDA] [MOANING] AH, FORGET IT, THIS DOESN'T MAKE ANYTHING OF ANYTHING
IMPORTANCE. [LAUGHTER] YOU'RE REALLY TOO RESPONSIBLE,
HEIN, BUT REMEMBER ONE THING, WE NEED TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT
WHILE YOU'RE A CHILD, IT'S THE BEST PHASE OF YOUR LIFE AND IT GOES BY QUICKLY.
[LAUGHTER] GO ON, GET THE POTATO, GO HAVE FUN, GO, GO, GO
PLAY, GO PLAY... GIVE A KISS, KISS, KISS.
[POTATO] COME BACK HERE, I'LL GET YOU.
[RITA] YOU CAN'T CATCH ME, SLUG FACE.
[POTATO] COME BACK HERE. I'LL GET YOU.
[RITA] NO, YOU WON'T.
[POTATO] COME BACK HERE.
[RITA] YOU ARE TOO WEAK. OW.
[POTATO] I'LL GET YOU.
[RITA] NO, YOU WON'T.
[POTATO] NOW I'M GOING TO GET IT!
[RITA] IT WON'T GO. [LAUGHTER]
[RITA] CATCH ME.
[POTATO] OH YEAH? THEN YOU'LL SEE.
[RITA] [LAUGHTER]
[POTATO] GOT YOU!
[POTATO] OH, I GOT YOU. TICKLE.
[LAUGHTER]
[RITA] STOP, STOP, PLEASE, I'M TIRED.
[DEEP SIGH]
[RITA] WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[POTATO] LET'S JUMP THE WALL.
[POTATO] WOW!
[RITA] WOW.
[RITA] POOL BATH!
[POTATO] DARLING, I'M HERE!
[RITA] HI, DEAR! HOW WAS IT AT WORK?
[POTATO] IT WAS GREAT, I EVEN GOT PROMOTED.
[RITA] CONGRATULATIONS! OUR TWO SONS, RENATO AND EVARISTO,
YOU WILL BE VERY HAPPY!
[POTATO] AH! GOOD NIGHT, RENATO, GOOD NIGHT, EVARISTO.
[RITA] TODAY I PREPARED THAT SOUFFLÉ YOU LOVE.
[POTATO] OH! GREAT, DEAR. I HAVE AN APPETITE TODAY!
[POTATO] WOW, IT SMELLS DELICIOUS.
[RITA] TRY IT.
[POTATO] YUM, IT'S DELICIOUS, DEAR!
[POTATO] WHAT NOW? WHAT DOES THE HUSBAND SAY?
[RITA] NOW, THE HUSBAND SAYS:
"I WAS THINKING WE COULD SPEND THE HOLIDAYS WITH OUR
TWO SONS, RENATO AND EVARISTO, ON THE BEACH".
[POTATO] OK.
I WAS THINKING...
RITA.
[RITA] WHAT'S UP, BATATA, ARE YOU TIRED OF PLAYING?
[POTATO] WILL YOU MARRY ME?
[RITA] WHAT?
[POTATO] NOW IT'S NOT A JOKE ANYMORE, IT'S SERIOUS.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY PACE♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK IT♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[POTATO] ANSWER, RITA. DO YOU WANT TO MARRY ME?
[RITA] BUT CHILDREN CANNOT GET MARRIED.
[POTATO] YOU CAN. YOU CAN BECOME A GROOM.
[RITA] NOT EVEN A GROOM.
[POTATO] YOU CAN, YOU CAN. ANYONE CAN BECOME A GROOM.
JUST WAIT TO GROW UP TO GET MARRIED.
[RITA] OK then.
[POTATO] WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "SO ARE YOU"?
[RITA] I ACCEPT, I ACCEPT TO MARRY YOU.
[RITA] NOW YOU HAVE TO GIVE THE KISS.
[POTATO] AND I'M THE ONE WHO GIVES THAT KISS?
[RITA] YES, IT'S YOU.
[RITA] IS THIS HOW YOU KISS?
[POTATO] [STUTTERING] I... I DON'T KNOW. I'VE NEVER KISSED BEFORE.
[KISS SNAP]
[RITA] WE'RE GOING TO GET MARRIED, WE'RE GOING TO LIVE HAPPILY EVER AFTER...
WE WILL HAVE TWO CHILDREN WHO WILL BE NAMED RENATO AND EVARISTO.
[STEPS]
[WOMAN] MONALISA, CALM DOWN FOR A MINUTE AND LISTEN TO ME!
[MONALISA] OH AUNT, I'M TOO ANGRY TO BE ABLE TO STAND STILL,
KEEP TALKING WHILE I MOVE. WHERE'S MY BRUSH?
[WOMAN] HEY, COME TO RIO DE JANEIRO, GET A PLAYER
OF FOOTBALL AND WILL RETURN TO PARAÍBA WITH US DONE
A PAW'S PERCH? TYPHOON IS THE FATHER OF YOUR CHILD, YOU HAVE YOURS
SALON, YOUR BUSINESS IS HERE, YOUR PLACE IS HERE, GIRL!
[MONALISA] I FOUND IT... NO! I'M GOING TO PARAÍBA,
HE CHEATED ON ME! I'M GOING TO LEAVE AND RAISE MY CHILD ALONE!
[WOMAN] YOU WANT TO HUNT UNHAPPINESS, THAT'S IT,
MY DAUGHTER?
[STEPS]
[WOMAN] YOU EVEN HAVE THE RIGHT TO NOT WANT IT ANYMORE
THE TYPHOON, BUT WHAT ABOUT YOUR SON, GIRL? YOUR SON WILL NOT HAVE
THE RIGHT TO KNOW HIS FATHER? A RICH MAN
THAT CAN GIVE YOU EVERYTHING!
[MONALISA] WHAT FOR? WHAT FOR? FOR MURICY'S BITCH
SAY THAT I... THAT I GAVE THE BELLY BLOW?
MY DAUGHTER, I DON'T NEED THIS, LET THEM SWALLOW IT
THEIR MONEY. I AM STRONG, I AM NOT AFRAID OF WORK,
I WILL RAISE MY SON, HE WILL NOT LACK ANYTHING!
[OLENKA] WHAT IS THIS CONFUSION?
[HATES] MAKE ME... HELP ME SENSITIVELY
ON HER HEAD, PLEASE!
[MONALISA] NO, NO, NO, OLENKA, I'M LEAVING.
I HAVE NOTHING ELSE TO DO HERE.
[OLENKA] HOW NOT, MONALISA? HUH? AND YOUR WORK,
YOUR CLIENT? YOUR SALON IS YOUR LIFE,
ARE YOU GOING TO LEAVE AND LEAVE EVERYTHING YOU HAVE BUILT?
[MONALISA] I'M GOING AWAY WITH MY FAMILY, TO GO FAR AWAY
THIS FALSEHOOD. COME ON, PEOPLE. IMAGINE, A MAN WHO SAYS
WHO LOVES ME ONE DAY, THE NEXT DAY IS SLUTTING UP WITH THE WIDOW
OF A DECEASED MAN WHO HASN'T EVEN COOLED DOWN!
MY GOD, WHAT WORLD IS THIS?
KEEP THIS IN MIND. NOW THAT'S ENOUGH. THIS CONVERSATION IS OVER.
NOW I'M GOING TO PARAÍBA, I'M GOING TO COOL MY HEAD, I'LL SEE THERE
IF I COME BACK, IF I STAY, BUT, NOW, NOT EVEN IF THE WORLD
I'M GOING, COME ON. TURN AROUND, UNCLE, TURN AROUND.
COME. AUNT, GO FRONT, AUNT, GO FRONT.
[OLENKA] I'M GLAD YOU LIKED IT, MARI.
[MARI] OH, I LOVED IT, I LOVED IT, OLENKA.
[OLENKA] OK, BUT COME BACK BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO CUT THE TIPS, OK?
KISS, TAKE CARE, LOVE, BYE.
[TYPHOON] OLENKA! IS MONALISA THERE?
[OLENKA] CAME LATE, MY BROTHER, SHE LEFT WITH HER SUITCASE
AND GO TO THE BUS STATION. LEFT, GOT FUCKED UP, WENT TO PARAÍBA, OK?
[TYPHOON] HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN?
[OLENKA] OH, IT'S ABOUT TEN MINUTES.
YOU WOULD HAVE GOT HER HERE IN TEN MINUTES. LATE.
♪OUR LOVE KNOWS♪
♪WELL TO YOU♪
♪NEITHER THE SAME NOR DIFFERENT♪
♪IT'S NOT BEFORE OR AFTER♪
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪IT'S WHAT WE FEEL♪
♪NEITHER GUILTY OR INNOCENT♪
♪IN THIS STORY OF US TWO♪
♪OUR LOVE♪
♪IT'S NOT A WORK OF CHANCE♪
♪IT'S A PLAN DESIGNED♪
♪ SIMPLE THING TO UNDERSTAND ♪
[HATES] THINK ABOUT IT, MY LOVE, LET'S STAY!
YOU'LL REGRET LEAVING, I'M TELLING YOU!
[MONALISA] AUNT, ENOUGH! I'VE ALREADY DECIDED.
♪THAT MAKES US ONE BEING♪
♪THIS IS WHY I LIVE FOR YOU♪
♪FAR FROM YOU♪
♪MY HEART IS LOST♪
♪THE WORLD IS DIVIDED♪
♪BETWEEN WHAT WILL BE♪
♪AND WHAT HAS BEEN♪
♪THIS IS WHY I LIVE FOR YOU♪
♪FAR FROM YOU♪
♪MY HEART IS LOST♪
♪THE WORLD IS DIVIDED♪
♪BETWEEN WHAT WILL BE♪
♪AND WHAT HAS BEEN♪
♪THIS IS WHY I LIVE FOR YOU♪
♪I'M CALLING FOR YOU♪
♪BECAUSE NOBODY HAS THE RIGHT♪
♪TELL US WHAT IS PERFECT♪
♪IN THIS STORY♪
♪WHICH IS JUST FOR THE TWO OF US♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪MY PLACE♪
♪IT'S A SMILE, IT'S PEACE AND PLEASURE♪
♪YOUR NAME IS SWEET TO SAY♪
♪IT'S DIVINE, LA, LAIÁ♪
[CARMINHA] YOU?
[TYPHOON] AM I GETTING IN THE WAY?
[CARMINHA] COME IN.
[TYPHOON] EXCUSE ME.
[STEPS]
[DOOR CLOSE]
[CARMINHA] I JUST MADE SOME COFFEE, DO YOU WANT SOME?
[TYPHOON] NO THANKS. CAN I SIT DOWN?
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE, SIT DOWN, IT'S YOUR HOUSE. IN FACT, YOURS.
[TYPHOON] [SIGH] HOW ARE YOU
ADAPTING TO THE NEW APARTMENT?
[CARMINHA] THE APARTMENT IS GREAT. I FEEL
IT'S GETTING WORSE AND WORSE TO BE LIVING ON FAVOR,
IN AN APARTMENT LOANED BY YOU.
[TYPHOON] DON'T SAY THAT, DON'T SAY THAT,
BECAUSE IT WILL BE... IT WILL BE A FAVOR THAT YOU
YOU'RE MAKING ME ACCEPT THIS APARTMENT.
I'M SO EMBARRASSED BECAUSE I LIED TO YOU,
I HAVE NEVER DONE THIS IN MY LIFE. NOW LOOK,
I'LL TELL YOU, MY LIE HAD A LITTLE TRUTH IN IT,
DO YOU KNOW WHY? BECAUSE GENÉSIO DIED
IN MY ARMS SPEAKING YOUR NAME.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] DIED...
SAYING MY NAME?
[TYPHOON] IT IS, AND I KNOW THAT IT
I WANTED TO TELL ME SOMETHING ABOUT YOU,
BUT HE COULDN'T COMPLETE THE SENTENCE.
BUT I'M SURE HE WOULD ASK ME TO TAKE CARE OF YOU.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] I KNOW THAT GENÉSIO'S DEATH WAS NOT YOUR FAULT,
I KNOW YOU CALLED THE AMBULANCE.
[TYPHOON] BUT I... I CALLED THE AMBULANCE,
BUT HE WAS ALREADY DEAD, I WAS SCARED, I RUN AWAY,
BECAUSE I THOUGHT THIS COULD MAKE MY LIFE VERY COMPLICATED.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT A FAMOUS PERSON'S LIFE IS LIKE.
[CARMINHA] NO, NO, YOU DON'T NEED TO EXPLAIN, NO,
I KNOW THAT GENÉSIO WAS REALLY DRUNK, DISCONNECTED,
I WAS ALWAYS TELLING HIM TO BE CAREFUL WHEN CROSSING THE STREET.
LOOK, IF YOU CAME HERE BECAUSE YOU'RE SCARED
IF I GIVE YOU A PART OF THE POLICE, YOU CAN STAY
CALM DOWN, I WOULD NEVER DO ANYTHING TO HARMS YOU.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] [SIGH] YOU TOOK A WEIGHT OFF MY BACK,
TWO TONS. YOU'RE WONDERFUL, CARMINHA.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] I KNOW... I HAVE A LOT OF FAITH IN GOD,
I KNOW IT WAS THE TIME FOR GENÉSIO.
IT WAS GOD WHO TOLD ME TO CALL MY HUSBAND
AND HE GAVE ME IN EXCHANGE OTHER VERY GOOD THINGS. YOU,
IF IT WERE NOT FOR YOU, THE DAY BEFORE YESTERDAY I WOULD HAVE THROWN MYSELF OUT OF THE WINDOW,
YOU KNOW THIS. IT WAS AN ENVOY FROM GOD WHO SAVED ME,
YOU. YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
NOT JUST MINE.
[TYPHOON] WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[CARMINHA] THERE IS ANOTHER LIFE PULSING INSIDE ME.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] I'M PREGNANT.
[TYPHOON] [THROAT CLEARING] PREGNANT?
[CARMINHA] I FOUND OUT YESTERDAY.
PREGNANCY ALREADY TWO MONTHS. IT'S FROM THE GENÉSIO, ISN'T IT BEAUTIFUL?
[TYPHOON] I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
[CARMINHA] I WANTED YOU TO
WERE THE GODFATHER, BECAUSE IF IT WASN'T YOU, THIS CHILD
IT WOULDN'T EXIST, WOULD IT?
[TYPHOON] NO, SURE, SURE,
I MAKE A POINT, AND I MAKE A POINT OF... OF... OF TAKING ALL THE COSTS
HOSPITAL EXPENSES, DOCTOR...
[CARMINHA] NO, NO, NO, IMAGINE, YOU DON'T NEED IT. NO,
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING, I DON'T WANT ANYTHING FROM YOU. I'VE ALREADY BEEN IN THE WAY
I'VE BROKE UP YOUR LIFE SO MUCH, IMAGINE. I'VE BROKE UP YOUR LIFE SO MUCH
WITH YOUR BRIDE, I FELT SO BAD BECAUSE OF IT.
EVEN, COME HERE, HAVE YOU GUYS AGREEED?
[TYPHOON] AH... NO.
NO, SHE... SHE BROKE UP WITH ME AND WENT BACK TO...
FOR THE NORTHEAST, I THINK THIS TIME IT IS DEFINITIVE.
[CARMINHA] NO. FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, I CAN'T LET YOU
THAT SUCH AN ABSURDITY LIKE THIS HAPPENS. LET'S GO THERE,
I NEED TO EXPLAIN MYSELF...
[TYPHOON] NO, NO, LOOK...
[CARMINHA] SHE CAN'T THINK WE HAD SOMETHING.
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA, MONALISA IS HARD-HEADED,
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
[CARMINHA] LET ME TRY.
[TYPHOON] NO, IN RELATION TO THAT,
THERE IS NOTHING THAT CAN BE DONE. SHE TOLD ME
THAT HE NEVER WANTED TO LOOK AT MY FACE AGAIN.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] OH...
[TYPHOON] I...
I HAVE TO GO.
[CARMINHA] OK.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW HOW TO THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] I'M THE ONE WHO SHOULD THANK YOU.
A PERSON LIKE YOU IS A RARITY. TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF,
AND TAKE CARE OF HIM TOO, MY... MY GODSON.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[DOOR OPEN]
[VOMITING]
[HATES] OH MY GOD, CAN'T YOU TAKE IT ANYMORE, MY DAUGHTER?
[MONALISA] OH, WHAT A DISCOMFORT. ALSO, WHAT A GIRL IDEA
MY TRAVEL IN THIS OLD CAN, IN THIS STATE I'M IN.
[VOMITING]
[HATES] MY GOD...
EAT SOMETHING, MY LOVE.
[MONALISA] I DON'T WANT IT.
[HATES] A LITTLE BIT.
[MONALISA] IMPOSSIBLE.
I DON'T WANT IT, YOU CAN EAT IT AS MUCH AS YOU WANT.
IF I FEEL HUNGRY THEN I'LL ORDER SOMETHING.
[CHILD] MY MOTHER PICKED IT UP OUTSIDE AND TOLD ME TO DELIVER IT
FOR YOU, LADY. IT'S BOLDO.
SAYS IT'S GOOD FOR MOTION SICKNESS.
[MONALISA] OH, MY SON. MAY GOD Bless You, OK?
[COMMOTION]
[MONALISA] HOW LOVELY.
[DÉIA] [LAUGHTER] ANY TIME NOW
YOUR BACURI WILL BE LIKE THIS.
[MAN] BUT WITHOUT A FATHER TO RAISE HIM,
YOU'RE GOING TO BECOME A PUSSY, THAT'S FOR IT.
[DÉIA] MONALISA, THERE'S STILL TIME. LET'S GET IT
THE FIRST BUS TO RIO DE JANEIRO, HUH?
GO AFTER YOUR MAN, BUILD A FAMILY.
BECAUSE A SINGLE MOTHER, DAUGHTER, IS A DISGRACE, IT IS A PERDITION.
AND GO RIGHT AWAY BEFORE THE OTHER SIRIGAITA TAKES YOUR PLACE.
[MONALISA] NO, I'M GOING... I'M GOING TO TAKE A BREAK IN PARAÍBA,
SIT MY HEAD DOWN.
[DÉIA] HE'S REALLY HARD HEADED, WOW.
[TYPHOON] IT'S BAD FOR ME TODAY, IT'S BAD.
[LELECO] LET'S GO HOME, MY SON, BEFORE YOU HAVE
A BRUISE, OR SOMETHING WORSE.
[TYPHOON] YES, DAD, I'M DEFINITELY NOT LUCKY
THAT THE LORD HAS WITH A WOMAN.
[MURICY] NOW YOU TOLD THE TRUTH, SEE, MY SON?
BECAUSE HERE, MY NEGO, WHEN THE SUBJECT IS THE OTHER HALF,
YOU'VE GOT NOTHING TO COMPLAIN ABOUT, RIGHT, DEAR? [LAUGHTER]
YOU HAVE TO THINK POSITIVELY, SON, IT IS. THERE ARE EVILS THAT COME FOR THE GOOD,
YOU GOT RID OF A JARARACA, WHICH IS NOT ONLY OF A LOW LEVEL,
IT'S SO CHEAP, HE STILL BETRAYED YOU, HE DENOUNCED YOU.
[LELECO] IT'S YOUR MOTHER'S IMPLICATION.
MONALISA IS A GOOD PERSON.
[MURICY] "GOOD PERSON", GO. THAT WIDOW IS A GOOD PERSON,
THAT ONE THAT... THAT THE TYPHOON RAN OVER,
WHO DIDN'T GIVE PART OF HIM, THAT'S A GOOD PERSON.
AFTER ALL, A WOMAN OF CHARACTER.
WHO IS THIS GIRL, HUH, SON?
[TYPHOON] A VERY GOOD WOMAN, AN EDUCATED WOMAN
TO WHOM I OWE A LOT, MOTHER.
[MURICY] AH... IT LOOKS LIKED HER, RIGHT, SON?
[TYPHOON] [MOANING] OH, MOTHER. I'M CRAZY ABOUT THE MONALISA, YOU DON'T KNOW.
I'M GOING TO LAY DOWN BECAUSE I'M CRUSHED.
[MURICY] GO, SON, GO TO BED, GO.
A MOTHER'S LIGHT IS NOT FOOLED. SHE'S IN LOVE WITH THIS WIDOW.
BUT I THINK IT'S GOOD, I THINK IT'S GOOD, I THINK THIS WOMAN HAS VALUE,
I LIKED HER ATTITUDE. I THINK I'LL EVEN GO THERE
TALK TO HER. I'LL GO THERE, OFFER SUPPORT,
OFFER... WHATEVER ELSE SHE WANTS, RIGHT?
[LUCINDA] WILL YOU HAVE A LITTLE MORE? HAVE YOU EATEN?
Yeah, come on, okay? WHO MADE THE BEANS TODAY, HUH? [LAUGHTER]
WOW, FINALLY, BUT WHERE WERE THE MISSING PEOPLE?
[RITA] OH, PICKING UP SOMETHING OLD AROUND.
[LUCINDA] [EXTENDED] OH... BUT I WANT TO SEE, I WANT TO SEE,
I WANT TO SEE, LET'S SEE. OH, WHAT'S IN THERE, GUYS?
NO... [LAUGHTER] WHAT IS THIS, OH WHAT IS THIS?
[RITA] I WANT TO MAKE A DRESS.
[BETANY] HUM, WHITE FABRIC IS A WEDDING DRESS.
[ALL] OH...
[LUCINDA] HEY, WHAT'S FUNNY ABOUT THIS?
[BOY] BATATA AND RITA ARE DATING.
[EVERYONE] ARE DATING, SO DATING.
[POTATO] THAT'S RIGHT, AND WE'RE GOING TO GET ENGAGED.
[LUCINDA] GROOM? WOW, WHAT AN OLD THING,
MORE OLD FASHIONED, PEOPLE.
[RITA] AH, WE THINK IT'S NICE, WE'RE GOING TO DO IT
EVEN A PARTY IN FRONT OF OUR ENGAGEMENT HOUSE.
[LUCINDA] PARTY? WOW, I LIKED IT. TOP,
THE PARTY IS WITH ME, DID YOU KNOW?
[LAUGHTER]
[RITA] I WANT TO BE THE PRINCESS BRIDE
AND YOU ARE OUR GODMOTHER PRINCESS.
[LUCINDA] [EXTENDED] I LIKED IT. LET'S HAVE THE MOST BEAUTIFUL PARTY
WHAT HAS THE DUMP EVER SEEN? HUH? TO GO DOWN IN HISTORY. LOOK HERE,
LET'S START WITH THE WEDDING DRESS. MR. POTATO
YOU CAN GO AWAY, BECAUSE NOBODY CAN SEE THE BRIDE
BEFORE THE CEREMONY. ALL THE BOYS OUT.
[TALK]
[LUCINDA] LOOK, IT'S GOING TO BE THE MOST BEAUTIFUL THING!
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[DOOR OPEN]
[ALEXIA] WHAT IS THIS?
[CRUCIBLE] CALM DOWN.
[ALEXIA] WHAT DO YOU MEAN "CALM DOWN"? WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
HOW DID YOU MANAGE TO GET INTO THE HOUSE?
[CRUITLING] WELL, THE DOOR WAS OPEN.
[ALEXIA] WHAT DO YOU MEAN THE "DOOR WAS OPEN"?
HAVE YOU NEVER HEARD OF CALLING PEOPLE,
MAKE A PHONE CALL, RING THE DOORBELL BEFORE ENTERING, NO?
[CADINHO] I CALLED YOU, BUT YOU DIDN'T CALL ME BACK.
[ALEXIA] I DIDN'T COME BACK AND I WILL NEVER COME BACK! MY GOD,
HOW MANY TIMES DO I NEED TO TELL YOU FOR YOU TO UNDERSTAND
THAT YOU AND I, WE DON'T HAVE A RELATIONSHIP!
[CADINHO] NO, NO, NO, JUST ONE CHILD IN COMMON,
A LITTLE DETAIL. EXCUSE ME,
I'M JUST GOING TO FIX IT A LITTLE.
[ALEXIA] GET YOUR HAND OFF MY CRIB, GET YOUR HAND OFF MY CRIB!
[CADINHO] I BOUGHT YOU A FUTON. LOOK, MUCH BETTER
THAN A CRIB. LOOK, MUCH MORE SPACE
FOR CHILDREN TO PLAY, MUCH SAFER. [LAUGHTER]
[ALEXIA] HOW DO YOU KNOW?
[CRUCIBLE] HUM?
[ALEXIA] YEAH, HOW DO YOU KNOW THESE THINGS?
[CRUITLING] I READ IT, HUH.
[ALEXIA] DID YOU READ IT?
[CRUCIBLE] I READ, I READ, I READ. "MY SON, MY TREASURE", GREAT BOOK,
IT'S ALL THERE. COME ON, I'LL TEACH YOU. YOU LAY DOWN HERE, LOOK,
IN THIS POSITION YOU CAN BREASTFEED THE BABY, UNDERSTAND?
[ALEXIA] YOU'VE GONE CRAZY, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND ANYTHING.
ME LYING IN A POSITION LIKE THIS
IT'S A SHOT AND A DOWN, TWO MINUTES, HEARTBURN.
[CRUITING] [LAUGHTER] HEARTBURN IS VERY COMMON IN PREGNANT WOMEN.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IS A SHOT AND A FALL? SUCKING ICE.
[ALEXIA] SUCK?
[CRUITLING] YES, BUT YOU HAVE TO SUCK IT,
YOU CANNOT CHEW, UNDERSTAND?
[ALEXIA] I UNDERSTAND. YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY SURE
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE A CHILD?
[CADINHO] I DON'T HAVE A SON, GIRL, WHAT SON, ARE YOU CRAZY?
I DON'T EVEN HAVE A GIRLFRIEND, AND LOOK, I DON'T LIKE MOVEMENT, HUH?
[ALEXIA] PERFECT FOR ME, EXACTLY.
OK, YOU CAN GO BACK WITH YOUR PARTY, OK?
[CRUCIBLE] NO, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
A PARTY IS A PARTY, A SON IS A SON, IT'S A SERIOUS THING.
ONE THING HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE OTHER.
[ALEXIA] OH, I DON'T WANT YOU TO BE THE FATHER, HUH?
[CADINHO] NO, THAT WASN'T IN MY PROJECTS EITHER,
BUT NOW IT'S TOO LATE. INÊS IS PREGNANT
AND I WILL NOT LEAVE INÊS IN THE LIGHT, THAT'S IT.
[ALEXIA] IN YOUR HAND? NO, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND, LEAVE IT
I WILL EXPLAIN SOMETHING TO YOU. YOU WON'T LEAVE ME HANDLING, YOU KNOW
WHY? BECAUSE I'M RICH, I'M A MILLIONAIRE, I DON'T NEED IT
YOUR HELP. BY THE WAY, EXCUSE ME, GET OUT OF THIS THING HERE, LOOK.
AND I WILL LOOK FOR MY LAWYER IMMEDIATELY, I WILL ASK HIM
WRITE A DOCUMENT PROHIBITING YOU FROM GIVING ANY HELP
FOR MY SON, OK? A KIND OF, LIKE,
"FOOD DISPENSATION", I DON'T WANT ANY CONNECTION.
[CADINHO] LOOK, I'M GOING TO TELL YOU SOMETHING,
PAY ATTENTION. LOOK. THE SON IS OURS
AND I GIVE HIM WHATEVER I WANT, UNDERSTAND?
[ALEXIA] HOLY SHIT, LIFE REALLY IS A SURPRISE, ISN'T IT?
LOOK, SO MANY WOMEN COMPLAINING, BUT SO MANY WOMEN,
YOU KNOW? SAYING THAT MAN IS IRRESPONSIBLE,
UNNATURED FATHER... LOOK, YOU DON'T HAVE THIS PROBLEM,
ISN'T IT? THEN DO THIS,
MY LOVE, GO BE IRRESPONSIBLE, GO BE UNNATURED.
[CADINHO] NO, NOT AT ALL. I BELIEVE IN THE FAMILY.
[ALEXIA] YOU HAVE NO FAMILY!
[CRUCIBLE] NOW I HAVE IT.
[ALEXIA] OH, THAT'S CRAZY. YOU... LET ME GO, STOP!
GIVE ME THIS FUTON HERE. WHAT'S FUTON?
I DON'T WANT A FUTON. STOP IT... STOP IT... OW!
[CADINHO] HOW ARE YOU GOING TO STOP ME NOW? HUH?
♪GOD PROTECT ME FROM YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
♪GOD HELP ME FROM YOUR ANGER♪
♪GOD IMMUNIZES ME FROM YOUR POISON♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR END♪
♪GOD PROTECT ME FROM YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
[ALEXIA] I CONFESS TO YOU...
[LAUGHTER] IF I KNEW THE THOUSAND AND ONE USES OF THE FUTON,
I SWEAR I HADN'T RESISTED SO MUCH.
[CRUITING] [LAUGHTER] LOOK, ALEXIA, I WANT TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I REALLY SHOULDN'T, BUT LOOK, I'M GOING TO SAY IT.
I'M COMPLETELY IN LOVE WITH YOU.
[ALEXIA] WHAT'S UP, CRUCIBLE?
THAT'S CRAZY, I DON'T EVEN KNOW YOUR NAME PROPERLY.
[CRUCIBLE] LOOK, IT'S CARLOS EDUARDO DE SOUZA QUEIROZ,
I AM 35 YEARS OLD, 5'11" TALL,
78 KILOS, BRAZILIAN, FAN
FROM THE DIVINE FOOTBALL CLUB.
[ALEXIA] MARITAL STATUS?
[CRUCIBLE] SINGLE.
[ALEXIA] CONVINCED?
[CADINHO] I'VE BEEN, BUT I CHANGED MY MIND ABOUT TWO MONTHS AGO.
[ALEXIA] WHY?
[CADINHO] BECAUSE I MET AN INCREDIBLE WOMAN, THE WOMAN
MOST WONDERFUL I HAVE EVER MET IN MY LIFE.
[ALEXIA] YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
[CADINHO] NOT YET, UNLESS, OF COURSE, SHE ACCEPTS
MY PROPOSAL.
HE WANTS?
BE MY GIRLFRIEND? HUH?
[ALEXIA] OH CADINHO, MY LOVE, I PROMISE I WILL THINK ABOUT IT
WITH LOVE IN YOUR PROPOSAL, OK? I PROMISE.
[CADINHO] ARE YOU REALLY GOING? THINK ABOUT IT CAREFULLY, OK? BECAUSE...
I'VE NEVER FELT THIS FOR ANYONE.
[ALEXIA] MY LOVE, NOW GO FOR IT, OK?
[CARMINHA] NO, AUNT, I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN NO PRODUCT, NO.
[MURICY] NO, NO, WAIT, I'M NOT SELLING ANYTHING,
I AM THE MOTHER OF THE TYPHOON.
[CARMINHA] MRS. MURICY?
[MURICY] IS IT [LAUGHTER] DID I ARRIVE AT A BAD TIME? AM I BOTHERING YOU HERE?
[CARMINHA] NO, NOT AT ALL.
[MURICY] HERE, I BROUGHT YOU THIS PAPAYA SWEET, THIS
THIS IS MY SPECIALTY, I MAKE IT. LET ME PUT IT IN
IN THE FRIDGE, MY DAUGHTER. EVERYONE LOVES THIS SWEET
AT HOME, MY DAUGHTER.
[CARMINHA] OH, I LOVE PAPAYA JAM.
[MURICY] WOW, YOU KNOW I REMEMBER YOU PERFECTLY
IN THAT AD. THAT AD WAS FOR... OIL.
TANNING, ISN'T IT? [LAUGHTER]
THERE WAS A HUGE BILLBOARD IN FRONT OF MY HOUSE, GIRL.
[CARMINHA] WOW, BUT DO YOU REMEMBER? IT'S BEEN SO LONG.
[MURICY] BUT JUST BY LOOKING AT YOU I CAN ALREADY TELL
THAT YOU ARE A PERSON, SO, WELL-TRAVELLED, A PERSON OF CLASS.
LOOK AT THIS NICE WAY YOU GAVE TO THIS APARTMENT,
GIRL.
[CARMINHA] OH, IMAGINE, DONA MURICY, YOUR SON WAS THE ONE WHO WAS
VERY GENEROUS TO LET ME STAY HERE FOR THIS LONG, I WHO
I DON'T FEEL VERY COMFORTABLE, YOU KNOW? BUT I'M ALREADY LOOKING FOR IT
A PLACE TO GO.
[MURICY] NO WAY, MY DAUGHTER, YOU'RE GOING TO STAY HERE
AS LONG AS YOU WANT. THIS WOULD BE BETTER HERE.
IMAGINE, MY FAMILY, MY FAMILY HAS A DEBT
WITH YOU, MY DEAR, YOU... YOU COULD HAVE GIVEN PART OF THE
MY SON WHEN HE RUN OVER YOUR HUSBAND, BUT YOU DIDN'T GIVE IT!
[CARMINHA] NO, BUT THE TYPHOON WASN'T TO BLAME, NO, GENÉSIO WAS
IT'S THAT YOUR SON THREW HIMSELF IN FRONT OF THE CAR, EVEN
CALLED THE AMBULANCE.
[MURICY] BUT I KNOW, MY DAUGHTER, BUT IF YOU WERE NOT
THIS PERSON OF CHARACTER, THIS PERSON OF INTEGRITY THAT YOU ARE,
YOU COULD HAVE USED THIS FOR EVIL, TO BLACKMAIL,
THESE THINGS, RIGHT?
[CARMINHA] WOW, I WOULD NEVER DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
[MURICY] I KNOW, I KNOW YOU DON'T, I ALREADY LIKED YOU THERE
BEFORE, NOW THAT I KNOW YOU, I LIKE YOU EVEN MORE.
I WILL TAKE THE LIBERTY OF SAYING ONE THING TO YOU, MY DAUGHTER.
[CARMINHA] YOU CAN SAY.
[MURICY] I KNOW YOU'RE GOING THROUGH A MOMENT
VERY DIFFICULT. WHAT'S THERE? IT'S BEEN A LITTLE OVER A MONTH, RIGHT?
THAT YOU LOST YOUR HUSBAND IN SUCH A STUPID WAY,
SO BRUTAL, ISN'T IT?
[CARMINHA] THE PAIN ONLY GETS WORSE, DONA MURICY.
[MURICY] I IMAGINE, DEAR, I IMAGINE, BUT LOOK, LIFE...
LIFE IS A THING... IT'S A VERY CRAZY THING, IT TAKES YOU AWAY
ONE THING ABOUT US, SHE RETURNS ANOTHER IN ITS PLACE.
IT'S TRUE, MY DAUGHTER, LOOK AT YOUR CASE, FOR EXAMPLE, ISN'T IT?
GOD TOOK AWAY YOUR HUSBAND, BUT HE PUT MY SON IN YOURS
WAY. GOD IS CRAZY, MY DAUGHTER, GOD IS CRAZY, HE WRITES
RIGHT IN CROOKED LINES!
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE, YOU CAN, YOU CAN.
[MURICY] YOU, LIKE THIS...
DO YOU HAVE ANY FEELINGS FOR MY SON?
[CARMINHA] OH, MRS. MURICY...
IT IS DIFFICULT TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION, LIKE THIS, AT THIS TIME.
IMAGINE, IF IT WERE IN OTHER CIRCUMSTANCES, I WOULD SAY THAT...
YES.
[MURICY] I KNEW! THE TYPHOON DIDN'T TELL ME ANYTHING, NOTHING, BUT LOOK,
I KNOW THAT BOY, HE FEELS SOMETHING TOO
THING FOR YOU.
[CARMINHA] OH, DONA MURICY, PLEASE, DON'T SAY A THING
NOT THOSE, MY HEAD IS VERY CONFUSED, IMAGINE,
I CAN'T, I CAN'T EVEN THINK ABOUT ANYTHING.
[MURICY] NO, OF COURSE, IMAGINE, LET'S GIVE TIME TO TIME, RIGHT?
DAUGHTER? LET'S LET THINGS TAKE THEIR COURSE, RIGHT? BUT I
I ALSO WANTED TO INVITE YOU, WE HAVE A HOUSE
FROM THE BEACH, YOU KNOW? OVER IN CABO FRIO. THE HOUSE, LIKE, IS NOT THOSE
GREAT LUXURIES, NO, YOU KNOW? BUT IT'S FACING THE SEA,
THERE'S NOTHING BETTER TO, YOU KNOW, COOL YOUR HEAD.
[CARMINHA] AH, IMAGINE, I CAN'T ACCEPT IT...
[MURICY] OF COURSE YOU CAN, YOU MUST ACCEPT. IMAGINE, MY DAUGHTER,
WHAT'S THIS? LOOK, HERE'S THE KEY TO THE HOUSE AND THE ADDRESS IS HERE
INSIDE, OK? AND LOOK, I DON'T ACCEPT "NO" FOR AN ANSWER.
[CARMINHA] OH, BUT, DONA MURICY, NO...
[MURICY] IT WILL DO YOU GOOD.
[MURICY] WHO KNOWS MY SON WON'T COME THERE TO MAKE YOU DO IT
A LITTLE VISIT, HUM?
[MURICY] I'M GOING.
I WON'T TAKE UP ANY MORE OF YOUR TIME, DEAR.
[CARMINHA] DONA MURICY, WHAT'S THIS? BUT ARE YOU SURE?
DON'T YOU WANT TO STAY A LITTLE LONGER? SHALL I MAKE YOU SOME COFFEE?
[MURICY] NO, ANOTHER DAY, ANOTHER DAY, NOW YOU GO THERE
INSIDE, ARE YOU GOING TO PACK YOUR BAGS AND GO TO CABO FRIO, HUH? [LAUGHTER]
LOOK, DEAR...
[CARMINHA] I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
[MURICY] YOU DON'T SAY ANYTHING. IT WAS A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU,
CAN I SAY ONE THING?
[CARMINHA] YOU CAN.
[MURICY] I WOULD LOVE TO HAVE YOU AS A DAUGHTER-IN-LAW!
[LAUGHTER]
[MURICY] LET ME OPEN THE DOOR MYSELF, OTHERWISE I WON'T COME BACK.
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE, OF COURSE, COME BACK ANYTIME.
[CARMINHA] WHAT...
WHAT IS THIS?
[CARMINHA] HOMEMADE PAPAYA SWEET.
[FOOD HANDLING]
[CARMINHA] OH YOU SCLEROTIC OLD WOMAN.
YOU FELL FROM THE SKY, HUH? HERE, LOOK. IN MY HAND.
[DÉA] YOU CAN CRY, MY LITTLE CALF, YOU CAN CRY.
CRY, MY LOVE.
[MONALISA] AUNT DÉA, YOU'RE RIGHT. I LOVE MY TYPHOON.
I NEED TO GO BACK TO RIO RIGHT NOW.
[DÉA] I'M GLAD YOU'VE COME TO SOME SENSE IN THAT LITTLE HEAD OF YOURS,
MY DAUGHTER.
[MONALISA] WHEN I ARRIVE IN ILHÉUS, I WILL CHANGE BUSES,
I'M GOING TO TAKE A BUS BACK TO RIO. YOU NEED TO COME, NO,
THAT WOULD BE ASKING TOO MUCH.
[DÉA] HUM, AND I WILL LEAVE MY FAVORITE NIECE
COME BACK ALONE? NO WAY, WE'RE ALL GOING BACK, MY LOVE.
[LAUGHTER] PEOPLE, PEOPLE, MONALISA IS COMING BACK.
[JUCA] THIS IS NOW WHEN THIS ENGAGEMENT PARTY WILL HAPPEN. [LAUGHTER]
[MONALISA] NOW GET OUT, JUCA.
[DÉA] NOW GET OUT.
[MONALISA] TYPHOON, I'M COMING BACK, MY LOVE.
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[CARMINHA] I'M GOING TO CABO FRIO AND THE TYPHOON WILL FIND ME THERE.
[MAX] YOU'RE NOT EVEN SURE THIS GUY IS GOING TO CABO FRIO.
[CARMINHA] GO BECAUSE EVERYTHING WILL WORK OUT, BECAUSE
MY MOTHER-IN-LAW IS BY MY SIDE. WRITE DOWN WHAT I'M TELLING YOU,
MAX, IN A SHORT TIME THIS GUY WILL BE HERE, LOOK, IN MY HAND.
[MAX] OH. SHIT. CAN I SING YOU A LITTLE SONG, REAL QUICK?
AND WHAT AM I GOING TO DO WITH MY WEEKEND?
[CARMINHA] YOU SACRIFICE YOUR WEEKEND
FOR A GREATER GOOD.
[MAX] HEY CARMINHA, STOP THIS, I'M GETTING FED UP ALREADY
TIRED OF THIS STUFF, LIVED?
[CARMINHA] BE PATIENT, COME ON, MY LOVE. HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF
PATIENCE WILL BE WORTH IT. WE WILL HAVE THE LIFE WE WANT
WE ALWAYS DREAMED, WE'RE GOING TO PUT, OH, OUR OX IN THE SHADE.
[MAX] IS IT? I WANT TO SEE THIS.
[LAUGHTER]
[CARMINHA] I'M GOING TO NEED A LITTLE FAVOR FROM YOU.
[KISS SNAP]
[CARMINHO] YOU KNOW THAT FRIEND OF YOURS, THAT PHOTOGRAPHER
UNEMPLOYED MAN WHO TAKES PHOTOS OF FAMOUS PEOPLE ON THE BEACH?
[MAX] HUM.
[CARMINHA] YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE HIM TO CABO FRIO, I NEED A PHOTO.
JUST ONE PHOTO.
[MONALISA] DO YOU CURSES? SO YOU REALLY WANT TO MARRY ME?
[TYPHOON] DO YOU THINK I'M DOING WHAT I BROUGHT HERE?
UNTIL ALLIANCE.
♪OUR LOVE KNOWS♪
♪WELL TO YOU♪
[TYPHOON] I'LL START FROM THE BEGINNING.
♪NEITHER THE SAME NOR DIFFERENT♪
[TYPHOON] MONALISA.
♪IT'S NEITHER BEFORE NOR AFTER♪
[TYPHOON] WILL YOU ACCEPT ME AS YOUR FUTURE HUSBAND?
♪NEITHER GUILTY OR INNOCENT♪
[MONALISA] I ACCEPT.
OF COURSE I ACCEPT!
[MURICY] SON?
[DOOR CLOSE]
[TYPHOON] HOW DID YOU GET IN HERE, MOM?
[MURICY] WELL, I HAVE A SPARE KEY, DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
NO? SON, YOU DISAPPEAR, YOU DON'T ANSWER THE PHONE,
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO? TO LEAVE YOU?
[TYPHOON] I NEED TO BE ALONE FOR A LITTLE BIT.
[MURICY] AH, ALONE, ALONE... IT'S BEEN TWO DAYS SINCE YOU'VE BEEN
ALONE HERE IN THIS APARTMENT. FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, SON, BALL
UPWARDS, ACTIVITY. AN EMPTY HEAD IS THE DEVIL'S WORKSHOP.
I KNOW YOU'RE HERE JUST THINKING ABOUT THAT BANDIT.
[TYPHOON] OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, MOTHER, OH, DON'T TALK ABOUT MONALISA LIKE THAT,
HEY, RESPECT MY FEELINGS, UNDERSTAND?
I STILL LOVE THE MONALISA.
[MURICY] YOU KNOW SOMETHING? I'M GLAD YOU CHEATED
THE MONALISA WITH CARMINHA.
[TYPHOON] WHAT'S IT LIKE?
[MURICY] THAT'S A WOMAN OF YOUR LEVEL, SON.
[TYPHOON] MOTHER, YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW CARMINHA, MOTHER.
[MURICY] OF COURSE I KNOW HER, I WENT TO HER HOUSE.
I MET HER, WHAT A WOMAN, HUH, SON, WHAT CLASS!
[TYPHOON] YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE THIS.
[MURICY] WELL, WHY NOT? I WENT THERE, I MADE A PAPAYA SWEET,
I WENT THERE TO TAKE IT TO HER. WE NEED TO SHOW GRATITUDE TO HER
THIS WOMAN, SON. I EVEN LOANED HER OUR HOUSE THERE
FROM CABO FRIO FOR HER TO SPEND THE WEEKEND, SHE NEEDS IT
GET OUT OF RIO DE JANEIRO, SON, SHE NEEDS TO RELAX. I SAID,
INCLUDING, YOU CAN GO THERE AND FIND HER.
[TYPHOON] MRS. MURICY, YOU'RE FORCING IT, HUH?
[MURICY] [LAUGHTER] I'M NOT FORCING IT, IT WAS JUST A COURTESY
THAT I DID. YOU CAN PERFECTLY GO THERE,
AS A FRIEND, KEEP HER COMPANY, WHY NOT?
THAT'S THE LEAST I WOULD DO IF I WERE IN YOUR SHOES, OK?
[TYPHOON] LOOK HERE, MOTHER, LET ME EXPLAIN SOMETHING TO YOU,
YOU'RE THROWING ME ON TOP OF CARMINHA, BUT MINE
HEAD IS STILL IN MONALISA, I'M STILL INVOLVED
WITH MONALISA, GET THAT IN YOUR MIND.
[MURICY] I KNOW, BUT YOU FEEL SOMETHING FOR THE OTHER ONE,
DON'T YOU FEEL IT?
[TYPHOON] I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ANYMORE, MOTHER.
[MURICY] SON, LISTEN TO WHAT YOUR MOTHER IS TELLING YOU,
PACK A BAG, GO TO CABO FRIO, GO TAKE A SWIM IN THE SEA,
IT WILL BE MUCH BETTER THAN STAYING THE WHOLE WEEKEND
LOCKED INSIDE THIS APARTMENT BROWING
THE RETIRED WHO RETIRED.
[TYPHOON] Hey...
[MURICY] OK, OK, I WON'T SAY ANYTHING ELSE,
I WILL NOT INVADE YOUR SPACE ANYMORE. BYE, DEAR.
[TYPHOON] BYE, MOM.
[MURICY] THINK WITH LOVE.
[TYPHOON] OK.
[MURICY] OH, THE FRIDGE IS FULL, RIGHT?
[TOGETHER] THE FLOWERS!
[LUCINDA] [LAUGHTER] OH MY GOD!
[LAUGHTER] NOW I...
[POTATO] WHERE'S RITA, MOTHER LUCINDA?
[LUCINDA] IMAGINE! I ALREADY TOLD YOU, YOU CAN'T SEE IT
THE BRIDE FIRST! LET'S CHOOSE THE PRIEST, THE GODPARENTS,
THE GODMOTHERS... LET'S GO? [LAUGHTER]
ATTENTION, KIDS, ATTENTION!
NOW I HAVE TO CHOOSE THE GODMOTHERS AND GODPARENTS,
AND THE PRIEST! LET'S SEE WHO WILL BE THE PRIEST, THE PRIEST,
WHO WILL BE THE PRIEST... EMERSON!
[LAUGHTER]
[EMERSON] OH MOTHER LUCINDA, AND I LOOK LIKE A PRIEST, DO I?
[LUCINDA] LET'S SEE IF YOU LOOK LIKE A PRIEST, COME HERE,
COME HERE. LOOK THERE, LOOK HERE, LET ME SEE...
I CONFESS THAT YOU LOOK VERY WELL!
[LAUGHTER] WELL, NOW I'M GOING TO CHOOSE...
WHAT AM I GOING TO CHOOSE? THE GODMOTHERS!
[JUMBLE] GLADIS AND... BETANY!
[CHRIES OF CELEBRATION]
[LUCINDA] VERY WELL. AND NOW THE GODFATHERS, LET'S SEE, LET'S SEE,
LET'S SEE. LET'S SEE, LET ME THINK. OH, VALENTE AND TONICO.
[LAUGHTER] OK, NOW LET'S FINISH, BECAUSE THIS HOUSE
IT'S LOOKING BEAUTIFUL, LOOK!
[RITA] LOOK HOW BEAUTIFUL BATATA IS, BRUNA.
HE WILL BE MINE FOREVER.
[KNOCK ON GLASS]
[SEA WAVES]
[CARMINHA] I DON'T WANT YOU AROUND, MAN! WHAT IF THE TYPHOON
IT APPEARS FROM ONE HOUR TO THE NEXT!
[MAX] LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING, IF THE TYPHOON COMES,
HE'S GOING TO COME THROUGH THAT ROAD, WE'RE GOING TO SEE HIS CAR.
IN THE MEANWHILE, WE WILL BE ABLE TO ENJOY A LITTLE,
BECAUSE THIS PLACE IS SO NICE.
[CARMINHA] YOU WON'T GET IN THE WAY OF MY PLANS.
[MAX] I WON'T GET IN THE WAY, BUT WE'RE NOT GOING TO MAKE A MOVIE...
COME ON, COME ON, MUCH TASTIER?
[CARMINHA] AND THE PHOTOGRAPHER?
[MAX] THE PHOTOGRAPHER IS AT THE BEACH AS WE AGREED,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE HE WON'T TAKE ANY PHOTOS, BECAUSE THERE ARE NONE
A FOOTBALL PLAYER'S FLAGRANCE, ISN'T IT? AND WHAT'S WORSE,
WE WILL HAVE TO PAY FOR THE PHOTOGRAPHER'S TICKET.
[CARMINHA] LOOK THERE! THE TYPHOON CAR, GO! GO!
HURRY UP, MAX, GET OUT OF HERE!
[CARMINHA] YOU CAME.
[TYPHOON] MOM SAID YOU WERE THERE. WAS IT WRONG FOR ME TO COME?
WANT TO BE ALONE?
[CARMINHA] I MISSED YOU.
[LUCINDA] IN...
[EMERSON] HEALTH AND DISEASE.
[EMERSON] WEALTH AND POVERTY.
[POTATO] OH MOTHER LUCINDA, I WANT TO GET MARRIED SOON.
[LUCINDA] [LAUGHTER] BUT THE GROOM HAS TO BE PATIENT.
OK, LET'S START? COME ON, GET IT, GET IT, GET IT FOR US,
I'M GOING TO START. ATTENTION, BRUNA!
COME ON, BRUNA, BRUNA! WHERE'S BRUNA?
BRUNA, GO, BRUNA! MUSIC, BRUNA! HEY!
[EMERSON] [WHISPERING] IT'S HER, MAN.
[LUCINDA] THE BRIDE IS YOURS. [LAUGHTER]
[LUCINDA] START, YOU CAN START, GO. GO.
[ROBERTO] AND WHERE DO I START?
[POTATO] YOU REHEARSED, MAN.
[ROBERTO] OH, I FORGOT.
[RITA] RITA DE SOUZA...
[ROBERTO] OH YES. [CLEARING]
RITA DE SOUZA, DO YOU ACCEPT TO MARRY A POTATO?
AND PROMISES... PROMISES...
[LUCINDA] LOVE AND RESPECT HIM.
[ROBERTO] IN HEALTH, IN SICKNESS...
[RITA] IN RICHNESS AND IN POVERTY.
[ROBERTO] UNTIL DEATH DO US PART?
[RITA] I PROMISE.
[ROBERTO] AND MR. BATATA? DO YOU ALSO PROMISE?
[POTATO] I PROMISE.
[ROBERTO] THEN, I NOW DECLARE YOU HUSBAND AND WIFE.
♪AFTER DREAMING FOR SO MANY YEARS♪
♪MAKING SO MANY PLANS♪
♪GIVE US A FUTURE♪
♪AFTER SO MANY DISAPPOINTMENTS♪
♪WE LEAVE EACH OTHER♪
♪LIKE SO MANY COUPLES♪
[ROBERTO] THEN, YOU CAN KISS THE BRIDE.
♪I WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY♪
♪YOU HAVE TO BE HAPPY♪
[LUCINDA] COME ON, A PHOTO. A PHOTO.
OH. [EXTENDED] OH, HOW BEAUTIFUL.
[CHRIES OF CELEBRATION]
[LUCINDA] OH HOW BEAUTIFUL! IT'S BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL!
HERE, HERE, HERE THE PHOTO, HERE THE PHOTO, LOOK AT THE PHOTO!
THIS PICTURE HERE! VERY WELL.
[NATURE AMBIENCE]
[BUS ENGINE]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[DÉA] OUR LADY, THIS DRIVER IS SPEEDING TOO FAR.
[MONALISA] GREAT. I CAN'T DYING TO GET TO ILHÉUS
TO CATCH THE BUS TO RIO RIGHT AWAY.
[LAUGHTER]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MAN] ARE YOU CRAZY DRIVER?
[HORN]
[IMPACT ON BUS BODYWORK]
[TIRE SINGING]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY PACE♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK IT♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
.