[SILENCE]
[TALK]
[MONALISA] CALM DOWN, GUYS, CALM DOWN!
[MONALISA] MY GOD, WAIT, LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
[HOSEA] CALM DOWN, GRANDPA, CALM DOWN. CALM DOWN, BREATHE.
[TALK]
[MONALISA] [SCREAM]
[IMPACT ON BODYWORK]
[DÉA] [SCREAM] AN ABYSS! MY GOD!
[MONALISA] CALM, CALM, NOBODY MOVE.
NOBODY MOVES.
[DÉA] BE CAREFUL, MY LOVE!
[MAN] OVER HERE!
[TALK]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[DÉA] BE CAREFUL, MONALISA!
[MONALISA] GO ON, GO ON, AUNT! GO ON!
[DÉA] [CRYING]
[MAN] OW, OW, OW, OW, OW...
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[IRAN] HELP! HELP!
[DÉA] [SHOUTING] MONALISA! WHERE ARE YOU GOING, CREATURE? COME BACK!
[HOSEA] ARE YOU CRAZY OR WHAT? COME BACK!
[MAN] THE BUS IS GOING TO CRASH!
[MONALISA] BOY! BOY!
[IRAN] MY MOTHER! MY MOTHER!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] [PANTING] LET'S GO!
[METAL CREAKING]
[MONALISA] COME ON!
[IRAN] NO!
[MONALISA] COME ON! LET'S GO, THIS BUS IS ON THE END!
[MONALISA] YOU DON'T HAVE TO STOP,
GO!
[IRAN] MOTHER!
[MONALISA] GO! GO, GO!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[BOOTS]
[IRAN] MOTHER!
[MONALISA] WAIT, BOY,
COME BACK HERE! COME BACK HERE, BOY!
[IRAN] [SCREAMING] MOTHER!
[MONALISA] BOY, WAIT, CALM DOWN, MY ANGEL, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
[DÉA] MONALISA, ARE YOU OKAY, MY DAUGHTER? ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
[HOSEA] MONALISM! MONALISM!
MONALISA!
[MONALISA] [PANTING]
[CRYING]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] YOU DON'T THINK ABOUT GOING AFTER IT
FROM YOUR BRIDE IN PARAÍBA?
[TYPHOON] HELLO! IF I COULD FIND OUT WHERE SHE'S HIDING,
SHE WILL CERTAINLY BE WAITING FOR ME
FIVE STONE IN HAND.
[BEACH ATMOSPHERE]
[CARMINHA] BUT YOU... DO YOU FEEL, LIKE, THAT YOU STILL LOVE HER?
[TYPHOON] IF I LOVE, I'M WRONG, RIGHT? THAT'S WHAT SHE SAID
WHO DOESN'T LOVE ME ANYMORE.
[CARMINHA] YES, MY DEAR, WE'RE BOTH SCREWED.
OH, I'LL BE AWARE OF YOU RIGHT AWAY, HUH:
COOKING IS NOT MY STRENGTH.
[BEACH ATMOSPHERE]
[TYPHOON] OK.
[CARMINHA] IT'S HORRIBLE!
[TYPHOON] [COUGH]
[CARMINHA] THE WORST FISH I'VE EVER EATEN IN MY ENTIRE LIFE,
SORRY, TYPHOON! A THOUSAND APOLOGIES!
[IMPACT OF DISHES IN THE SINK]
[CARMINHA] OH MY GOD.
[SIGH] SORRY.
GENÉSIO WAS THE ONE WHO COOKED AT HOME, HE MADE EVERY DISH.
[TYPHOON] I MAKE A WONDERFUL SPAGHETTI CARBONARA,
I'LL MAKE ONE FOR YOU, DO YOU WANT IT?
[BEACH ATMOSPHERE]
[CARMINHA] I WANT TO. SHALL WE TAKE A DIVE IN THE SEA FIRST? THEY SAY THAT
SEA SALT CURES EVERYTHING, EVEN ELBOW PAIN. LET'S GO WITH ME?
[CARMINHA] COME.
[MONALISA] [MOAN]
[DÉA] ARE YOU OK, DAUGHTER.
SHE'S ALIVE, THANK GOD.
[MONALISA] [CRYING] OH MY GOD, THE BUS... THE BOY...
[HOSEA] STAY CALM, THE DOCTOR TOLD YOU TO STAY CALM
RESTING FOR A FEW MORE HOURS.
[MONALISA] A FEW MORE HOURS? WHY?
A FEW HOURS... OH! OH, WHAT PAIN!
[MAN] I THINK I'D BETTER TELL HER RIGHT AWAY.
[MONALISA] WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU GUYS HIDING FROM ME?
[HATES] YOUR BABY, DAUGHTER, YOU LOST IT.
[CRYING]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] [CRYING] MY SON!
MY LITTLE SON...
[CRYING]
[CARMINHA] YUM, DELICIOUS! YOU'RE A GOOD COOK,
HUH, TYPHOON?
[TYPHOON] IS THE ONLY RECIPE I KNOW HOW TO MAKE. NOW,
THE WINE YOU BROUGHT IS GOOD, HUH? GOOD WINE!
[CARMINHA] BARBARESCO, GOES WELL WITH PASTA.
[TYPHOON] YOU'RE A SOPHISTICATED WOMAN, AREN'T YOU?
[CARMINHA] [LAUGHTER] I THINK I LEARNED A LOT AS A MODEL.
[TYPHOON] SHE LOOKS LIKE A WELL-BORN GIRL. TELL ME SOMETHING,
WHAT WAS YOUR LIFE LIKE BEFORE GENÉSIO?
[CARMINHA] AH, LIFE AS A MODEL, A LOT OF WORK, A LOT OF EXCITEMENT.
I MADE MONEY, RIGHT, BUT I SAVED ALMOST NOTHING,
I SPENT EVERYTHING, I HAD NO HEAD.
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE MY LIFE HAS REALLY BEGUN
REALLY WHEN I MET GENÉSIO.
[TYPHOON] WHO KNOWS YOUR LIFE IS NOT STARTING AGAIN.
[CARMINHA] I'M GOING TO WASH THE DISHES.
[TYPHOON] I'LL WASH TOO.
[CARMINHA] NO, NO, NO, STAY THERE, STAY LIKE THAT,
THIS WAY I CAN HELP WITH SOMETHING.
[CARMINHA] I KEEP THINKING HOW A FAMOUS GUY LIKE YOU,
WASTING YOUR TIME LIKE THIS, WITH A WIDOW
LOW INCOME, LIKE ME.
[TYPHOON] I'M NOT WASTING TIME,
I LIKE BEING WITH YOU, I ALREADY TOLD YOU THAT.
[MONALISA] IT HURTS ME SO MUCH TO KNOW THAT THE TYPHOON
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW I WAS GOING TO BE A FATHER.
HE WOULD BE SO HAPPY.
[CRYING] WE COULD
HAVING A BEAUTIFUL FAMILY.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] BOY...
[MONALISA] COME HERE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] WERE YOU WITH YOUR MOTHER ON THE BUS?
[MONALISA] SO YOU'RE GOING TO STAY WITH US.
[HATES] WHAT, MONALISA?
[MONALISA] WHERE DO YOU WANT HIM TO SLEEP, AUNT DEIA?
HE'S GOING WITH US TO THE HOTEL
THAT THE BUS COMPANY WILL ARRANGE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] I WILL TAKE CARE OF HIM.
[LUCINDA] NOW IT'S GOOD! IT'S GETTING GOOD!
[LAUGHTER] NO, BETANIA, YOU HAVE TO CUT THE CAKE FIRST.
AND THEY HAVE TO MAKE THE ORDER. GO, GO, POTATO, MAKE THE ORDER.
[POTATO] SO...
[LUCINDA] SPEAK.
[POTATO] I WANTED TO ASK GOD FOR US TO STAY
TOGETHER FOR THE REST OF OUR LIFE.
[RITA] I WOULD LIKE TO ASK GOD TO LET ME LIVE FOR A LONG, LONG TIME
YEARS TO BE ABLE TO GET REALLY OLD NEAR YOU.
[LUCINDA] OH, YAY! LET'S CUT THE CAKE!
[CHRIES OF CELEBRATION]
[LUCINDA] GO THERE. AH!
[RITA] THE FIRST PIECE GOES TO YOU, MOTHER LUCINDA.
[POTATO] YOU ARE OUR GODMOTHER FOREVER.
[LUCINDA] AND YOU ARE MY TWO LOVES. GIVE ME A HUG,
GIVE ME A HUG! HEY! [LAUGHTER]
[OVATION]
[LUCINDA] LET'S DANCE, LET'S DANCE TO GET THIS PARTY STARTED!
[LUCINDA] LOOK WHO'S HERE, LOOK.
BOUQUET, BOUQUET, BOUQUET, BOUQUET. BOUQUET, GO THERE.
BOUQUET, GO THERE. LOOK, GO THERE, GO THERE. TIME FOR THE BOUQUET.
LET'S CONCENTRATE... CONCENTRATE! TIME FOR THE BOUQUET,
COME ON, COME ON! GO ON.
[TOGETHER] AND IT'S ONE, IT'S TWO, AND IT'S THREE AND THAT'S IT!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[NILO] THE PARTY LOOKS NICE, IT'S A SHAME THEY DIDN'T INVITE US.
[NILO] HUM... THIS IS REALLY STINKING,
I THINK THEY FOUND THESE FLOWERS IN THE GARBAGE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RITA] DISGUSTING!
[LUCINDA] GET OUT OF HERE, GET OUT OF HERE, GET OUT OF HERE. GO, GO, GO.
GET OUT, YOU MISERABLE ONE, GET OUT.
[NILO] I FOUND IT VERY INELEGANT FOR YOU TO HAVE A LARGE PARTY
AND NOT HAVING THE DECENCY TO INVITE FRIENDS
FROM THE NEIGHBORHOOD. COME ON, COME ON, GUYS. YOU CAN EAT IT ALL
WHAT'S HERE, YOU CAN EAT, GUYS.
[LUCINDA] IF I WERE YOU, I WOULD TELL YOU TO STOP NOW!
I'LL DRILL YOU, I'M NOT KIDDING!
WHERE HAVE YOU EVER SEEN AN INVADE?
THE OTHER'S LAND LIKE THIS, HUH?
[NILO] YOU STARTED IT, YOU STOLE IT
MY GOODS, WASN'T IT?
[LUCINDA] ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT RITA?
[NILE] Yes.
[LUCINDA] I WILL TAKE OUT WHOEVER I WANT. EVERY TIME I GO
I NEED TO SAVE A CHILD FROM YOU, OKAY, YOU WRETCH?
DO YOU KNOW WHY I DO THIS? BECAUSE I GUARANTEE MYSELF,
YOU'RE NOT A MAN TO FACE ME, NO.
[NILO] YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE TAKEN THAT GIRL TO YOUR HOUSE.
[LAUGHTER] IF YOU KNEW...
[LUCINDA] WHAT IS IT? IF YOU KNEW WHAT?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[NILO] YOU'RE CREATING A SNAKE, IT WILL END
WITH YOUR LIFE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] I DON'T BELIEVE A WORD THAT COMES OUT OF YOUR MOUTH.
[NILO] GREAT, WORSE FOR YOU. I JUST CAME TO WARN YOU.
♪TENSION MUSIC
[NILO] LET'S GO, LET'S GO, YOU MONKEYS.
WE'RE OVER WITH THE PARTY. [LAUGHTER]
[RITA] GO AWAY.
[TOGETHER] RALA, RALA. GO AWAY.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[URBAN AMBIENCE]
[MONALISA] IT'S JUST THE OVERNIGHT STAY, GUY. TWO ROOMS.
[DÉA] ARE YOU CHANGING YOUR IDEAS, MONALISA?
THE BUS COMPANY IS RESPONSIBLE FOR THE BOY,
NOT OURS.
[MONALISA] IT'S MINE, AUNT DÉA, I DECIDED TO KEEP THE BOY.
YOU STAY OUT OF THIS.
[MAN] BUT... I'M NOT GOING TO SHARE A ROOM WITH SLEEP.
[MONALISA] DON'T WORRY, HE WILL SLEEP WITH ME.
[STEPS]
[MONALISA] BOY, LET'S REST?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[DOOR SQUEAKING]
[STEPS]
[HANDLING PLASTIC BAGS]
[MONALISA] I BROUGHT YOU SOME FOOD, IT'S WARM.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] YOU DIDN'T TELL ME YOUR NAME.
[IRAN] IRAN.
[MONALISA] IRAN? HUM, LIKE THE COUNTRY, IS IT IRAN? [LAUGHTER] NICE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] THE FOOD IS TASTY, IT'S PAÇOCA
OF DRIED MEAT. TEST.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] OK.
[MONALISA] LEAVE IT HERE, OK? WHENEVER YOU WANT,
IF YOU'RE HUNGRY, YOU EAT.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO DO AT NIGHT?
WHAT WOULD YOU AND YOUR MOTHER BE DOING NOW?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[IRAN] DO YOU HAVE A DECK OF CARDS?
[MONALISA] DECK OF CARDS? I DON'T KNOW, I CAN ASK.
[DOOR OPEN]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[DOOR SQUEAKING]
[MONALISA] OH IRAN, LOOK WHAT I GOT FOR YOU,
CLEAN CLOTHES. SEE? WOW, IT LOOKS GREAT. LET'S GO.
[IRAN] WHERE TO?
[MONALISA] YOU HAVE NOWHERE TO GO?
YOU DON'T HAVE A FAMILY, YOU DON'T HAVE A FATHER?
[IRAN] NO, MA'AM. MY FATHER IS IN JAIL, I DON'T KNOW WHERE.
[MONALISA] WHERE WERE YOU GOING WHEN
OUR BUS CRASHED, IRAN?
[IRAN] FOR MY MOTHER'S FATHER'S BURIAL.
I THINK IN PARAÍBA.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] YOU WERE LEFT WITH NOBODY AFTER YOUR MOTHER...
[DÉA] MONALISA, COME ON, THE OTHER BUS HAS ALREADY ARRIVED, MY DAUGHTER.
[MAN] DOES THE BOY HAVE ANY BAGGAGE LEFT?
[MAN] COME ON COUSIN, LET'S GO BACK TO RIO. [LAUGHTER]
[MONALISA] WHAT ABOUT IRAN?
[WOMAN] IS THIS THE BOY WHO LOST HIS MOTHER IN THE ACCIDENT?
[MONALISA] YES, HIMSELF.
[WOMAN] I AM AN EMPLOYEE OF THE BUS COMPANY,
I CAME TO GET YOU.
[MONALISA] BUT WHERE IS HE GOING?
[WOMAN] TO THE NEAREST JUVENILE COURT, BUT YOU CAN LEAVE IT,
HE WILL BE TREATED WELL.
[MONALISA] OF COURSE.
[WOMAN] LET'S GO?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, OK, MY LITTLE ANGEL?
[IRAN] THE LADY WHO IS AN ANGEL WHO SAVED MY LIFE,
I WILL NEVER FORGET YOU, DONA MONALISA.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[IRAN] [SIGH]
[MONALISA] [SCREAMING]
IRAN, IRAN!
[STEPS]
[MONALISA] DO YOU WANT TO COME WITH ME?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] HE COMES WITH ME.
[WOMAN] WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[MONALISA] I'M GOING TO SUBMIT AN APPLICATION TO ADOPTION HIM.
I LOST MY SON IN THIS ACCIDENT, THIS BOY IS COMING
TO ME AS A GIFT FROM GOD. HE CHOSE ME,
DESTINY CHOSE US. AND IT HAS THE RIGHT TO DECIDE
ABOUT YOUR FUTURE.
[WOMAN] BUT THINGS ARE NOT LIKE THAT.
[MONALISA] THEY ARE LIKE THAT, YES, GIRL. YOU CAN LET ME
I CAN UNDERSTAND WHOEVER IT IS. COME ON, IRAN. [LAUGHTER] THANK YOU.
[HATES] MONALISA. WHERE HAVE YOU GONE, GIRL? I WAS ALREADY
GETTING WORRIED.
[MONALISA] AUNT, I'M NOT GOING TO RIO DE JANEIRO ANYMORE.
[HATES] OH, BUT YOU HAD ALREADY DECIDED, MY DAUGHTER.
AND YOUR FIANCÉ IS THERE.
[MONALISA] I KNOW, I KNOW, BUT... BUT MY LIFE HAS CHANGED
A LOT IN THESE LAST FEW HOURS, YOU KNOW? I CAN'T FACE IT
THE TYPHOON NOW. I REALLY NEED TO GO BACK TO MY LAND,
REST, GET MY HEAD IN PLACE, TAKE CARE OF THIS
KID THAT LIFE GAVE ME.
[MONALISA] SO WHAT? ARE WE GOING TO PARAÍBA?
[DIOGENES] I DON'T BELIEVE IT. IS IT STILL LIKE THIS? MY SON,
LET'S PUT THESE TABLES HERE, COME ON, LET'S GET THIS DONE QUICKLY,
THAT THIS STILL HAS TO END IN THIS MILLENNIUM.
[SILAS] BUT, DIOGENES, YOU WILL PUT THE TABLES HERE IN
CENTER? THIS IS THE DANCE FLOOR, WHERE ARE PEOPLE GOING TO DANCE?
[DIOGENES] I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS,
BOY, I DON'T UNDERSTAND, YOU GUYS SOLVE IT YOURSELF. WHO TOOK CARE OF EVERYTHING
THIS WAS THE MONALISM BEFORE.
[MURICY] WHAT MONALISA, WHAT MONALISA? I'VE NEVER HEARD OF IT
THAT NAME.
[LELECO] DON'T TALK LIKE THAT,
MURICY. MONALISA IS THE KEY FIGURE IN THIS CLUB.
[DIOGENES] WAS A VERY NICE PERSON, YOU SEE?
[MURICY] NOW YOU SAID IT VERY WELL, DEAR, "IT WAS", "IT WAS",
BECAUSE FOR ME SHE'S ALREADY DIED.
[STEPS]
[OLENKA] HERE, DONA MURICY. DONA MURICY, UNINTENTIONALLY
MEDDING, BUT ALREADY MEDDING, THIS WOMAN
THAT'S IN THE PHOTO WITH THE TYPHOON...
[MURICY] AH, I DON'T COMMENT ON MY SON'S PERSONAL LIFE. LOOK,
THE TYPHOON WITH CARMINHA, LELECO, LOOK HERE, THEY'RE DATING,
WE'RE DATING.
[LELECO] YOU DON'T KNOW. YOU DON'T KNOW.
[MURICY] THIS HERE, THIS HERE IS NOT A PHOTO OF A BOYFRIEND?
[TALK]
[ADAUTO] THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING, IT WAS A PLEASURE, SEE YOU LATER.
[DIOGENES] NO, WAIT, WAIT... ADAUTO, WHERE IS IT?
ARE YOU GOING, MY SON?
[ADAUTO] ME? I'M GOING NOWHERE, WHICH IS WHERE EVERYONE GOES
WE'RE GOING, THE WORLD IS GOING TO END.
[OLENKA] WHAT'S THIS? HAVE YOU GONE CRAZY?
[ADAUTO] "GOING CRAZY" NO, OLENKA, YOU KNOW NOSTRADAMUS,
ARE YOU MINDFUL? NOSTRADAMUS SAID THE WORLD IS GOING TO END, THIS PARTY
THERE'S NO POINT HERE, THE MILLENNIUM APOCALYPSE IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
[MURICY] MY GOD IN HEAVEN, WHAT APOCALYPSE? TURN THAT MOUTH UP
GET OUT THERE, BOY.
[ADAUTO] YES, IT'S A PITY WE DIDN'T HAVE TIME, RIGHT, MURICY?
[LELECO] SH, SH, SH... WHAT DID YOU HAVE TIME FOR?
WHAT DIDN'T HAVE TIME?
[ADAUTO] NO, NO, I WAS TALKING TO HER HERE.
[DIOGENES] COME HERE, DO ME A FAVOR, DO ME A FAVOR?
MAKE SURE YOU'VE PUT ALL THE DRINKS ON ICE, GO ON.
[ADAUTO] I WON'T GO, I WON'T GO, MR. DIÓGENES, DO YOU KNOW WHY?
THERE'S NO POINT IN CHILLING THE DRINKS, WE WON'T EVEN BE HERE
TO TAKE. SO I'M RESIGNING FROM THE DIVINE COUNCIL,
IT WAS A PLEASURE, THANK YOU. I'M GOING TO GET MY CHEST RUBBED, KISS, BYE.
[OLENKA] GO AWAY, CRAZY BOY. GO AWAY.
[LELECO] WHAT IS THIS STORY, MURICY? THAT ADAUTO
I WAS SAYING THERE WAS NO TIME, WHAT DID THERE NOT HAVE TIME?
[MURICY] NONSENSE, IMAGINE. THIS BOY HAS GONE CRAZY,
PUT IT THERE, DEAR.
[LELECO] I'M WATCHING YOU, HUH, MURICY?
[MURICY] OH, OKAY, YEAH? HUM, THAT'S TASTY.
[KISS SNAP]
[CLICKING OF DISHES]
[RITA] GOOD MORNING.
[TOGETHER] GOOD MORNING.
[RITA] GOOD MORNING, POTATO.
[POTATO] GOOD MORNING, RITA.
[LUCINDA] OH! IS IT BRIDE OR IS IT SLEEPING BEAUTY?
[LAUGHTER]
[POTATO] WHEN WE GROW UP, I'LL BE THE ONLY ONE WHO WILL WORK,
RITA WILL BE TAKING CARE OF OUR CHILDREN.
RENATA AND EVARISTO.
[RITA] NO, BATATA, I'M GOING TO WORK TOO.
[LUCINDA] OH, THE AUTHORITY SPOKEN. WOW!
[LAUGHTER]
[LUCINDA] Hey, RITA.
[CAR ENGINE]
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] OH RITA, WHERE DO YOU KNOW THIS MAN FROM, RITA?
DO YOU KNOW MAX?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] I THINK IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO TELL YOUR STORY,
RIGHT, GIRL?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY PACE♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK IT♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[RITA] THAT BANDIT MAX, MOTHER LUCINDA. MY STEPMOTHER,
CARMINHA CHEATED MY FATHER WITH HIM.
[LUCINDA] OH, HOW HORROR. YOUR FATHER DIED THE DAY YOU
DID YOU FIND OUT... WHO GOT THE MONEY?
[RITA] WITH THEM. THEY STOLE EVERYTHING THAT BELONGED TO MY FATHER,
EVERYTHING THAT WAS MINE.
[LUCINDA] POOR YOU, HUH, DAUGHTER?
[RITA] YOU NEED TO HAVE PITY ON ME, NO, MOTHER LUCINDA,
I WILL TAKE REVENGE ON THEM.
[LUCINDA] YOU DON'T HAVE TO THINK LIKE THAT. WHOEVER WANTS TO
THE EVIL OF OTHERS ENDS UP SUFFERING CONSEQUENCES TOO.
HATRED ATTRACTS MORE HATRED, MORE UNHAPPINESS.
LOOK, I KNOW IT'S HARD, YOU HAVE TO FIND A WAY TO FORGET
THAT'S ALL, GET ON WITH YOUR LITTLE LIFE FROM HERE ON.
[RITA] NO, I WON'T FORGET.
[LUCINDA] WHAT'S THIS? YOU HAVE YOUR WHOLE LIFE AHEAD OF YOU.
A BEAUTIFUL LIFE. YOU'LL STILL MARRY THE REAL BATATA.
DO YOU WANT... DO YOU WANT TO GIVE UP ALL THIS?
BECAUSE OF A STUPID REVENGE?
[RITA] I WANT!
[LUCINDA] YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
[RITA] YES I KNOW.
[LUCINDA] GO, GO, GO OUT FOR A LITTLE.
GO... GO OCCUPY THAT HEAD OF YOURS, GO OUT, GO. GO FOR A WALK,
GO. GO PLAY OUTSIDE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CAR ENGINE]
[TYPHOON] ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT TO GO TO MY HOUSE?
[CARMINHA] I HAVE. I WANT TO GO BACK HOME.
[TYPHOON] SHOULD I GO UP?
[CARMINHA] NO, I DON'T THINK IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
[TYPHOON] MY GOD, WHAT'S WRONG? DID I SAY SOMETHING?
[CARMINHA] NO, NO, YOU DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING WRONG.
[TYPHOON] OH, SO WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
[CARMINHA] IT'S JUST EVERYTHING GOING TOO FAST,
UNTIL A FEW DAYS AGO YOU WERE ENGAGED, ARE YOU STILL CAPABLE?
TO GO BACK TO YOUR FIANCE, AND MAYBE THAT'S EVEN THE RIGHT THING.
[URBAN AMBIENCE]
[TYPHOON] YOU'RE NOT ENJOYING IT, YOU'RE NOT ENJOYING IT.
[CARMINHA] YOU STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND.
[TYPHOON] WHAT?
[URBAN AMBIENCE]
[CARMINHA] I FELL IN LOVE WITH YOU.
I REALLY LIKE YOU, IT'S DRIVING ME CRAZY,
I JUST LOST MY GENESIO, I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE QUIET
IN MY CORNER, SUFFERING, BUT NO, I'M HERE, HAVING AN AFFAIR
WITH A MAN COMMITTED TO ANOTHER WOMAN,
THIS IS NOT RIGHT.
[TYPHOON] NO, HAVE YOU EVER IMAGINED IF... LOOK, IF GENÉSIO
IF HE KNEW I WAS HERE WITH YOU, HE COULD BE HAPPY,
I CAME INTO YOUR LIFE BECAUSE OF HIM.
[CARMINHA] DON'T DO THIS TO ME, I'M AT MY LIMIT,
I'VE ALREADY SUFFERED TOO MUCH IN THIS LIFE, I CAN'T.
[TYPHOON] WHO SAID I'M GOING TO MAKE YOU SUFFER?
[CARMINHA] NO, I DON'T WANT TO CHARGE YOU ANYTHING, PLEASE,
I DON'T WANT TO CHARGE YOU ANYTHING. I DON'T WANT YOU TO THINK
THAT I WANT NO KIND OF COMMITMENT,
THE MISTAKE WAS THAT I ACCEPTED YOUR BORROWED APARTMENT,
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING FROM YOU.
[TYPHOON] EVERYTHING IS OK BETWEEN US.
ARE WE NOT HAVING FUN? SPEAK UP.
[CARMINHA] YOU FEEL GUILTY BECAUSE...
FOR WHAT HAPPENED TO GENÉSIO,
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HERE WITH ME, ISN'T IT?
[TYPHOON] OH MY GOD, WHAT LOW SELF-ESTEEM IS THIS?
WHAT DO YOU THINK? DO YOU THINK I WAS
WHY DO I GO TO BED WITH YOU? OUT OF PITY?
[CARMINHA] YOU'D BETTER STOP HERE. PLEASE,
I BETTER STOP HERE, I NEED TO PUT
MY HEAD IS IN THE RIGHT PLACE, I HAVE A SON TO RAISE, PEOPLE,
I NEED TO FIND A WAY TO GET A JOB,
AND MAKE MONEY...
[TYPHOON] ACCEPT THIS HOUSE I'M GIVING YOU.
[CARMINHA] NO.
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA. CARMINHA.
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA, LOOK, JUST CALL THE BROKER,
IT'S ALL OK.
[CARMINHA] I CANNOT ACCEPT IT. AND NEXT WEEK
I'M LEAVING THE APARTMENT YOU LENT ME.
[TYPHOON] LET ME HELP YOU.
[CARMINHA] YOU'VE ALREADY HELPED ME A LOT, YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW MUCH. YOU SAVED ME. YOU GAVE ME A BREATH OF LIFE,
YOU GAVE ME THE WILL TO MOVE FORWARD, YOU WERE EVERYTHING TO ME,
EVERYTHING. YOU WERE A TRUE ANGEL TO ME.
[CARMINHA] GOODBYE.
[TYPHOON] WHAT IS THIS? WHAT THE HELL
"GOODBYE"? WHAT IS THIS?
[CARMINHA] I NEED TO STAY AWAY FROM YOU, I NEED TO.
SEE IF YOU UNDERSTAND ME, PLEASE, TRY TO FORGET ME, TRY.
[TYPHOON] WILL YOU BE ABLE TO FORGET ME?
[CARMINHA] IMPOSSIBLE.
[CARMINHA] I WILL NEVER FORGET YOU, NEVER.
[CARMINHA] I LOVE YOU.
[TYPHOON] LOOK, THIS WEEK IS NEW YEAR'S EVE, IT'S ENDING
THE MILLENNIUM IS BEGINNING, ANOTHER ONE, LET'S BREAK IN THE YEAR TOGETHER.
[CARMINHA] GOODBYE, LOVE.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[DOOR CLOSE]
[CARMINHA] "I NEED TO STAY AWAY FROM YOU, I NEED TO.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND? TRY TO FORGET ME."
[LAUGHTER] IDIOT! TOO MANY NAILS
THAT TYPHOON, NAIL!
[MAX] FUCK, "TYPHOON, TYPHOON, TYPHOON", DUDE, CARMINHA,
STOP IT, CHANGE THAT RECORD.
[CARMINHA] OK, SORRY. AND THE PHOTO, MAN?
SPEAK, AND THE PHOTO, DID IT TURN OUT GOOD?
[MAX] IT'S UP THERE ON THE KITCHEN COUNTER.
[STEPS]
[TELEVISION IN THE BACKGROUND]
[CARMINHA] SENSATIONAL! I LOOK GOOD IN THIS PHOTO, HUH?
OH, MAX, IT'S NOW. COME HERE, WAS IT IN THE DUMP?
DID YOU SEE HOW THAT PLAGUE RITA IS?
[MAX] VI. SHE FLEE FROM THE HOUSE OF THE NILE,
BUT HE ENDED UP AT LUCINDA'S HOUSE.
[CARMINHA] HUM, THIS IS NOT GOOD AT ALL.
[MAX] RELAX, MY PRINCESS, RELAX. RELAX,
THAT SHE WILL NEVER LEAVE THERE AGAIN.
HERE, THERE IS NOTHING TO EAT IN THIS HOUSE,
I HAD TO ORDER A PIZZA, HUH?
[TELEVISION IN THE BACKGROUND]
[CARMINHA] LOOK, I'LL TAKE GOOD CARE OF YOU, OK?
I WILL TAKE VERY WELL CARE OF YOU, YOU WERE VERY PATIENT,
THEN YOU DESERVE IT. BUT, HEY, THE EFFORT WILL BE WORTH IT, OK?
DO YOU WANT TO BET HOW MUCH TYPHOON WILL ASK ME TO MARRY HIM?
[MAX] WOW, TYPHOON AT MARRIAGE? I SAW THAT AT NIGHT
IT MUST HAVE BEEN WARM, RIGHT?
[CARMINHA] ON THE CONTRARY, I DIDN'T GO TO BED WITH HIM
AND IN THE END I SENT HIM AWAY.
[MAX] WHAT DO YOU MEAN? YOU MEAN
THAT YOU DISMISSED THE GUY?
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE, I SAID I WAS IN LOVE WITH HIM
THAT HE NEEDED TO STAY AWAY FROM ME SO I WOULD NOT SUFFER
MORE. I'VE FUCKED HIS MIND, WHAT DOES HE THINK NOW? THAT I AM
A SAINT, WHO DOESN'T WANT ANYTHING FROM HIM, WHO WILL RAISE HIS SON
FROM THE MAN HE RUN OVER, ALONE, WITHOUT A PENNY.
CAN YOU IMAGINE THE GUILT, RIGHT, GROWING, GROWING...
[MAX] NO, WAIT, TELL ME ONE THING, WHAT ABOUT THE MONEY?
WHAT WAS HE GOING TO GIVE US TO BUY THE HOUSE?
[CARMINHA] I REFUSED.
[MAX] CO... HOW DID YOU REFUSE, ARE YOU CRAZY, CARMINHA?
DON'T YOU REMEMBER THE OLD SAYING, DO YOU?
"A BIRD IN THE HAND IS WORTH MORE,
THAN TWO FLYING", GIRL?
[CARMINHA] MY BUSINESS IS TWO, THREE,
FOUR BIRDS, A FLOCK!
[CARMINHA] I DON'T WANT MUCH FROM LIFE, MAX,
HAVEN'T YOU GET IT YET? I WANT IT ALL, HUH? [LAUGHTER]
AND HOW MUCH TO BET? NEW YEAR'S EVE HE'LL LOOK FOR ME.
♪SHE'S MY WIFE'S FRIEND♪
♪YES, YES, YES♪
♪BUT HE KEEPS COMING ON TO ME♪
♪FINALLY, FINALLY♪
[MURICY] YOU LOOK GREAT, SON, YOUR SKIN IS GOOD.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE WEEKEND WAS FULL OF FUN, RIGHT?
OH, SAY, HOW WAS IT WITH CARMINHA?
[TYPHOON] NO, NOTHING LIKE YOU SAID HAPPENED
ARE YOU THINKING. SHE DOESN'T WANT ANYTHING TO DO WITH ME!
[IVANA] OH, WHAT A LIAR MY BROTHER IS, HUH?
BECAUSE THAT'S NOT WHAT THIS PHOTO IN THE NEWSPAPER SAYS.
[TYPHOON] WHO WAS THE BASTARD WHO TOOK THIS PICTURE?
[MURICY] WAS A "PAPARAZZO", HE IS THE ITALIAN PHOTOGRAPHER, RIGHT,
THAT IS BEHIND CELEBRITIES. IVANA EXPLAINED IT TO ME.
[IVANA] EXACTLY, MOTHER,
"PAPARAZZO".
WHO TOLD YOU TO BE FAMOUS?
[TYPHOON] MY GOD, CARMINHA ISN'T EVEN A MONTH AGO
WIDOW AND SHE ALREADY APPEARS IN THE NEWSPAPER WITH ME. THIS IS BAD FOR HER.
[IVANA] HUM. COME HERE, IT'S TRUE THAT SHE DIDN'T ACCEPT THAT HOUSE
WHAT DID YOU PROMISE HER?
[TYPHOON] SHE DOESN'T WANT ANYTHING FROM ME.
[MURICY] YES, OF COURSE. SHE'S A WORTHY WOMAN, RIGHT, IVANA? WORTHY.
YOU ARE A SPECIAL PERSON, DID YOU KNOW THERE ARE STILL A FEW
OF THESE IN THE WORLD? AND THE DAMN THING STILL HAS CLASS,
IT WAS MISS BANGU, IS THAT OK FOR YOU? IT'S NOT FOR EVERYONE, NO.
GO AFTER HER, SON, GO.
[MURICY] IT'S WORTH INSISTING. IT'S YOUR OBLIGATION TO GO THERE NOW,
OFFER HER HELP, SUPPORT, ALL THE STRENGTH YOU CAN GIVE.
LISTEN TO WHAT YOUR MOTHER IS SAYING, I HAVE A SIXTH SENSE, SON.
GO THERE.
♪I'LL WAIT FOR YOU HERE♪
♪BUT MAKE SURE YOU ANSWER THE PHONE♪
♪EVEN IF I HAVE TO CHARGE♪
♪TODAY I'M NOT GOING OUT♪
♪WHY IS MY CAR BROKEN♪
♪I CAN'T SPEND ANYTHING♪
♪WHEN YOU GET HERE♪
♪GIVE ME A SHOUT UP FRONT♪
♪I'LL COME RUNNING TO FIND YOU♪
♪THERE'S NOBODY HERE♪
[ADAUTO] NO, NO, YOU DON'T NEED TO BOTHER WITH AN ENVELOPE, NO,
I'M GOING TO... I'M GOING TO TAKE IT IN MY HAND.
♪I ALREADY GAVE YOU MY CELL PHONE♪
♪AND THE ADDRESS♪
♪FROM THAT DAY♪
[ADAUTO] THANK YOU! THAT'S ALL, RIGHT?
♪I KNOW YOU♪
[ADAUTO] COME ON, GUYS! LET'S DRINK, LET'S EAT,
LET'S HAVE FUN, BECAUSE WHEN IT'S MIDNIGHT, THE WORLD WILL END
SAME. THE WORLD IS GOING TO END, AND THEN YOU KNOW WHAT WILL HAPPEN?
IT WILL RAIN FIRE FROM THE SKY, METEOR OF FIRE.
[SILAS] NO, NO, NO, NO, NO. STOP, PEOPLE! STOP, STOP,
GIVE IT BACK, IT'S BETTER. GIVE THIS BACK, GIRL!
GIVE IT BACK HERE. STOP, STOP, STOP, STOP.
[TALK]
[SILAS] STOP, STOP. GIVE THIS BACK HERE... GIVE THIS BACK HERE,
YOU KID! GO AWAY, GO AWAY. ADAUTO, WHAT'S THIS?
ARE YOU CRAZY? ARE YOU CRAZY?
[ADAUTO] CRAZY, NO! CRAZY, NO, SILAS. CRAZY, NO,
THAT THE PLANET... THE PLANET WILL END AT MIDNIGHT.
IT WILL END AND WE WILL DIE, SILAS!
[SILAS] GO, GO, PEOPLE, IT'S OVER. THIS IS OVER, IT'S OVER!
GO, GO, GO! GO DO SOMETHING, GO!
NO, IT'S NOT COMING, NO. IT'S NOT COMING, NO.
[BUS ENGINE]
[TELEVISION IN THE BACKGROUND]
[MONALISA] UNCLE LUIZ PORANGA?
[MONALISA] IT'S ME, MONALISA.
[PORANGA] MY DEAR NIECE! [LAUGHTER]
BRIDE OF THE TYPHOON, THE GREAT TYPHOON. DID HE COME?
[MAN] LET'S GO INSIDE, DAMN, WE'RE FULL OF NEWS
TO TELL YOU. AND DOVALINA, MY OLD GIRL, WHERE ARE YOU, HUH? [LAUGHTER]
[WOMAN] EVERYTHING IS OK HERE ON COPACABANA BEACH,
FOR THE NEW YEAR'S EVE, THE CENTURY, THE MILLENNIUM SHOW! THE FORECAST
MORE THAN A MILLION PEOPLE ATTEND THE PARTY.
♪EVERYBODY SWING♪
♪FROM THE WOMAN FROM RIO DE JANEIRO♪
[IVANA] SO, TODAY IS THE DAY I'M GETTING READY, OLENKA.
[OLENKA] [LAUGHTER]
[IVANA] OH GOD, IF YOU FIND ME A BOYFRIEND
TONIGHT... [LAUGHTER] I SWEAR I WILL NEVER EAT SWEETS AGAIN
IN MY LIFE! NO, I EVEN CUT OUT THE SWEETENER IN MY COFFEE,
I'LL CUT IT, PLEASE, GOD, PLEASE. [EXTENDED] OH!
OH THERE, OH THERE. [LAUGHTER] I WAS LOOKING AT US. COME ON, COME ON.
[TALK]
[TYPHOON] WAIT, WAIT, WAIT. HAPPY NEW YEAR. HAPPY NEW YEAR.
[MAN] IS IT TRUE THAT YOU ENDED AN ENGAGEMENT?
[TYPHOON] HEY PEOPLE, TODAY IS NEW YEAR'S EVE, TODAY IS NEW YEAR'S EVE,
GIVE ME A BREAK, GIVE ME A BREAK.
[CRUCIBLE] HAPPY NEW YEAR, HAPPY NEW YEAR, HEALTH. LIVE!
[VERÔNICA] EXCUSE ME, I'M GOING TO STEAL MY HUSBAND.
[CADINHO] NO, IMAGINE, YOU DON'T NEED TO STEAL. SPEAK, LOVE.
[SIGH] EXCUSE ME.
[VERÔNICA] HI, I'M SO GLAD YOU CAME.
[CRUITLING] HAPPY NEW YEAR.
[VERÔNICA] HAPPY NEW YEAR TO YOU.
[CADINHO] FEEL FREE, OK?
[VERÔNICA] YES, MAKE YOURSELF COME, OK? GET A DRINK.
[CADINHO] IT WASN'T A GREAT IDEA TO HAVE NEW YEAR'S EVE
HERE AT THE HOTEL, HUH?
[VERÔNICA] IT WAS GREAT, LOVE, GREAT. LOOK WHO'S THERE ALONE,
MARCO AURÉLIO. MAKE A ROOM FOR HIM, GO ON.
[CRUCIBLE] MARCUS AURELIUS.
[VERONICA] BEAUTIFUL DRESS.
[WOMAN] DID YOU LIKE IT?
[VERÔNICA] BEAUTIFUL, IS IT IMPORTED?
[WOMAN] Yes.
[VERÔNICA] OH, I GET IT.
[ALEXIA] HI.
[VERÔNICA] ALEXIA. IT'S GREAT THAT YOU'RE HERE.
[ALEXIA] EVERYTHING OK?
[VERÔNICA] DIDN'T YOU GO TO NEW YORK AFTER ALL?
[ALEXIA] OH, NO. IT TURNED OUT AT THE LAST MINUTE,
AT THE LAST MINUTE I GAVE UP.
[VERÔNICA] OH, LUCKY ME. YOU DON'T KNOW MY HUSBAND,
DO YOU KNOW?
[ALEXIA] NOT YET.
[VERÔNICA] WELL, ALMOST NOBODY KNOWS IT, RIGHT, LOVE?
HE DOESN'T STAY HOME, BUT TODAY IS NEW YEAR'S EVE,
IF HE DOESN'T SHOW UP IT'S A DIVORCE. I'LL INTRODUCE YOU,
YOU'LL LIKE HIM. I DON'T KNOW WHERE HE'S GONE,
HE ALWAYS DISAPPEARS WHEN I NEED HIM.AH, HE'S THERE,
CRUCIBLE. CRUCIBLE. CRUCIBLE!
[ALEXIA] VERONICA.
[VERONICA] HI.
[ALEXIA] ARE YOU MARRIED TO THAT GUY OVER THERE?
[VERÔNICA] LOVE, IT'S BEEN ALMOST TEN YEARS. WHY, DO YOU KNOW HIM?
[ALEXIA] NO, I DON'T KNOW, NO.
[VERÔNICA] HUM! YOU'LL LOVE IT, I'LL INTRODUCE YOU. CADINHO.
CADINHO, I'M CALLING YOU, LOVE. WELL, WHERE ARE YOU?
[CRUCIBLE] SPEAK, LOVE OF MY LIFE, SPEAK.
[KISS SNAP]
[VERÔNICA] I WAS GOING TO INTRODUCE YOU TO A FRIEND, BUT I DON'T KNOW, SHE DISAPPEARED.
[CRUCIBLE] SOON, SOON, YOU INTRODUCE ME. LOOK,
BECAUSE I'M GOING TO HAVE TO GO DOWN QUICKLY NOW
BECAUSE I FORGOT TO BUY POMEGRANATE. [LAUGHTER]
[VERONICA] WHAT POMEGRANATE, CRUCIBLE?
[CADINHO] I'M SERIOUS.
[VERÔNICA] POMEGRANATE AT THIS TIME, IT'S ALMOST MIDNIGHT, LOVE.
[CRUITLING] BUT POMEGRANATE SEEDS BRING LUCK, MY FATHER TAUGHT ME SO.
I HAVENT SPENT A SINGLE NEW YEAR'S EVE WITHOUT POMEGRANATE SEEDS.
[VERÔNICA] STOP THIS NONSENSE, IT WON'T WORK... FOR CADINHO.
I WANTED A WAITER, GUYS, WHERE IS HE?
♪GOD PROTECT ME♪
♪OF YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME♪
♪FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
♪GOD HELP ME FROM YOUR ANGER♪
♪GOD IMMUNIZES ME♪
♪OF YOUR POISON♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR END♪
♪GOD PROTECT ME FROM YOUR ENVY♪
♪GOD DEFEND ME♪
♪FROM YOUR MACUMBA♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR PLAGUE♪
♪GOD HELP ME FROM YOUR ANGER♪
♪GOD IMMUNIZES ME♪
♪OF YOUR POISON♪
♪GOD SAVE ME FROM YOUR END♪
♪GOD GOD GO WITH ME♪
♪GOD SUPPORT ME♪
♪GOD LIFT ME UP♪
♪GOD GIVE ME STRENGTH♪
♪GOD FORGIVE ME FOR WANTING TO♪
♪GOD SAVE ME♪
♪AND KEEP IT FROM YOU♪
[PANTING BREATHING]
[CRUCIBLE] HAPPY NEW YEAR!
[CLEARING]
[CRUCIBLE] MY LITTLE FLOWER OF THE FIELD.
[NOÊMIA] WHERE WERE YOU, DUDU?
[ALEXIA] ANOTHER ONE?
[NOÊMIA] WHAT'S THIS? YOU'RE ALL SWEATY.
[CROUCH] NO, NO, IT'S A LITTLE Trick I DO.
EVERY TURN OF A DECADE CLIMB TEN FLIGHTS OF STAIRS
TO HAVE TEN YEARS OF LUCK, MY FATHER TAUGHT ME.
[NOEMIA] FEZINHA?
[CRUCIBLE] Yes.
[NOÊMIA] YOU'RE BEING STRANGE, YOU'RE BEING VERY STRANGE.
[CADINHO] NO, IT'S OK, YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL, HUH?
[THOMÁS] FATHER, FATHER!
[CADINHO] HI. WHAT'S UP, SON?
[ALEXIA] "SONY"?
[CADINHO] SO, HAVE YOU HAD DINNER?
[THOMAS] NO.
[CRUCIBLE] NO?
[NOÊMIA] GO TO DINNER NOW BECAUSE IT'S AFTER MIDNIGHT
IT'S GOING TO BE A MESS. COME, COME, COME, TOMÁS.
[LAUGHTER] YOU WON'T GET OUT OF THERE.
[CADINHO] I'M NOT GOING TO LEAVE, NO.
[NOÊMIA] [LAUGHTER] TOMAS!
[CRUCIBLE] [CLEARING]
[ALEXIA] SO, ARE YOU NOT GOING TO INTRODUCE ME TO THE FAMILY?
[CRUCIBLE] ALEXIA?
[ALEXIA] OR RATHER, THE FAMILIES, RIGHT?
[CRUCIBLE] LOOK, I CAN EXPLAIN. LOOK...
[ALEXIA] YOU'RE A PSYCHOPATH!
HOW CAN A MAN
WHO SAYS HE LOVES ME, WHO SWEARS ETERNAL LOVE TO ME, BEYOND EVERYTHING BEING
A MARRIED MAN AND FATHER OF A FAMILY. OR RATHER, OF FAMILIES,
RIGHT? YES, BECAUSE JUST HERE IN THIS BUILDING THERE ARE THREE FAMILIES, THREE!
HOW MANY ARE THERE, ACTUALLY? HOW MANY ARE THERE? [WHISPERING] EIGHT? EIGHT?
[CADINHO] DON'T EXAGGERATE, RIGHT? ONLY THREE,
INCLUDING YOU NOW.
[ALEXIA] ENOUGH! I WILL STOP YOU.
[CRUCIBLE] WHAT'S IT LIKE?
[ALEXIA] YES, I WILL SAVE THESE WOMEN,
I WILL FREE THOSE POOR YOU!
[CRUILT] NO, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD... DON'T DO IT, DON'T DO IT!
JUST TONIGHT, JUST TONIGHT. LOOK, TOMORROW MORNING WE'LL
TALK, BUT FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, DON'T DO IT HERE IN FRONT OF US
FROM EVERYONE. IT WILL BE A PUBLIC DISGRACE, UNDERSTAND?
FOR THIS SON, FOR OUR SON WHO IS THERE IN YOUR BELLY.
YOU WANT HIM TO GROW UP HEARING THAT HIS FATHER WAS HUMILIATED,
HUMILIATED LIKE THIS IN PUBLIC,
RIGHT ON NEW YEAR'S EVE YOU WANT THIS, HUH?
TELL ME, DO YOU WANT THIS?
[ALEXIA] OH, PEOPLE, EXCUSE ME,
I HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT TO MAKE...
[THOMAS] FATHER... FATHER...
[CADINHO] SPEAK, SPEAK, SPEAK, WHAT'S WRONG?
[TOMÁS] WHAT IS THAT PRAYER YOU SAY BEFORE SUPPER LIKE?
NEW YEAR'S EVE? I PROMISE, I SWEAR...
[CRUILT] REPEAT WITH DADDY, REPEAT. I PROMISE
THINK MORE ABOUT OTHERS AND LESS ABOUT MYSELF IN THE YEAR THAT IS ABOUT TO COME.
[TOMÁS] I PROMISE TO THINK MORE ABOUT OTHERS AND LESS ABOUT MYSELF
IN THE YEAR THAT WILL BE BORN.
[CADINHO] I PROMISE TO TRY ON MY PROJECTS
AND NEVER GIVE UP ON MY DREAMS IN THE YEAR THAT IS ABOUT TO COME.
[TOMÁS] I PROMISE TO TRY ON MY PROJECTS
[TOGETHER]AND NEVER GIVE UP ON MY DREAMS
IN THE YEAR THAT WILL BE BORN.
[CALDER] HEY, BOY! GO WITH MOMMY, GO.
[ALEXIA] It's...
[CADINHO] COME WITH ME, LET'S TALK OUTSIDE, COME.
COME WITH ME. SHH! CALM DOWN.
[MONALISA] [ECHOEDING VOICE] IT'S OVER, TYPHOON!
[TYPHOON] [ECHOEDING VOICE] IT'S NOT OVER, IT'S NOT OVER,
WE WILL GET MARRIED AND WE WILL BE HAPPY
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU, UNDERSTAND?
[MONALISA] [ECHOED VOICE] YOU WON'T, BECAUSE I DON'T LOVE YOU ANYMORE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] [ECHOED VOICE] TRY TO FORGET ME, TRY.
[TYPHOON] [ECHOING VOICE] WILL YOU EVER BE ABLE TO FORGET ME?
[CARMINHA] [ECHOED VOICE] I LOVE YOU.
[SILAS] WHAT'S UP, TYPHOON? [LAUGHTER]
WHAT IS THIS DEPRESSION, TYPHOON?
NEW YEAR, NEW LIFE, BOY. LOOK AT THIS,
THINK YOU'RE NOT OFFSIDE, DRIBBLE THE GOALKEEPER,
PUT A HAT ON IT AND GO TO THE GOAL, KID! [LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
[SILAS] BUT WAIT, WAIT, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HAPPY NEW YEAR, TYPHOON! [LAUGHTER]
[MAX] HEY, MY HOT GIRL, PUT ON SOME COOL OUTFIT,
LET'S GO TO COPACABANA TO WATCH NEW YEAR'S EVE...
LET'S WATCH THE FIREWORKS, MILLENNIUM NEW YEAR'S EVE.
[CARMINHA] GO AWAY, MAX. IN FACT, YOU SHOULD HAVE GONE ALREADY,
THE TYPHOON WILL APPEAR AT ANY MOMENT.
[MAX] OH, FORGET ABOUT IT. HEY CARMINHA, STOP IT,
FORGET ABOUT THIS GUY, HE'S NOT GOING TO COME AT ALL, DUDE.
[CARMINHA] WANT TO BET HOW MUCH HE COMES?
[MAX] NO, LET'S DO THIS, IT'S COOLER,
LOOK, THINK WITH ME, WE'RE GOING INSIDE THE MOTEL,
THE TWO OF US, WE DO THAT DELICIOUS LITTLE THING
THAT YOU KNOW I DO...
[CARMINHA] GET OUT OF HERE.
[MAX] STOP IT. YOU WANT ME TO GO, DO YOU?
I'LL GO, IF YOU WANT I'LL GO, BUT FIRST YOU'LL PAY ME
A GIFT, THAT LITTLE GIFT...
[JUMBLE]
THE LAST OF THE MILLENNIUM, GO, GO.
[IMPACT ON THE CLOSET]
[KNOCKING ON THE DOOR]
[CARMINHA] RUN, MAX, RUN. GET YOUR THINGS AND GET OUT OF HERE!
STAY IN THE AREA, STAY IN THE AREA.
[STEPS]
[KNOCKING ON THE DOOR]
[CARMINHA] JUST A MINUTE.
[STEPS]
[DOOR OPEN]
[CARMINHA] TYPHOON.
[TYPHOON] CAN I COME IN?
[CARMINHA] WE AGREED...
OH, COME IN.
[STEPS]
[DOOR CLOSE]
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA, AFTER EVERYTHING WE SAID I...
I WAS THINKING AND I THINK IT'S NOT FOR NOTHING
THAT WE ARE SPENDING THE TURN OF THE MILLENNIUM TOGETHER.
I THINK IT WAS MEANT TO HAPPEN,
I THINK THE TIME HAS COME. HERE WE GO...
CARMINH...
[CARMINHA] HUH?
[TYPHOON] WILL YOU MARRY ME?
I WANT TO TAKE CARE OF THIS KID IN YOUR BELLY
AS IF HE WAS MINE.
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[TYPHOON] I WILL MAKE YOU THE HAPPIEST WOMAN IN THE WORLD,
TRUST ME, WE'RE GOING TO BE A NICE COUPLE.
GENÉSIO, UP THERE, WILL BE HAPPY...
[CARMINHA] FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, DON'T SAY THINGS LIKE THAT,
DON'T TALK NONSENSE, DON'T TORTURE ME.
[TYPHOON] WHY? DON'T YOU WANT ME? DIDN'T YOU SAY YOU LOVE ME? HUH?
[CARMINHA] IT SOUNDS LIKE A DREAM. IT'S EVERYTHING I WANTED TO HEAR
IN MY LIFE. IT SEEMS LIKE THIS ISN'T HAPPENING.
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA, DREAM, DREAM TOGETHER IS REALITY. HUM?
[CARMINHA] I'M AFRAID... I'M AFRAID THAT YOU'LL CHANGE
IN AN IDEA, I'M AFRAID TO BELIEVE AND GO DOWN THE DRAIN,
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, DON'T DO THIS TO ME, I'VE ALREADY SUFFERED TOO MUCH,
I CANNOT SUFFER.
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA, TRUST ME THAT I WILL NOT GO BACK.
I WILL TAKE YOU TO THE DIVINE, I WILL INTRODUCE YOU AS
MY GIRLFRIEND, MY FUTURE WIFE FOR EVERYONE.
LET'S SPEND THIS NEW YEAR'S EVE TOGETHER, THIS IS A LOT, THIS WILL
TO BE JUST THE FIRST OF MANY, FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
[TYPHOON] GO ON, GO ON. GO PUT ON SOME CLOTHES, YOU'LL LOOK PRETTY,
UNDERSTAND? LET'S GO TO THE PARTY, LET'S WATCH THE FIREWORKS WITH ME. HUM?
[CALMIN] CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN, COME HERE, LET'S TALK,
ALEXIA, LET'S TALK.
[ALEXIA] LET ME GO! WHAT IS THIS? YOU'RE A PERVERT,
YOU ARE A PSYCHOPATH.
[CRUITLING] ALEXIA, LISTEN TO ME. I LOVE YOU THREE.
I LOVE ALL MY CHILDREN.
[CRUNCHING] THE ONES I ALREADY HAVE.
[CADINHO] AND THE ONES I WILL STILL HAVE. I ALWAYS TOOK CARE OF
EVERYONE, I NEVER LET ANYONE LACK ANYTHING.
[CADINHO] I WILL BE A GOOD HUSBAND FOR YOU TOO.
[ALEXIA] STOP, STOP, STOP, WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU LIVE,
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD? DO YOU THINK YOU'RE LIVING IN A HAREM?
[CRUCIBLE] LISTEN.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[CALMIN] JUST A MINUTE. NOÊMIA? HI, LOVE. CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN,
I CAME HERE TO JUMP THE SEVEN WAVES. OF COURSE, I ALWAYS JUMP FIRST
AT MIDNIGHT, YOU KNOW THAT AT THE TIME OF THE CHANGE OF CHRISTMAS IT IS IMPOSSIBLE,
THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE. OK, IN FIVE MINUTES
I'M HERE, KISS, BYE.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[CRUCIBLE] VERONICA! HI, LOVE, CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN, LOVE. I... I,
I ALREADY GOT THE POMEGRANATE SEEDS, YES, I'M AT THE DOOR
FROM THE ELEVATOR, I'LL BE THERE IN A MOMENT, KISS.
[ALEXIA] I'M SO UNLUCKY. LOOK, I'M SO UNLUCKY
LUCKY. WHERE DID I TIE MY DONKEY, MY GOD?
NOW ME... WHY? HONESTLY, WHY?
[CADINHO] DON'T WORRY, EVERYTHING WILL BE OK, I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT
FROM YOU, SEE? I WILL MAKE YOU VERY HAPPY, I SWEAR.
♪GOD FORGIVE ME FOR WANTING TO♪
♪GOD SAVE ME♪
♪KEEP IT FROM YOU♪
♪GOD SAVE ME, KEEP ME FROM YOU♪
[MAN] ATTENTION...
[MONALISA] [EXTENDED] HEY, LOOK!
[LAUGHTER] TO YOU, MY FAMILY.
AND TO MY IRAN, MY NEW SON.
[CLICKING GLASSES]
[MAN] AND TYPHOON, YOUR GROOM? WHY DOESN'T HE COME?
I SO WANTED TO MEET OUR CHAMPION.
[HATES] HE DIDN'T COME BECAUSE HIS NIECE IS A FOOL
AND SHE LET THE MAN IN HER LIFE SLIP AWAY.
[MONALISA] AUNT, PLEASE DON'T START. IT'S A PARTY DAY,
LOOKING FORWARD, NOT BACKWARDS AT WHAT HAS PASSED,
THIS IS A PAGE TURNED.
[MAN] YOUR COUSIN IS MORE THAN RIGHT. LOOK HERE,
HAVE YOU SEEN THIS? IT'S THERE FOR EVERYONE TO SEE. TYPHOON IN A
DESERTED BEACH, WITH A MYSTERIOUS GIRL IN THE MOST NAUGHTY WAY.
[MONALISA] [SNIFFLING] SO IT'S TRUE?
[CARMINHA] ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO COME IN THERE WITH ME?
INTRODUCE ME TO EVERYONE AS YOUR GIRLFRIEND? YOU'RE NOT
BEING TOO PRECIPITATE? YOU WON'T REGRET IT LATER?
[TYPHOON] I'M SURE, ARE YOU SURE?
IT'S ALL I WANT MOST IN LIFE.
[KISS SNAP]
[TYPHOON] LET'S GO?
[DIOGENES] [LAUGHTER] LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, DEAR FRIENDS
OF OUR DIVINE FOOTBALL CLUB, WHO CAME HERE TO
CELEBRATING OUR NEW YEAR'S EVE!
AND IT IS WITH EMOTION THAT I COMMUNICATE
TO YOU WHO ARE ONE MINUTE LEFT UNTIL THE YEAR 2000!
[CHRIES OF CELEBRATION]
[DIOGENES] HERE WE GO!
[ADALTO] OH MY GOD IN HEAVEN!
ONE MINUTE UNTIL THE WORLD END!
GOODBYE, MURICY!
[MURICY] MY GOD, AND AT THIS TIME THE TYPHOON DOESN'T APPEAR, MY GOD.
DID YOU CALL HIS CELL PHONE?
[IVANA] GUYS, WHERE'S MY BROTHER? IT'S ONE MINUTE LEFT UNTIL NEW YEAR!
[MURICY] I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T KNOW, HE DISAPPEARED,
HE DIDN'T GIVE ANY NEWS! HE'S NEVER DONE THIS, IT'S THE FIRST TIME.
[DIOGENES] WHERE... WHERE IS THE TYPHOON, MY GOD IN HEAVEN?
DID HE CALL, DID HE GIVE YOU ANY NEWS?
[MURICY] NOTHING, NOTHING, NOTHING, NOTHING.
[DIOGENES] MY GOD IN HEAVEN, COUNCILMAN SILVEIRINHA FONTOURA
IS THERE TO TAKE A PICTURE WITH HIM! NOT ONLY HIM,
THE SPONSOR... THE SPONSOR IS ALSO THERE, THE PHOTOGRAPHERS...
[LELECO] IT'S HERE! IT'S HERE!
[MURICY] OH MY GOD! THANK GOD!
[TALK]
[MAN] TYPHOON, TYPHOON, IS THAT YOUR NEW GIRLFRIEND?
[TYPHOON] NO, THAT'S NOT MY NEW GIRLFRIEND,
THIS IS MY FUTURE WIFE.
[COMMOTION]
[MAN] WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
[CARMINHA] CARMEN LUCIA MOREIRA DE SOUZA.
[MAN] ATTENTION, MY PEOPLE, THE TIME IS COMING.
I'M GOING TO SET OFF THE FIREWORKS.
[MAN] COUNTDOWN!
[TOGETHER] TEN! NINE! EIGHT! SEVEN!
SIX! FIVE! FOUR! THREE!
TWO! ONE! HAPPY NEW YEAR!
[FIREWORKS EXPLOSION]
[WOMAN] [LAUGHTER] HAPPY NEW YEAR!
[MONALISA] HAPPY NEW YEAR, MY LITTLE ANGEL.
[IRAN] HAPPY NEW YEAR MY NEW MOTHER.
[MONALISA] [LAUGHTER] FROM HERE ON,
LIFE WILL GET A LOT BETTER, YOU SEE? YOU'LL SEE.
[MAN] AND THEN, DID YOU SEE? DID YOU SEE THE FIREWORKS, DID YOU SEE?
[WOMAN] WELCOME, OK?
[LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] HAPPY NEW YEAR.
[CHRIES OF CELEBRATION]
[MURICY] AH! MY LOVE, HAPPY NEW YEAR!
[LELECO] MY SON, MY SON.
[MURICY] HAPPY NEW YEAR, DEAR! OH! THIS ONE,
LOOK, IT'S LELECO, YOUR FATHER-IN-LAW. HEY!
[CARMINHA] I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY, IT'S SO MUCH EMOTION.
[LELECO] WELCOME TO OUR FAMILY, RIGHT? [LAUGHTER]
[IVANA] SISTER-IN-LAW! HI, SISTER-IN-LAW!
[LAUGHTER]
[MURICY] OH, MY LOVE, LET'S GO FOR A WALK...
[LUCINDA] HAPPY NEW YEAR!
[CHRIES OF CELEBRATION]
[LUCINDA] HAPPY NEW YEAR! HAPPY NEW YEAR!
MY LOVE, HAPPY NEW YEAR!
[LUCINDA] OH, MY LOVE!
[POTATO] HAPPY NEW YEAR, MOTHER LUCINDA.
[LUCINDA] FOR YOU TOO, MY LOVE. AND YOU, MY PRINCESS!
YOU ARRIVE VERY HAPPY, VERY HAPPY. GIVE ME A HUG.
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH! AND, OH, DON'T YOU FORGET ONE THING THAT I
I TOLD YOU: THE HEART IS NOT A PLACE TO KEEP HATE.
DO YOU PROMISE YOU'LL NEVER FORGET THIS?
[RITA] OK, MOTHER LUCINDA, I PROMISE.
[LUCINDA] OH, MY LOVE! THEN LET'S DANCE, LET'S DANCE.
COME, LET'S DANCE.
[BETANIA] WOW, RITA, IT'S Fancy, HUH?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING LIKE THIS, ALL DRESSED UP?
[RITA] I'M GOING TO GO OUT. DO YOU KNOW IF THERE'S A BUS?
FROM HERE TO MARACANÃ?
[BETANIA] WAIT, LET ME SEE.
113. BUT WHAT IS THAT
ARE YOU GOING TO DO IT AT MARACANÃ?
[RITA] I'M GOING TO TELL THE PLAYER EVERYTHING. LOOK HERE.
[STEPS]
[RITA] IT SAYS HERE THAT MY WITCH STEPMOTHER IS GOING TO COME TO
MARRY THIS TYPHOON.
SHE WILL DO THE SAME THING SHE DID WITH MY FATHER, THE SAME.
HE WILL END UP DYING. I WON'T LET HIM.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY PACE♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK IT♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
.