[SILENCE]
[RITA] I HAVE TO FIND THIS PLAYER, BETÂNIA.
I HAVE TO TELL HIM THAT HIS BRIDE IS A WITCH!
THAT SHE STOLE MY FATHER AND STOLE ME.
[BETANIA] YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING, THE PLAYER COULD BE HER FRIEND.
MAYBE HE'S BAD TOO.
[RITA] NO, IT'S NOT! CARMINHA IS DECEIVING HIM, SHE DIDN'T EVEN DO IT
WITH MY FATHER. I'M GOING TO MARACANÃ.
[BETANIA] THEY DON'T LET CHILDREN IN
ALONE AT MARACANÃ.
[RITA] I CAN FIND MYSELF!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RITA] GUY, STOP THE BUS!
[RITA] STOP THE BUS! STOP!
TO!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[RITA] STOP! STOPPED!
[CARMINHA] UGLY BUSINESS. DO YOU THINK IT'S GOOD LIKE THIS OR SHOULD BE?
PUT SOMETHING ELSE, HUH? THESE TEAM SHIRTS ARE SO UGLY.
[MAX] FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, THAT'S ALL I NEEDED,
HELP YOU GET DRESSED TO GO OUT WITH YOUR MAN.
[CARMINHA] FOR MY MAN, NO, MY LOVE, FOR THE MAGAZINES,
FOR NEWSPAPERS, FOR BRAZIL. [LAUGHTER]
COME HERE, HELP ME CUT IT
THAT NECKLINE, LET'S SEE IF IT IMPROVES IT A LITTLE.
[MAX] HEY, CAN I TELL YOU JUST A QUICK STOP?
[CARMINHA] HUM?
[MAX] HERE, CRAZY, YOU'RE GOING TO A SOCCER GAME,
IT'S NOT A SAMBA SCHOOL BOX, NO, HEY. ME, HUH?
[CARMINHA] LEAVE IT TO ME, EVERYTHING IS GOING TO BE FINE.
THE DUCK ALREADY ASKED ME TO MARRY HIM. NOW YOU'RE GOING TO GET IT
HIS SISTER'S LITTLE BUZZER.
[MAX] WHAT'S UP? WHAT... WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
[CARMINHA] YOUR FUTURE BRIDE, IVANA.
[MAX] [LAUGHTER] THAT WAS THE BEST OF THE DAY,
YOU'RE REALLY CRAZY, ARE YOU, DEAR?
[CARMINHA] LISTEN TO WHAT I'M SAYING, MY LOVE,
TYPHOON HEARS HIS SISTER. SHE HAS ACCESS TO HIS BANK ACCOUNT.
AND WHAT DOES THE CUTE WANTS MOST? A HUSBAND. IF YOU CAN GET HIM OUT OF THE WAY
THAT BOAT, WE SURROUND THEM ON ALL SIDES,
AND WE STILL STAY CLOSE TO EACH OTHER.
[MAX] HUM, AH... CONGRATULATIONS. PLANASSO, VERY GOOD, PERFECT!
I LOSE MY WIFE, I STILL KILL HER IN THE CHEST
THAT BIG BULL, WONDERFUL.
[CARMINHA] FIRST, YOU WILL NEVER LOSE ME, AND SECOND,
THAT I AM SACRIFICED SO AS NOT TO SPEND THE REST OF MY LIFE
EATING YELLOW EGG IN A BAR. SO MAKE A LITTLE EFFORT, OK?
[MAX] IT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
[CARMINHA] YOU'LL CHANGE YOUR MIND, I KNOW.
[LUCINDA] HEY, KIDS, TAKE A BREAK,
LET'S TAKE A REST, GET SOME WATER. EVERYONE COME HERE.
HELLO, HERE WE GO. [LAUGHTER] VERY GOOD, VERY GOOD. WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT. GUYS, WHERE'S RITA? WHERE'S... GUYS, WHERE'S RITA?
HAS ANYONE SEEN RITA? MY GOD, COULD NI...
[BETANIA] CALM DOWN, LUCINDA, CALM DOWN. THE NILE DIDN'T GET HER, NO.
[LUCINDA] WHERE IS SHE? TELL ME, WHERE IS RITA, GIRL?
IT WON'T MAKE ME NERVOUS.
[BETANIA] I DON'T KNOW, MOTHER LUCINDA.
[LUCINDA] HOW DO YOU NOT KNOW? YOU DON'T KNOW THAT THE NILE
DIDN'T YOU GET RITA? YOU WON'T... DON'T MAKE ME NERVOUS,
WHERE IS RITA?
[BETÂNIA] SHE WENT TO MARACANÃ, THAT'S IT, I SAID.
[LUCINDA] WHAT?
[BETANIA] SHE SAID SHE SAW A PHOTO OF A SOCCER PLAYER,
WITH A WOMAN IN THE NEWSPAPER, AND SAID HE WAS GOING THERE.
[LUCINDA] TAKE CARE OF YOUR BROTHERS
THAT I WILL GO AFTER HER.
[BETANY] OK.
[LUCINDA] MY GOD.
[IVANA] THERE! [LAUGHTER]
[CARMINHA] I CAN'T GET USED TO IT
PRESS HARASSMENT.
[IVANA] OH, ME, I LOVE IT. I WANT MORE TO BE SEEN,
MY DAUGHTER, AND VERY SEEN, THAT IS TO SEE IF
SOMEONE SEES ME, RIGHT?
[MURICY] YOU WOULDN'T EVEN GET ON A MAGAZINE COVER,
YOU CAN GET OUT OF IT, MY DAUGHTER.
[LELECO] OH MURICY, IS THAT ANY WAY TO TALK ABOUT OUR DAUGHTER?
[MURICY] YES, NO... SHE HAS A... TALENT FOR GETTING A MAN,
THAT IS AN IMPRESSIVE THING. IT WILL END UP IN CARITÓ THIS
GIRL, LISTEN. NOW, YOU, YOUR WEDDING PARTY,
BUT IT WILL BE A CLOSING ONE! I ALREADY MADE MY GUEST LIST,
OH, HUGE, I'M WAITING FOR YOURS.
[CARMINHA] AH, I HAVE NOBODY
TO INVITE, NO, MURICY.
[MURICY] WHAT IS THIS?
[CARMINHA] ONLY ABOUT TEN PEOPLE. MURICY, I WOULD BE HAPPY
IF I COULD INVITE ONE VERY SPECIAL PERSON, IT WOULD BE HIM
HE WAS A GREAT FRIEND OF GENÉSIO, I THINK OF HIM LIKE A BROTHER.
[MURICY] IMAGINE, WITH THE GREATEST PLEASURE.
[CARMINHA] IS A VERY GOOD PERSON.
WOW, IT'S A GOLDEN CHARACTER.
[MURICY] OF COURSE, DEAR, OF COURSE.
[CARMINHA] IVANA... HOW DID I NOT THINK OF IT?
BEFORE, IVANA?
[IVANA] IN WHAT, CARMINHA?
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE, YOU AND MAX HAVE EVERYTHING TO DO WITH EACH OTHER.
[IVANA] I swear? OH, WHAT'S HE LIKE? IS HE SINGLE?
[CARMINHA] IS TOTALLY AVAILABLE.
HE GOT A KICK FROM HIS EX, POOR THING.
[IVANA] OH, SEE? IT MUST BE A PIECE OF CRAP, AN OLD RAG?
OH, I DON'T WANT TO TAKE ANYONE'S LEFTOVERS, NO. [MOANING]
[MURICY] THAT'S HOW SHE DOES IT, THAT GIRL.
[CARMINHA] IVANA, NO, NOTHING LIKE THAT.
[IVANA] I KNOW.
[LELECO] LOOK THERE, THEY'RE COMING IN!
[OVATION]
[TOGETHER] UH!
[CLÉBER] GOOD MOVE FOR HIM,
THERE'S A TYPHOON IN THE MIDDLE.
RECEIVED, DRIBBLE AND WAS FOULED. FOUL BY JOÃO MARIA,
GONÇALO REI'S PLAYERS COMPLAIN TO TIAGO,
GIVING ACTIVITY, THE JUDGE IN THE GAME, HEARS THE FOUL.
[CLÉBER] READY TO CHARGE THE TYPHOON, BARRIER IN POSITION
CORRECT. GOOD CHANCE OF A GOAL FOR FLAMENGO, GO, HIT IT...
ON THE CROSSBAR! FLAMENGO CONTINUES TO ATTACK, SERGINHO, CROSSING,
TYPHOON!
[EXTENDED] GREAT GOAL!
TYPHOON, FROM FLAMENGO!
♪DRUMS♪
[CLÉBER] [ELECTRONIC VOICE] BUT THERE WAS A FOUL. THE BALL HIT THE CROSSBAR,
IT ALMOST GOT IT. THE BICYCLE, A PAINTING!
A GREAT GOAL FROM THE STAR TUFÃO!
RECEIVED, DRIBBLED, WAS FOULED...
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CLÉBER] EYE ON THE CLOCK, 47
MINUTES. IT'S ALMOST OVER OF THE GAME.
AND WHAT A CHANGE OF PASSES FROM FLAMENGO. BOLÃO PRO TUFÃO,
CATCH THE GOALKEEPER, VALMIR. AND THE REFEREE BLOWS THE WHISTLE, END OF THE GAME
AT MARACANÃ. FLAMENGO WINS, 1X0
ON TOP OF GONÇALO REI.
[TALK]
[WOMAN] CARMINHA, IT'S TRUE THAT YOU'RE WAITING
AN HEIR TO THE STAR?
[TALK]
[CARMINHA] I WASN'T SUPPOSED TO SAY IT, BUT I AM.
[IVANA] NOW EXCUSE ME, OK? THANK YOU, LET'S GO,
COME ON, GUYS, COME ON.
[TYPHOON] FIRSTLY, I WANTED TO DEDICATE THIS VICTORY
FOR MY BRIDE. EVERYONE WANTED THIS SHIRT HERE,
BUT THIS SHIRT GOES TO HER.
[MAN] THAT CELEBRATION OF YOURS, TYPHOON, ARE YOU GOING TO HAVE A CHILD?
[TYPHOON] YES, I'M PREGNANT.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MONALISA] YOU BASTARD, YOU BASTARD!
[SIGH] THIS BLACK WIDOW SHOULD HAVE BEEN PREGNANT BY NOW
I FOUND OUT THEIR AFFAIR. GOODBYE, TYPHOON, ORDINARY!
[IRAN] MOTHER, MOTHER, COME HERE AND SEE AUNT DUVALINA'S DOG,
WHO IS GIVING BIRTH TO THE PUPPIES.
[MONALISA] I'M COMING, MY SON. I'M COMING, MY ANGEL. OR RATHER,
LET'S GO, BEFORE I'M THE ONE WHO HAS A CHILD HERE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[ALL] TYPHOON, TYPHOON, TYPHOON, TYPHOON!
TYPHOON, TYPHOON, TYPHOON, TYPHOON!
[RITA] [GRUNTING]
[ALL] TYPHOON, TYPHOON, TYPHOON, TYPHOON!
TYPHOON, TYPHOON, TYPHOON, TYPHOON!
[RITA] [SIGH] YOU TYPHOON, YOU TYPHOON, LISTEN TO ME!
[TYPHOON] HI, PRINCESS, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪WHETHER YOU'RE BRUNETTE OR BLONDE♪
♪COME AND SWING WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪FOLLOWING MY PACE♪
♪I WANT TO SEE IT SWING♪
♪ALL SIDE BY SIDE♪
♪IT'S GOING TO BE ALL NIGHT♪
♪COME DANCE UNTIL YOU'RE TIRED♪
♪SHAKE AND SHAKE♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪THE SCALES ARE CRAZY♪
♪BRUNETTE COME BY MY SIDE♪
♪NOBODY WILL STAND STILL♪
♪I WANT TO SEE, MESS WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[TYPHOON] WANT AN AUTOGRAPH? WHERE'S YOUR PAPER?
[RITA] I DON'T WANT AN AUTOGRAPH. CARMINHA, YOUR FIANCE,
YOU MUST KNOW...
[MAN] TYPHOON, TYPHOON, GIVE A SMILE FOR A PICTURE HERE, WILL YOU!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] CHILD, GO!
[RITA] WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MOTHER LUCINDA?
[LUCINDA] BUT ARE YOU CRAZY?
[RITA] I NEED TO TALK TO HIM!
[LUCINDA] YOU DON'T NEED TO TALK TO HIM ABOUT ANYTHING!
YOU WON'T GET IN TROUBLE ANYMORE!
[RITA] I WAS ALMOST GETTING IT,
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO GET INVOLVED!
[LUCINDA] OH, COME ON, GO HOME, GO HOME!
COME ON, LET'S GO! LET ME EXPLAIN SOMETHING TO YOU: YOU WERE
I PROMISED MYSELF THAT I WOULD TURN IN THE NEW YEAR WITHOUT KEEPING HATE INSIDE
FROM YOUR HEART, YOU WOULD FORGET THIS STORY
OF REVENGE ON THIS WOMAN.
[RITA] BUT IT'S YOU WHO SAYS IT
WE HAVE TO HELP OTHERS, RIGHT?
AND THIS MAN, POOR MAN, THIS PLAYER,
HE WILL BE DECEIVED BY THAT WITCH.
[LUCINDA] YOU'RE NOT THINKING ABOUT HELPING ANYONE,
YOU ONLY THINK ABOUT TAKING REVENGE, I KNOW.
[RITA] WHAT IF IT IS? SHE ENDED MY LIFE, SHE ENDED MY LIFE
FROM MY FATHER, SHE MULTITUDED ME AS IF I WAS A DOG
DISGUSTING!
[LUCINDA] STOP, RITA, STOP.
WHAT'S PAST IS PAST. WE CANNOT CHANGE THE PAST,
NOT EVEN THE FUTURE. THIS STORY DOESN'T BELONG TO YOU ANYMORE,
IT'S AN ADULT'S BUSINESS, OK? IT'S THEIR BUSINESS,
IT'S NOT FOR CHILDREN TO GET INVOLVED IN, NO.
[RITA] YOU'RE AFRAID, RIGHT? I'M NOT.
SHE HAS TO PAY, SHE WILL PAY ME, YOU WILL SEE!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[POTATO] MOTHER LUCINDA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
[LUCINDA] I DON'T KNOW, MY SON, I DON'T KNOW, BUT GET READY.
AT ONE OF THESE TIMES RITA WILL HAVE TO LEAVE THIS DUMP.
[POTATO] LEAVE? WHY?
[LUCINDA] FOR HER OWN GOOD.
[POTATO] BUT YOU CAN'T, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] YES, IF RITA STAYS HERE,
TRYING TO GET CLOSE TO DANGEROUS PEOPLE,
SHE WILL END HER LIFE.
IS THIS WHAT WE WANT?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] OH, HERE.
[LUCINDA] OVER THERE, LOOK. DO YOU SEE THAT LITTLE GIRL?
THAT LITTLE GIRL, SHE'S VERY SPECIAL, SEE?
HE LOST HIS WHOLE FAMILY, THERE, OH.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MARTÍN] HI, GIRL. HOW ARE YOU? I'M MARTÍN.
[MARTÍN] THIS IS DENISE, MY WIFE, SHE IS BRAZILIAN.
AND YOU WOULD LIKE TO TAKE A TRIP TO VISIT A PLACE
BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL, CALLED ARGENTINA?
[RITA] WHAT'S GOOD THERE?
[MARTÍN] [LAUGHTER] THERE'S A GOOD DESERT, FULL OF STONES,
MOUNTAINS, FULL OF WHITE SNOW, LAKES, GRAPES, IN SHORT.
SO, DO YOU WANT TO GO?
[RITA] ONLY IF MY FIANCÉ COMES WITH ME.
[MARTIN] [LAUGHTER]
[RITA] IT'S NO USE, MOTHER LUCINDA,
WITHOUT BATATA I WON'T GO.
[LUCINDA] THIS FAMILY HAS CONDITIONS, IT CAN GIVE YOU
A BETTER FUTURE, A REAL HOME.
IT WILL BE MUCH BETTER FOR YOU, MY DAUGHTER.
[RITA] YOU WANT ME TO LEAVE, RIGHT? YOU NEVER WANTED ME HERE.
[LUCINDA] OH, DON'T SAY THAT, DON'T REPEAT THAT, IT'S NOT
TRUE, YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU. I LOVE YOU, OH RITA, YOU ALWAYS WILL
IT WILL BE YOUR HOME. BUT I AM AN ADULT, I KNOW THAT LIFE
WHAT YOU WILL HAVE IN ARGENTINA IS MUCH BETTER THAN LIFE
THAT I CAN GIVE YOU, MY DAUGHTER.
[RITA] LIE, LIE.
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO HAVE ANY MORE OF ME HERE, THAT'S NO PROBLEM.
I'M GOING WITH BATATA, RIGHT, BATATA?
WE LIVE SOMEWHERE ELSE, RIGHT?
SPEAK, POTATO. LOST YOUR TONGUE? DID SOMEONE EAT YOUR TONGUE? SPEAK!
[POTATO] WHERE ARE WE GOING, RITA?
[RITA] [SNORTS] WE LIVE UNDER THE MARQUISE,
BEGS FOR ALMS. WASN'T THAT YOUR PLAN WHEN I MET YOU?
AND MOTHER LUCINDA DIDN'T LET ME LIVE HERE IN HER HOUSE?
[POTATO] I KNEW THAT MOTHER LUCINDA
I WOULD LET YOU STAY.
[RITA] YOU'RE A SCARED ONE, POTATO.
[LUCINDA] LET'S DO THE FOLLOWING? LET'S AGREE ON SOMETHING?
YOU'RE GOING TO LIVE IN ARGENTINA, IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT, YOU'LL COME BACK.
IT'S JUST AN EXPERIMENT, LET'S GO?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[RITA] YOU DON'T LIKE ME ANYMORE, RIGHT?
[LUCINDA] RITA, STOP IT, RITA. WE LOVE YOU.
WE LOVE YOU.
[RITA] YOU WANT ME TO GO, RIGHT? THEN I WILL.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[RITA] YOU WILL NEVER SEE ME AGAIN.
[RITA] GET OUT OF HERE, GO AWAY.
[POTATO] I DON'T GO OUT, I DON'T GO.
[RITA] THEN I'M GOING AWAY, I DON'T EVEN WANT TO LOOK ANYMORE
IN YOUR FACE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[POTATO] YOU CAN'T TREAT ME LIKE THIS, I'M YOUR FIANCÉ.
[RITA] IT'S NOTHING ANYMORE, WE'RE NOTHING ANYMORE,
WE BREAKED UP. YOU SENT ME AWAY.
[POTATO] WE DIDN'T SEPARATE, WE WILL NEVER SEPARATE.
OUR MARRIAGE IS FOREVER, BUT WE ARE CHILDREN,
I WILL WAIT FOR YOU.
WHEN WE GROW UP, YOU'LL COME BACK AND BECOME MY WIFE.
MOTHER LUCINDA IS RIGHT, THERE YOU WILL HAVE A FATHER, HAVE A MOTHER,
YOU WON'T NEED TO WORK.
[RITA] YES, BUT THEN YOU WON'T BE THERE,
YOU WILL FORGET ABOUT ME.
[POTATO] NOT EVEN IF I FALL AND BEAT MY HEAD,
A TRUCK RUNS OVER HER,
AND MY HEAD TURNS TO PAÇOCA, I WILL NOT FORGET YOU.
[RITA] [LAUGHTER] I swear? NOT EVEN IF YOU TURN INTO PAÇOCA?
[POTATO] NOT EVEN IF IT TURNS INTO MASHED POTATO.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] NEVER FORGET, I AM YOUR MOTHER, THIS IS YOUR FAMILY
AND THIS IS YOUR HOUSE, HEARD?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[RITA] DON'T CRY, YOU FOOL. I'LL BE BACK.
[POTATO] [SCREAMING] RITA!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[POTATO] RITA!
♪HI,HI,HI♪
[MARTÍN] "HABER, HABER, HABER, WHAT CAN WE DO WITH THIS CHICA
BEAUTIFUL, HUH?" LET'S PLAY A JOKE? YOU LOOK AT ME
IN THE EYE, CANNOT LAUGH, CANNOT CRY,
YOU CAN'T BLINK YOUR EYES NOW.
[MARTÍN] LOST, LOST. [LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] VERY WELL. [LAUGHTER]
[MURICY] LET'S TAKE A PICTURE HERE, COME ON. ONE PICTURE, EVERYONE.
THAT, MAKES YOU LOOK RICH, HUH, LELECO.
[LELECO] WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE TO LOOK LIKE A RICH MAN?
[MURICY] LOOK AT ME, LOOK, PROUD. SHOW THE PIVOT,
THAT COSTS A FORTUNE.
[TOGETHER] ONE, TWO, THREE AND GO!
[CHRIES OF CELEBRATION]
[IVANA] I DID IT, I DID IT!
[CARMINHA] IVANA, IVANA...
THIS IS MAXWELL, HE WAS A GREAT FRIEND
FROM THE LATE GENÉSIO, I WANTED TO INTRODUCE YOU.
♪SAMBA♪
[IVANA] HI, MAXWELL! HOW ARE YOU?
[MAX] HOW ARE YOU? YOU CAN CALL ME MAX. [LAUGHTER]
OH CARMEN LUCIA, CARMEN LUCIA,
BUT WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME THAT TYPHOON'S SISTER
WAS HE SUCH A NICE PERSON?
SO, IF I HAD KNOWN, I WOULD HAVE COME TO THE DIVINE BEFORE.
[IVANA] [LAUGHTER] AS MUCH AS IT IS.
[MAX] [LAUGHTER] NOW YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TELL ME...
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, CARMEN LUCIA,
YOU WON'T TELL ME THAT BESIDES BEING BEAUTIFUL AND NICE,
YOU KNOW HOW TO DANCE, WAIT?
[IVANA] OH, I KNOW! [LAUGHTER]
I KNOW THAT.
[MAX] [EXTENDED] AH!
SO PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE.
♪SAMBA♪
[IVANA] AH!
[MURICY] LOOK AT THAT, LELECO, LELECO,
TAKE A LOOK AT IVANA, LELECO!
WILL THIS BOUQUET THING REALLY WORK? LOOK AT IT.
SO, SHE'S GETTING MARRIED, SHE'S GETTING MARRIED. GO ON, IVANA!
GO, MY DAUGHTER, GO UP! HEY!
♪SAMBA♪
♪SHE'S MY WIFE'S FRIEND♪
♪YES, YES, YES♪
♪BUT HE KEEPS COMING ON TO ME♪
♪FINALLY♪
[TYPHOON] GO, CARMINHA!
GO, CARMINHA, GO FOR IT!
STAY STRONG I'M HERE WITH YOU!
I'M HERE WITH YOU!
[CARMINHA] [SCREAM]
[TYPHOON] THAT'S IT, MY LOVE! THAT'S IT!
THAT!
[BABY CRYING]
[TYPHOON] LOOK THERE!
[CARMINHA] [PANTING]
[BABY CRYING]
[CARMINHA] A GIRL?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] LOOK AT MY LONG HAIR, BRUNETTE!
[TYPHOON] WILL BE NAMED AFTER GRANDMOTHER, ÁGATA.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[TYPHOON] WHAT A PRECIOUS THING!
[BABY CRYING]
[TYPHOON] I KNOW, I KNOW. I ALREADY WANT TO GO BACK TO THE BELLY.
[CARMINHA] TAKE IT, YOU CAN TAKE IT. YOU CAN TAKE IT, YOU CAN TAKE IT,
YOU CAN TAKE HER. TAKE HER.
TAKE HER, TYPHOON, PLEASE, TAKE HER. TAKE HER, TYPHOON!
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[BABY CRYING]
[LELECO] IT SEEMS LIKE IT'S OUR BLOOD,
BECAUSE LOOK, THE EMOTION IS THE SAME.
[TYPHOON] IT ISN'T, BUT IT HAS TO BE THE SAME,
BECAUSE IT DOESN'T MATTER IF IT IS LEGITIMATE OR ADOPTED,
THE IMPORTANT THING IS LOVE, AFFECTION
THAT WE WILL GIVE AND RECEIVE FROM THIS CHILD TOO.
[IVANA] OH, FINALLY, GUYS, IT WAS A LOT OF TRANSIT TO GET HERE.
I STILL HAD TO PICK UP MY FIANCE FROM THE CLUB, RIGHT?
HE DIDN'T WANT TO MISS THIS MOMENT FOR ANYTHING.
[MAX] YES, ACTUALLY, I LOVE SEEING NEWBORN BABIES.
WAS THE BIRTH OK?
[LELECO] EVERYTHING, THE CHILD EVEN HAS A NAME.
[MAX] WHAT'S THE NAME?
[TYPHOON] AGATE. AGATE.
[MAX] AGATE?
[TYPHOON] HUM.
[MAX] BUT ÁGATA IS A BIT OF A STRANGE NAME, ISN'T IT?
[MURICY] OF COURSE IT'S NOT STRANGE, IMAGINE,
IT'S MY GRANDMA'S NAME, RIGHT, DEAR?
IT'S GRANDMOTHER'S NAME. [LAUGHTER]
[MAX] I UNDERSTAND.
[IVANA] HEY! YOU GOT A NIECE, BABY!
WHEN YOU MARRY ME,
LET'S ALL BE PART OF THE SAME FAMILY.
[MAX] YES, MY PRINCESS, I'M GETTING USED TO IT ALREADY.
[MAX] AGATE.
♪DERÊ-RÊRÊ, DERÊ-RÊRE♪
[OLENKA] OH MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE HERE!
[MONALISA] OH, I MISS YOU SO MUCH!
[OLENKA] A LOT, A LOT! COME HERE, IS THIS IRAN?
[MONALISA] WHAT DO YOU THINK, OLENKA?
[OLENKA] OH REALLY? WHAT'S UP, LITTLE BROTHER?
HERE, I'M OLENKA, OK, I'M YOUR MOTHER'S BEST FRIEND,
AND NOW I'M GOING TO BE YOURS TOO, IS THAT IT? IS THAT IT.
Yes. NOW COME,
YOU WILL HAVE A VERY GOOD SURPRISE.
[MONALISA] OH, MY FATHER.
[OLENKA] A NICE SURPRISE, YOU'LL SEE!
♪WHERE HAVE WE COME?♪
♪I WANT YOU TO DO IT SO MUCH♪
♪PART OF MY MADNESS♪
[URBAN AMBIENCE]
[TALK]
[MONALISA] OH, OH.
[IVANA] [SCREAMING] I DON'T BELIEVE IT, I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
[MONALISA] IVANA!
[IVANA] OH, MONALISA! MY FRIEND, YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT HAPPENED HERE DURING THE TIME YOU WERE AWAY.
MY LOVE, YOUR SALON IS SIMPLY THE BIGGEST SUCCESS
FROM THE ENTIRE NORTH ZONE, NO, FROM THE ENTIRE CARIOCA SUBURB WORLDWIDE.
[OLENKA] OH, REALLY?
[IVANA] MY LOVE, PEOPLE ARE COMING EVEN FROM THE SOUTH ZONE
DO STRAIGHTENING HERE, CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
[OLENKA] YES, MY DAUGHTER, THIS IS A REAL LINE
ASSEMBLY, PARTNER.
[IVANA] OH, I ALREADY HAVE MONEY FOR TWO MORE BRANCHES.
[MONALISA] WHAT IS THIS!
[IVANA] YES, ONE IN THE CENTER AND ANOTHER IN PENHA.
[MONALISA] WOW, IVANA, LOOK, YOU'RE A TRUE GENIUS
BUSINESS. IT IS. FOR ME, IT'S DONE, I'M JUST GOING TO ASK YOU
TO REST, AFTER ALL, IT'S TWO DAYS BY BUS
FROM PARAÍBA TO HERE, RIGHT?
[IVANA] BY BUS? I DON'T BELIEVE IT, YOU'RE RICH,
DON'T YOU STILL UNDERSTAND THIS?
[MONALISA] IT DIDN'T GET TO ME.
[IVANA] HUM, OKAY.
[MONALISA] STILL.
[IVANA] AND WHO IS THIS ONE?
[MONALISA] THIS ONE IS MY ADOPTED SON,
THIS IS IRAN.
[IVANA] [EXTENDED] OH, HI, IRAN, HOW ARE YOU? CUTE.
[LAUGHTER] LOOK, MONALISA, THE TYPHOON ASKED...
[MONALISA] IVANA, LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING:
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOUR BROTHER TOLD ME TO SAY, BY THE WAY,
MY DEAL WITH HIM, WITH YOU, WILL ONLY WORK IF I DON'T HAVE
THAT WE ARE ALWAYS GOING TO MEET HIM, OK?
[IVANA] AGREEMENT, FRIEND.
[IVANA] LET'S DO SOME HYDRATION?
[OLENKA] WHAT'S THIS? THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS...
[CAR ENGINE]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MAX] THAT KID IS CUTE, ISN'T HE?
[CARMINHA] IT'S BEAUTIFUL, SO BEAUTIFUL.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] [SNIFLE]
[CARMINHA] ARE YOU THE POTATO?
[POTATO] IT'S ME, YES.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] HERE'S ONE, FOR YOU.
[POTATO] NO, MA'AM. MOTHER LUCINDA SAID THAT WE
CANNOT ACCEPT ANYTHING STRANGE.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MAX] WHAT'S UP?
[CARMINHA] HE HAS MY HANDS...
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] MY HANDS AND YOUR EYES.
[CARMINHA] I CAN'T LEAVE HIM HERE.
[MAX] CAN'T YOU LEAVE HIM HERE, CARMINHA? WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO.
[CARMINHA] YES, I WILL FIND A WAY. NOW, GET OUT OF HERE,
IF YOU GET OUT OF HERE, YOU CANNOT SHOW UP.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] WOW, SACRIFICE...
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE? GET OUT OF HERE.
[CARMINHA] DON'T WORRY.
[CARMINHA] THE SOONER I GET OUT OF THIS TRASH CAN THE BETTER.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[CARMINHA] WE HAVE A MATTER TO ARRANGE.
[LUCINDA] AS FAR AS I KNOW, WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO DO WITH
TO GET IT RIGHT.
[CARMINHA] I'M GOING TO STAY WITH BATATA.
[LUCINDA] NO WAY.
[CARMINHA] HE IS MY SON
AND I HAVE THE RIGHT.
♪HI, HI, HI♪
[LUCINDA] WHAT RIGHT DO YOU HAVE, HUH? SPEAK, YOU DEGENERATE,
YOU JUST GAVE BIRTH. I'M THE ONE WHO EDUCATES AND RAISES YOU!
[CARMINHA] I AM HIS MOTHER, MAX IS HIS FATHER! BEFORE WE DIDN'T
I HAD THE QUALITY TO RAISE A CHILD, BUT NOW WE DO!
THE RIGHT THING IS THAT HE STAYS WITH US!
[LUCINDA] AND YOU'RE GOING TO TELL THAT SOCCER PLAYER
WHO ARE YOU MARRIED TO?
[CARMINHA] HE WILL NEVER KNOW.
[LUCINDA] [LAUGHTER] COME ON, HOW? TELL ME HOW, IT'S VARIATING,
CARMINHA? FOR THE LOVE OF...
[CARMINHA] I WILL SAY THAT I ADOPTED A BOY! A BOY WHO
I REALLY LIKED THE DUMP THAT I KNEW AND I WANT TO ADOPT AND I
I'M SURE HE'LL AGREE!
[LUCINDA] YOU WILL RAISE YOUR LEGITIMATE SON, AS IF HE WERE YOUR OWN
ADOPTED, IN THE HOUSE OF A POOR MAN WHERE HIS LOVER LIVES,
WHO IS THE FATHER OF THE CHILD, IS THAT IT? I THINK NOW YOU
YOU REALLY OVERCOME ALL YOUR LOWLINESS
AND SCAMS, THAT'S THE WORST. I WILL NOT ALLOW IT,
THE POTATO STAYS!
[LUCINDA] YOU'D PREFER THE BOY TO BE RAISED IN THE GARBAGE...
THAN IN A MANSION, WITH LIFE AT HIS FEET WITH EVERYTHING BEST
AND THE BEST? IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT? TO DENY A FUTURE
TO A CHILD. HAVING ACCESS TO A DOCTOR, SCHOOL, IS THAT IT?
[LUCINDA] AT LEAST HERE HE HAS A REAL HOUSE, THERE,
HE WILL LIVE A LIE.
[CARMINHA] DID YOU DECIDE TO FACE ME?
[LUCINDA] I RESOLVED. YOU WANT TO CLAIM YOUR RIGHTS
BECAUSE THE SON IS YOURS, SO LET'S DO THIS: LET'S GO
TWO OVER THERE AT THE FOOTBALL PLAYER'S HOUSE, LET'S TELL THIS ONE
THE WHOLE STORY, FROM THE BEGINNING TO THE END, LET'S GO?
[CARMINHA] DID YOU FORGET? IS THAT IT? DID YOU FORGET THAT YOU
ARE YOU ALSO PART OF THIS STORY? DID YOU FORGET?
THAT IF WE TELL THE WHOLE STORY, YOUR DEAR BATATA WOULDN'T
YOU WILL NOT LIKE TO KNOW WHO THE REAL MOTHER LUCINDA IS
HIS. WE'RE BOTH TOGETHER AND MIXED FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES,
IF ONE FALLS, THE OTHER FALLS TOO.
[LUCINDA] BUT YOU ARE MY DESTINY, YOU ARE MINE
DISGRACE! WHY DO YOU WANT THIS BOY NOW? WHAT FOR?
THE BOY IS HAPPY HERE.
[PANTING] WHY... ARE YOU JUST GOING?
FIND A PROBLEM, YOU'RE TAKING A PROBLEM TO...
[CARMINHA] I LIKE HIM. I THINK I AM CAPABLE OF LOVE
THAT BOY.
[LUCINDA] YOU'RE NOT CAPABLE
TO LOVE NOBODY, CARMI...
[CARMINHA] [SHOUTING] I AM!
[LUCINDA] IT'S NOT, CARMINHA, IT'S NOT! LEAVE THIS BOY HERE
WITH ME, PLEASE, I... I'M ASKING YOU, I BEG YOU...
[CARMINHA] NO!
[LUCINDA] PLEASE...
[LUCINDA] LEAVE THE BATATA HERE...
[CARMINHA] NO, I'LL TAKE IT!
WHERE'S THE GIRL? THE PLAGUE RITA,
WHAT DID YOU DO TO HER?
HE SPEAKS!
[LUCINDA] I SAVED RITA FROM YOU. COME ON, GET OUT OF HERE!
[CARMINHA] I THINK IT'S BETTER IF THIS GIRL STAYS FAR AWAY
FROM ME, BECAUSE IF SHE SHOWS UP, YOU'LL BE DEALING WITH ME.
[LUCINDA] [SCREAMING]
GET OUT OF HERE! GO, PESTICIDE!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[LUCINDA] GET OUT OF HERE!
[LUCINDA] [SCREAM]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CARMELA] COME.
HE COMES.
LOOK AT THIS BEAUTIFUL HOUSE YOU'RE GOING TO LIVE IN.
[TYPHOON] I THINK THE SKYLIGHT WILL LOOK GOOD RIGHT THERE WHERE
THE LORD HAS SPOKE.
[MAN] SURE.
[TYPHOON] OK, THANK YOU.
[CARMINHA] COME. TYPHOON.
[CARMINHA] THIS IS BATATA, HE'S THE ONE WHO'S GOING TO LIVE
WITH US.
[TYPHOON] EVERYTHING GOOD, POTATO? ARE YOU HUNGRY?
[CARMINHA] SAY SOMETHING, BOY.
[TYPHOON] YOU DON'T NEED TO SAY ANYTHING, NO. DO YOU LIKE FOOTBALL?
ARE YOU GOOD AT FOOTBALL? COME HERE.
[TYPHOON] KICK A BALL THERE ON THE LAWN.
[TYPHOON] THE HEADBAND!
[TYPHOON] THE BIKE!
♪OOH OOOOH ARIA RAY♪
[TYPHOON] [LAUGHTER] LEAVE ME, I'LL TEACH YOU EVERYTHING I KNOW,
YOU WILL GIVE A BIKE, I WILL TEACH YOU EVERYTHING.
♪OOH OOOOH ARIA RAY♪
♪YAYYYYYYYY♪
♪WHAT'S NOTHING♪
♪GET OUT OF MY FACE♪
♪I WANT TO PASS♪
♪FOR THE SAMBA♪
[TYPHOON] COME HERE, POTATO. YOUR LITTLE SISTER IS THERE, LOOK.
[POTATO] WOW, IT EVEN LOOKS LIKE A TOY.
[TYPHOON] YEAH, SPEAKING OF WHICH
WE NEED TO COME UP WITH A REAL NAME FOR YOU,
STOP CALLING YOU POTATO.
WHAT NAME IS WRITTEN ON YOUR CERTIFICATE?
[POTATO] I DON'T EVEN HAVE A BIRTH CERTIFICATE,
THEY ALWAYS CALLED ME POTATO.
[TYPHOON] SO LET'S FIX IT
A NAME FOR YOU, WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO CALL YOURSELF?
[POTATO] HUM, I DON'T KNOW.
[TYPHOON] SPEAK, ANY NAME.
CHOOSE.
[POTATO] HUM. OH, JORGE,
LIKE YOU.
[TYPHOON] JORGE FATHER, JORGE SON.
[LAUGHTER] THAT'S RIGHT, KID.
♪IT AIN'T NO USE TO SIT♪
♪AND WONDER WHY, BABE♪
♪IF YOU DON'T KNOW BY NOW♪
♪AN' IT AIN'T NO USE TO SIT♪
♪AND WONDER WHY, BABE♪
♪IT'LL NEVER DO SOMEHOW♪
♪WHEN YOUR ROOSTER CROWS♪
♪AT THE BREAK OF DAWN♪
♪LOOK OUT YOUR WINDOW♪
♪AND I'LL BE GONE♪
[RITA] WILL YOU LET ME STEP ON THE GRAPES, DADDY?
[MARTÍN] OF COURSE, "MI AMOR", BUT YOU'LL GET TIRED SOON.
[RITA] I'M NOT GOING, NO.
[RITA] WHY DON'T YOU CALL ME RITA ANYMORE?
[MARTÍN] BECAUSE NOW YOU ARE NINA. RITA IS THE OTHER ONE,
LEFT BEHIND, HUH?
♪FOR COSECHA TIME♪
♪WHAT BEAUTIFUL TO PUT THE PAGO ON♪
♪HAY UN BRILLO DE CHAPECAS♪
♪IN THE EYES OF THE COUNTRYMAN♪
♪YENDING AND COMING IN THE CAR♪
♪MY PLACE♪
♪IT HAS ITS MYTHS AND BEINGS♪
[TYPHOON] GO, SON!
GO JORGINHO!
♪OSWALDO CRUZ♪
♪CASCADURA, VAZ LOBO AND IRAJÁ♪
♪MY PLACE♪
♪IT'S A SMILE, IT'S PEACE AND PLEASURE♪
♪YOUR NAME IS SWEET TO SAY♪
[TYPHOON] TAKE HIM, TAKE HIM!
THAT'S IT! THAT'S IT, SON,
KICK! GO... GOAL!
[EXTENDED] HEY!
[JORGINHO] THAT'S IT!
♪IT'S DIVINE♪
♪FROM THE VINEYARD TO THE BODEGA♪
♪ALWAYS A RACE♪
♪ON CHARGE♪
♪DE LA BLANCA OR DE LA NEGRA♪
♪ALWAYS A RACE♪
♪ON CHARGE♪
♪DE LA BLANCA OR DE LA NEGRA♪
♪PÓNGALE POR LAS HILERAS♪
♪SIN LET NOBODY RACE♪
♪HAY QUE LLENAR LA BODEGA♪
♪YA EL VINO IS ENDING♪
♪IT'S DIVINE, LÁ LÁ IÁ♪
[TYPHOON] GOAL! [SCREAM] MY SON, WOW! GREAT GOAL!
HEY, KID!
[JORGINHO] OH, AH! [LAUGHTER] SO WHAT?
♪IT'S SO DIVINE♪
[TYPHOON] GO ON. MAKE ANOTHER ONE, MAKE ANOTHER ONE!
[NINA] ''YOU CRAZY''!
[BEGONIA] ''YOU WILL FIND OUT
NOW I AM AS CRAZY AS I AM''.
[NINA] YOU'RE ANNOYING, PEPITA!
[BEGONIA] NINA, BEGONIA, STOP THAT DADDY IS WAITING FOR US!
[NINA] OH, "PAPA IS WAITING"!
[SCREAMS]
[TALK]
[LAUGHTER]
[NINA] HUM! "UNA DELÍCIA, PAPÁ!"
[MARTÍN] IT'S OUR 2003 HARVEST.
IT'S THE BEST IN LAST TIMES. LET'S MAKE A TOAST
TO YOUR MOTHER. MY DEAR DENISE, WHOM I FEEL EVERY DAY
THAT IS CLOSER TO US.
[TOGETHER] TIM-TIM! TIM-TIM!
[MARTÍN] "LOS OJOS, LOS OJOS, LOS OJOS." VERY GOOD!
SO GOOD TO HAVE YOU THREE HERE, MY THREE GIRLS.
MERCEDES, COULD YOU SHOW UP A LITTLE MORE, HUH?
[MERCEDES] AH, "YO TRABAJO MUCHO, PAPÁ.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR ANYTHING."
[MARTÍN] YES, I LOST YOU
PRO PABLO, NINA PRO RESTAURANT
AND I LOST DONA BEGONIA TO THE WORLD.
[BEGONIA] IT'S NOT TRUE, DAD, IT'S NOT TRUE.
[MARTÍN] YESTERDAY, FOR EXAMPLE.
[BEGONIA] I ALREADY SAID,
I SLEPT AT MANUELA'S HOUSE.
[MARTÍN] YES, YESTERDAY
AT MANUELA'S HOUSE, THE DAY BEFORE YESTERDAY AT HONÓRIA'S HOUSE,
AND SO ON, IS IT?
[NINA] HUM! "PERMISSION", DEAR,
BUT I HAVE TO SPEND A WHILE ON THE COMPUTER
TO FINISH THE NEW MENU.
[MARTÍN] HUM, I'VE ALREADY GIVE UP ON YOU.
[BEGONIA] "A TOAST, DADDY"?
[MARTÍN] NO, STOP!
[BEGONIA] "NO, YES, YES, OF COURSE!
COME ON, A TOAST FOR MOM."
[MARTÍN] OK, "PERO SIEDE POR LA VIDA".
[BEGONIA] "SIED FOR LIFE".
[MERCEDES] TICK! TICK!
[BEGONIA] TIM-TIM!
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MARTÍN] THE FOOTBALL PLAYER AGAIN.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[NINA] SINCE WHEN HAVE YOU BEEN SPYING ON ME LIKE THIS?
[MARTÍN] SINCE YOU PROMISED ME YOU WOULD STOP
WITH THIS OBSESSION TO RESEARCH THIS WOMAN'S LIFE
AND THIS MAN.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[NINA] THEY'RE CELEBRATING THEIR WEDDINGS, CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
THIS WOMAN SHOULD HAVE BEEN IN PRISON FOR YEARS.
[MARTÍN] BUT FORGET ABOUT IT, NINA, TURN THE PAGE.
[NINA] LOOK AT THIS, SHE MARRIED HER LOVER
WITH THE POOR PLAYER'S SISTER.
[MARTÍN] BUT YOU DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE STILL LOVERS,
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
[NINA] OF COURSE I KNOW. IT'S THE SAME LOVER FROM BACK IN THE DAY
FROM MY FATHER, THEY'RE STILL GOING TO HIT THIS PLAYER
OF FOOTBALL. AND YOU KNOW WHAT'S THE WORST OF ALL?
THIS CARMINHA STILL PRETENDS THAT SHE IS A FAMILY MOTHER,
EXAMPLE OF THE COMMUNITY, SHE IS FROM THE LEAGUE OF CATHOLIC WIVES,
CAN YOU BELIEVE SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
[MARTÍN] NINA, COME HERE, LOOK AT ME.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MARTÍN] I AM YOUR FATHER, YOUR LIFE IS HERE, YOU ARE NINA,
MY BELOVED DAUGHTER, THE BEST CHEF I KNOW,
HELLO? THAT GIRL IS WOUNDED, SCARED, DESPERATE
THAT I TOOK AWAY THAT PILE OF TRASH NO MORE. HUH?
[NINA] BUT I DREAM ABOUT HER EVERY NIGHT.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[MARTÍN] [SPEAKING IN ANOTHER LANGUAGE]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MARTÍN] WHEN WE LOOK INTO THE ABYSS...
HE LOOKS AT US TOO, HUH?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MARTÍN] YOU CAN BE HAPPY OR DIVE INTO THIS ENDLESS WELL.
[MARTÍN] I KNOW... I KNOW HOW MUCH THIS ABYSS ATTRACTS YOU, RIGHT?
BUT YOU WILL BE STRONG, YOU WILL RESIST
OR IF NOT YOUR FATHER WILL DIE OF HEARTBREAK.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[NINA] ARE YOU RIGHT, DAD?
[MARTÍN] ARE WE GOING ON A BOAT TOMORROW?
[NINA] LET'S SEE WHO WILL CATCH THE BIGGEST FISH.
[MARTÍN] [LAUGHTER] I WANT TO SEE THAT.
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
[ÁGATA] MOTHER, LOOK AT ME.
[CARMINHA] WAIT, ÁGATA.
OH, PLEASE, PUT THOSE CANDLES OVER THERE IN THE CORNER.
RIGHT CORNER, ANTIP.
[AGATE] MOTHER!
[CARMINHA] OH, MY DAUGHTER, PLEASE WAIT, MOM HAS
TO FOCUS. NO, SORRY, SORRY,
I CHANGED MY MIND, GO TO THE LEFT SIDE.
OH NO, NOT THIS, NOT NOW, PLEASE,
THIS IS OUTSIDE, PEOPLE, THE PARTY IS OUTSIDE.
[JANAÍNA] MADAME... MADAME, HERE'S THE JUICE.
[CARMINHA] OH, DID YOU PUT COCONUT WATER IN?
[JANAÍNA] NO, YOU DIDN'T ASK.
[CARMINHA] DO YOU NEED TO ASK? GO, MAKE ANOTHER ONE.
[AGATE] OH MOTHER!
[CARMINHA] GO, GO, DAUGHTER,
SPEAK UP. I DIDN'T TELL YOU TO TRY ON THE DRESS
FROM TONIGHT?
[ÁGATA] SO, THIS IS THE ONE I'M USING.
[CARMINHA] WHAT? ARE YOU CRAZY? DAUGHTER, YOU'RE NOT PRETTY ANYMORE,
YOU STILL WEAR A HORRIBLE DRESS LIKE THAT,
WHAT DO YOU WANT? TO END IT FOREVER? TO EMBARRASS ME?
[ÁGATA] I DON'T THINK THE DRESS IS UGLY.
[CARMINHA] OF COURSE YOU DON'T THINK SO, YOU ARE COMPLETELY
NO IDEA. DO YOU KNOW WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE?
A BAKERY TUBE INSIDE A PAPER BAG.
[AGATE] OH MOTHER...
[CARMINHA] SWALLOW YOUR CRYING! GO, GO UP THERE,
TRY ON ANOTHER DRESS, GO ON.
[MAX] GOOD MORNING, CARMEN LUCIA.
[CARMINHA] GOOD MORNING, MAX.
[IVANA] GUYS, I NEED MORE EQUIPMENT,
I'M OPENING TWO MORE SALONS THIS WEEK.
THE PARTY DECORATION IS LOOKING OUT AWESOME, SISTER-IN-LAW. [LAUGHTER] I KNOW.
THEN SEND ME EIGHT MORE SINKS
HAIR UNTIL MONDAY, OK? OK, KISS.
[CARMINHA] WHERE IS MAX GOING?
[IVANA] OH, ANOTHER ONE OF THOSE BUSINESS MEETINGS OF HIS
THAT DON'T END IN ANYTHING, RIGHT?
[CARMINHA] OH, CUNHA, I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU CAN HANDLE IT
THIS ASSHOLES, SEE?
[IVANA] [LAUGHTER] IT'S YOUR FAULT, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO GOT ME, REMEMBER?
[CARMINHA] TODAY I REGRET IT.
[IVANA] OH, DON'T REGRET IT. I LOVE MY BABY.
[CARMINHA] DO YOU KNOW ABOUT JORGINHO?
[IVANA] SHE MUST BE WITH HER GIRLFRIEND, RIGHT?
[CARMINHA] I NEVER KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THAT BOY.
[MUZZLE] ALL THAT'S LEFT IS NOT SHOWING UP AT THE PARTY.
[IVANA] OH, COME ON, OF COURSE HE'S COMING.
[CARMINHA] I'M GOING TO CALL DÉBORA.
[IVANA] WOW, CALL.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[CRUNCH] [SCREAM] OH, THIS NOISE WILL NEVER END,
ADILSON? GIVE ME A LITTLE TIME, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD,
I WANT TO READ MY NEWSPAPER, MAN.
[VERÔNICA] NO, NO, NO, MR. ADILSON, CONTINUE,
GET THE HAMMER DOWN, I'M THE ONE IN CHARGE HERE.
CADINHO, YOU YOURSELF AGREED TO MOVE THIS WALL.
[CRUCIBLE] LOVE... LOVE, I AGREE
WITH EVERYTHING YOU WANT. I... I'M TIRED OF FIGHTING.
NOW, COULD YOU BE KIND
TO DO THIS WORK WHEN I WAS NOT AT HOME.
[VERÔNICA] LOVE, LOVE, LOVE. YOU'RE NEVER HOME,
SO NOW YOU CAN HANDLE THE WORK. WELL DONE. OK?
[CRUCIBLE] OK... OK.
[DÉBORA] WOULD YOU LIKE TO DO US A FAVOR AND STOP FIGHTING.
OH, NEWSPAPER, I'M DYING TO SEE IT, DAD. GOOD MORNING.
[VERÔNICA] DÉBORA, WE REALLY HAVE TO GO
THERE AT THAT DIVINE PARTY, HUH?
[CRUITLING] BUT OF COURSE YES, VERONICA.
DO YOU THINK I'M GOING TO MISS THE OPPORTUNITY TO SEE,
WITH MY OWN EYES, WHAT MY FORMER MAID SAW
WHAT DID YOU DO WITH THE MILLIONS YOUR SON WON IN FOOTBALL?
[DÉBORA] [LAUGHING] THE HOUSE IS HILARIOUS, DAD.
I CANNOT DESCRIBE IT.
[VERÔNICA] WOW, I CAN IMAGINE.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[DÉBORA] JORGINHO'S MOTHER. THIS WOMAN WON'T STOP CALLING.
[VERÔNICA] BETTER ANSWER, HUH? MOTHER-IN-LAW IS MOTHER-IN-LAW.
[DÉBORA] HI, CARMINHA. NO, I DON'T KNOW WHY JORGINHO DIDN'T
IS IT SERVING YOU? OF COURSE WE'RE GOING TO THE PARTY. OK,
LEAVE IT, OK? OK, KISS. WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO THE DIVINE RIGHT AWAY BECAUSE I'M MISSING JORGINHO SO MUCH,
I TAKE THE OPPORTUNITY TO WATCH HIS TRAINING. KISS, KISS.
[CRUCIBLE] GO THERE.
[VERÔNICA] SEE, CADINHO?
DO YOU SEE? DO YOU SEE? HUH?
[CRUCIBLE] WHAT IS IT?
[VERÔNICA] DO YOU SEE? THIS IS WHAT YOU GET FROM RAISING A DAUGHTER
IN THE BEST SCHOOLS, DO YOU SEE WHAT HAPPENS?
WE RAISED THIS GIRL IN THE FINE FLOWER OF THE CARIOCA ELITE,
SEND HER ABROAD FROM A LITTLE AGE,
PUT THEM IN THE BEST SCHOOLS, WHAT FOR, LOVE? HUH? WHAT FOR, LOVE?
FOR SHE TO END UP IN THE SUBURB.
[CADINHO] YES, THEN. LONG LIVE THE SUBURB!
THAT'S WHERE THE FUTURE IS!
[VERÔNICA] GET THE HAMMER DOWN, ADILSON, GET THE HAMMER DOWN!
[DRILL]
[WHITE] WHAT'S THIS, JORGINHO?
NEXT TIME I'LL TAKE YOU OUT OF TRAINING, MAN.
[DÉBORA] WHAT'S THIS, JORGINHO?
[TALK]
[JORGINHO] SIZE DOESN'T MATTER, NO, IDIOT!
[IRAN] JORGINHO, COME HERE. WHAT'S UP, BROTHER? HUH?
[JORGINHO] WHAT'S UP
IT'S JUST THAT I'M NOT WELL TODAY, NO, BROTHER.
[IRAN] WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
YOU CAN'T LEAVE TRAINING LIKE THIS, NO, MAN.
[JORGINHO] WE'LL TALK LATER.
[WHITE] WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING, JORGINHO? HUM?
WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
[JORGINHO] DIDN'T YOU WANT TO TAKE ME OUT OF TRAINING, PROFESSOR?
SO. I WILL NOT GIVE YOU THAT JOB,
NO, I'M ALREADY LEAVING.
[BLANK] I WILL TALK TO THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS
AND YOU WILL BE SUSPENDED.
[JORGINHO] TALK TO WHOEVER YOU WANT.
[WHITE] STOP BEING A KID.
[JORGINHO] I'M NOT A KID, NO.
[DÉBORA] FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, WHAT HAPPENED?
ARE YOU CRAZY?
[JORGINHO] I WAS, I WAS CRAZY, YES.
TERRIBLE COMPANY TODAY.
[DÉBORA] LET'S TALK.
[JORGINHO] YOU KNOW WHAT? LEAVE ME ALONE, COME ON.
[DEBORAH] WAIT.
[JORGINHO] LEAVE ME ALONE.
[DEBORAH] [SIGH]
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪IT AIN'T NO USE TO SIT♪
♪AND WONDER WHY, BABE♪
♪IF'N YOU DON'T KNOW BY NOW♪
♪AND IT AIN'T NO USE TO SIT♪
♪AND WONDER WHY, BABE♪
♪IT'LL NEVER DO SOMEHOW♪
♪WHEN YOUR ROOSTER CROWS♪
♪AT THE BREAK OF DAWN♪
♪LOOK OUT YOUR WINDOW♪
♪AND I'LL BE GONE♪
♪YOU'RE THE REASON
♪I'M A-TRAVELING ON♪
♪BUT DON'T THINK TWICE
♪IT'S ALL RIGHT♪
[NINA] "LOS OJOS DE BIFE, MARTÍN, QUICK!"
[HECTOR] "WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?"
[NINA] "SALÍ, SALÍ DE MI COCINA, HECTOR."
[HECTOR] I'M LEAVING, MY BOSS.
[NINA] "DOS ENSALADAS PARA LA CUATRO Y UN SPAGUETI
TO LA TRES. UNA TERINA MÁS, GUSTAVO."
[NINA] "MÁS SAL EN ESE OJO DE BIFE, YES?"
[HECTOR] [SPEAKING SPANISH]
[NINA] ENOUGH EATING, HECTOR. I DON'T WANT A FAT BOYFRIEND.
[HECTOR] IT'S NOT MY FAULT IF MY GIRLFRIEND
COOKS SO WELL LIKE THIS.
[NINA] [LAUGHTER]
[HECTOR] THE MOVEMENT TODAY WAS BIG, HUH?
IN FACT, IT'S TIME TO MAKE YOU MY PARTNER.
[NINA] "YA SABEIS WHAT I THINK".
PARTNERS AND BOYFRIENDS WORKING TOGETHER, EXAGGERATION.
I PREFER TO BE YOUR EMPLOYEE,
I PREFER TO WORK FOR YOU.
[HECTOR] OH... I WAS THINKING, WE COULD GO TO THE MOVIES,
EAT A HOTDOG, POPCORN,
CHEESEBURGER, SODA. HUM?
[NINA] I WAS GOING TO GO OUT ON A BOAT WITH "MI PAPÁ".
[HECTOR] "CON MI PAPA"? "SIEMPRE MI PAPA?
I HAVE NO WAY TO COMPETE WITH THIS MAN."
ARE YOU MARRIED TO HIM, "NO"?
[NINA] "YES, YOU ARE MARRIED TO MY PAPÁ.
YOU ARE THE MAN OF MY LIFE". YOU ARE THE MAN I LOVE THE MOST
IN THIS WORLD YOU WILL GET USED TO IT.
BY THE WAY, I HAVE TO GO.
[HECTOR] HEY, HEY, HEY. CAN I STILL HOPE TO SEE YOU MORE?
LATE OR ARE YOU GOING TO STAY WITH DAD UNTIL DAWN?
[NINA] "I CALL YOU".
[HECTOR] HUM?
[DÉBORA] COME ON, MY LOVE. THE PARTY IS SOON
AND YOU STILL HAVE TO GET READY, LET'S GO.
[JORGINHO] I ALREADY TOLD YOU I'M NOT GOING.
[DÉBORA] HOW COME YOU'RE NOT GOING?
IT'S YOUR PARENTS' WEDDING PARTY.
[JORGINHO] I DON'T KNOW. IF WE SEPARATED, THEN I THINK WE DESERVED IT
A BIG PARTY. TUFÃO AND CARMINHA SEPARATE! HUM?
[DÉBORA] BASED ON WHAT ARE YOU SAYING THIS?
IN MY VIEW, THEY LOOK HAPPY.
[JORGINHO] BECAUSE YOU WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND, NO.
[DÉBORA] SO, WHY DON'T YOU EXPLAIN TO ME?
[JORGINHO] I KNOW THINGS, RIGHT, I FEEL. THAT WOMAN
IT'S NO GOOD, IT'S NOT GOOD FOR MY FATHER. IF MY FATHER WAS
EVEN IN THAT HOUSE, THEN HE WOULD BE FINE, VERY FINE.
[DÉBORA] DID YOU KNOW THAT YOU ARE MAKING A VERY STRONG ACCUSATION?
SERIOUS, WITH NO BASIS WHATSOEVER, RIGHT? HAVE YOU EVER STOPPED TO THINK THAT
COULD THIS BE A PROBLEM YOU HAVE WITH YOUR MOTHER?
[JORGINHO] OH, SHE SENT YOU HERE, DIDN'T SHE?
NO, YOU CAN SPEAK.
[DÉBORA] STOP BEING PARANOID,
I CAME TO SEE YOUR TRAINING. BY THE WAY, SPEAKING OF TRAINING,
CAN YOU EXPLAIN WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT'S GOING ON IN YOUR HEAD?
[JORGINHO] OH, THAT MARRIAGE STORY THERE,
CARMINHA'S WEDDING ANNIVERSARY WITH MY FATHER. THAT WAS IT.
THE WOMAN WAS CALLING ME ALL DAY... SHE BORED ME.
[DÉBORA] HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT GETTING AN ANALYSIS, MY LOVE? [LAUGHTER]
SERIOUSLY, THERAPY WOULD DO YOU GOOD.
[JORGINHO] YOU SUFFER A LOT WITH THIS PROBLEM LITTLE BOY,
IT IS NOT?
[DÉBORA] YES, I MUST LIKE IT
OF PROBLEM BOY.
[JORGINHO] I LOVE YOU, YOU KNOW?
[DÉBORA] SO, IF YOU LOVE ME, LET ME ASK FOR THE BILL
SO WE CAN GO RIGHT AWAY.
[JORGINHO] NO, NO, NO.
[DÉBORA] HEY, MY LOVE, LET'S GO? LET'S GO.
[JORGINHO] ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE ME THERE?
[BAR ATMOSPHERE]
[DÉBORA] I HAVE. ENOUGH, COME. WAITER, THE BILL, PLEASE!
[JORGINHO] NO, ONE MORE HERE.
[DÉBORA] NO, THE BILL.
♪IT AIN'T NO USE IN CALLIN'♪
♪OUT MY NAME, GAL♪
[NINA] DADDY!
[MARTÍN] "HEY"! READY FOR ADVENTURE, MARUJA?
[NINA] I CAME TO CATCH BIG FISH, CAPTAIN!
[MARTÍN] YES, I JUST WANT TO SEE, HUH. LET'S GO.
[LAUGHTER] LET'S GO.
♪I GIVE HER MY HEART♪
♪BUT SHE WANTED MY SOUL♪
♪DON'T THINK TWICE♪
♪IT'S ALL RIGHT♪
♪SO LONG, HONEY BEE♪
♪WHERE I'M BOUND♪
♪I CAN'T TELL♪
♪GOODBYE'S TOO GOOD A WORD♪
♪BABE♪
♪SO I'LL JUST SAY♪
♪FARE THEE WELL♪
♪I AIN'T SAYIN' YOU♪
♪TREATED ME UNKIND♪
♪YOU COULD HAVE DONE BETTER BUT♪
♪I DON'T MIND♪
♪YOU JUST KINDA WASTED♪
♪MY PRECIOUS TIME♪
♪DON'T THINK TWICE♪
♪IT'S ALL RIGHT♪
[TYPHOON] HEY! YOU CAME AT THE RIGHT TIME.
[TALK]
[VERÔNICA] CADINHO, IT'S WORSE THAN I THOUGHT,
IT'S THE CIRCUS OF HORRORS.
[CADINHO] I LOVE IT, THE WORKING CLASS IS GOING TO PARADISE.
GO, GO. TYPHOON!
[TYPHOON] OH, THAT'S GOOD.
[VERONICA] NICE TO MEET YOU.
[CRUCIBLE] LOOK, CONGRATULATIONS
FOR THE PARTY, SEE, CONGRATULATIONS!
[VERONICA] NICE TO MEET YOU.
[CARMINHA] IMAGINE!
[TYPHOON] THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
[CADINHO] I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU
LIST OF OUR CHILDREN, YOU SEE.
[CARMINHA] US TOO.
[CADINHO] VERÔNICA, IN PART, IS DYING TO RECEIVE YOU.
[VERONICA] CRAZY, CRAZY.
[TYPHOON] IS IT REAL?
[CRUCIBLE] AN INFORMAL DINNER.
[TYPHOON] NO, BOY, DON'T BE IMPRESSED BY THAT, NO,
THAT WE ARE HUMBLE PEOPLE. THERE IS NO SUCH SALAMALEQUE
NOT FROM CHIC PEOPLE.
[VERONICA] IMAGINE, IMAGINE.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A STROGANOFF
FOR YOU, DO YOU LIKE IT?
[CARMINHA] WE LOVE IT.
[VERONICA] THAT'S GREAT.
[CRUCIBLE] AGREEMENT, THEN.
[CARMINHA] FEEL FREE.
[TYPHOON] FEEL FREE THERE, FEEL FREE, GUYS.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING... MY LOVE OF MY LIFE,
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL OUTFIT!
[ÁGATA] DO YOU REALLY THINK SO, DAD?
[TYPHOON] DID YOU GET DRESSED BY YOURSELF?
[AGATE] YES.
[TYPHOON] WHAT A SHOW.
[LELECO] LET'S GO, LET'S GO, LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
[TALK]
[CARMINHA] JORGINHO HASN'T ARRIVED YET.
[TYPHOON] JORGINHO IS COMING, LOVE. DO YOU THINK HE'S GOING TO LOSE?
THIS, HUH? YOU WON'T MISS THIS FOR ANYTHING.
HE'LL BE HERE IN A MOMENT. COME ON, LET'S SIT DOWN HERE. LET'S GO!
OH, I'M GOING TO STAY HERE IN THE MIDDLE. COME WITH THE WOMAN, GUYS!
[CARMINHA] JORGINHO HAS ARRIVED.
[TYPHOON] I TOLD YOU HE WAS COMING. YOU THOUGHT HE WASN'T GOING TO COME
FOR A MOMENT IN YOUR LIFE?
[TYPHOON] WHAT'S UP, MY SON!
[JORGINHO] CONGRATULATIONS, DAD.
[DÉBORA] HELLO, GOOD NIGHT.
[JORGINHO] HI, GOOD NIGHT, EVERYTHING OK?
[CARMINHA] WHY DON'T YOU ANSWER MY CALLS?
[JORGINHO] HI, HI.
[TYPHOON] LEAVE HIM, LEAVE HIM, LEAVE HIM, CARMINHA.
LEAVE HIM, CARMINHA.
[MAX] CAN I KNOW WHERE YOU WERE?
[JORGINHO] I THINK IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS, RIGHT, YOU IDIOT?
[GLASS LINKING]
[JORGINHO] [EXTENDED] OOPS.
[POURING DRINK]
[CARMINHA] I THOUGHT A LOT ABOUT WHICH VOICE I WOULD WANT TO HEAR
THE STORY OF MY LIFE. THEN I THOUGHT OF A FAMOUS ANNOUNCER,
IN A WILLIAM BONNER, OR IN ANYONE OF MY OWN FAMILY,
BUT THEN I CAME TO THE CONCLUSION THAT THE BEST PERSON TO TELL
THIS STORY FOR YOU WAS ME, YOUR CARMINHA.
WELL, MY FAIRY TALE STARTED 12 YEARS AGO,
WHEN I MET THE MAN OF MY LIFE, MY COMPANION,
MY SOULMATE, MY GREAT FRIEND, FATHER OF MY CHILDREN
AND, ON TOP OF ALL, A GENIUS OF FOOTBALL AND LIFE.
IT IS HIM, YES, THAT I'M TALKING ABOUT, MY HUSBAND, JORGE TUFÃO,
A MAN WHO MAKES EVERY DAY I WAKE UP WITH HIM
A WONDERFUL ADVENTURE THAT CHANGED MY LIFE
IN A LOVE POEM. A MAN WHO, LIKE ME, INVESTED EVERYTHING,
LIFE, ENERGY, DREAMS, IN THE FAMILY
AND HE FORMED A CHRISTIAN FAMILY WITH ME, OF WHICH I AM VERY PROUD.
TO SAY: "OLD-FASHIONED, YES, SIR, THANK GOD".
[OVATION]
[POURING DRINK]
[DÉBORA] MY LOVE, ENOUGH, RIGHT?
I THINK IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO SLOW DOWN A LITTLE.
[JORGINHO] NO, LOVE, NOW THAT IT'S GETTING GOOD
AND I WANTED TO HAVE A BEER,
I DIDN'T WANT TO JUST STAY WITH WHISKEY, NO.
[DÉBORA] [LAUGHTER] LOVE, STOP. HUH?
[TYPHOON] CARMINHA IS... LOOK AT ME, LOOK AT ME.
CARMINHA IS MY WIFE, RIGHT? CARMINHA HAS BEEN WITH ME FOR 12 YEARS,
WE RAISED OUR CHILDREN TOGETHER.
CARMINHA, I'M GOING TO TELL YOU SOMETHING, IT'S A TOUGH BONE TO CRACK,
UNDERSTAND? SHE'S A WOMAN WHO WHEN AN ARGUMENT COMES,
RIGHT? THAT'S IT, MY LOVE. I LOVE YOU!
[CARMINHA] [LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
[WHISTLE]
[CRUCIBLE] VERY WELL.
[VERÔNICA] I'VE ALREADY HEARD THAT STORY.
[APPLAUSE]
[IVANA] HEY, PSST! YOU REALLY DIDN'T RECORD A STATEMENT, HUH?
[JORGINHO] NO, BUT IF YOU WANT I'LL GO THERE AND TALK TO YOU NOW, DO YOU WANT?
[IVANA] IT'S YOUR MOTHER, RIGHT?
[JORGINHO] OK, I'LL SAY IT. IF YOU WANT ME TO GO THERE, I WILL.
[NINA] WHO CAUGHT THE BIG FISH THIS TIME?
[MARTÍN] CONGRATULATIONS, "BUT NOTHING COMPARED TO THAT MARLIN
ON THE METRO AND MEDIUM, WHICH I TOOK THAT TIME''', HUH?
[NINA] AND ONLY YOU SAW IT, RIGHT? OH, A FISHERMAN'S STORY, HUH, DAD.
[MARTÍN] YES, GO, GO PULL THE ANCHOR. YES.
[BEACH ATMOSPHERE]
[BOAT IGNITION]
[BOAT ENGINE]
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[NINA] ''DADDY''?
[NINA] ''DADDY'', ''DADDY''!
[MOAN]
[NINA] ''DADDY'', WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MARTÍN] MY HEART.
[MARTÍN] I'M GOING TO DIE, I KNOW.
[NINA] DON'T SAY THAT, DAD.
[MARTIN] NINA.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MARTÍN] OF ALL MY DAUGHTERS,
YOU ARE THE ONE I LOVED THE MOST, EVEN THOUGH YOU ARE NOT MY BLOOD DAUGHTER.
YOU KNOW, RIGHT?
[NINA] I KNOW, DAD.
[MARTÍN] WILL YOU PROMISE ME THAT YOU WILL FORGET
FROM THIS WOMAN WHO CHANGED HER LIFE IN BRAZIL.
THAT YOU'RE GOING TO GIVE UP THIS REVENGE, HUH? PROMISE ME.
[NINA] I PROMISE.
[MARTÍN] PROMISES.
[NINA] [SCREAMING] HELP!
[MARTÍN] STOP. STOP, NINA. STOP, GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MARTÍN] LET'S PLAY? HUH? LOOK IN THE EYES, REMEMBER?
[NINA] [SNIFLE]
[MARTÍN] CAN'T LAUGH.
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[MARTÍN] YOU CAN'T CRY.
[MARTÍN] I CANNOT...
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[CRYING]
[JORGINHO] NO, JUST ONE MORE SIP.
[APPLAUSE]
[CARMINHA] GOOD NIGHT, GUYS.
[TYPHOON] GOOD NIGHT.
[CARMINHA] IT'S EASIER TO TALK TO A CAMERA THAN LIKE THIS, RIGHT?
LIVE, IN FRONT OF YOU ALL.
I'M SORRY,
BUT IT IS A MOMENT OF VERY EMOTION.
[APPLAUSE]
[CARMINHA] I WANT TO CALL THE MAN ON STAGE...
WHO TOOK ME OUT OF THE BOTTOM OF THE ROCK AND GAVE ME A LIFE...
[CRYING] I THOUGHT I NEVER DESERVED IT.
COME, TYPHOON!
[APPLAUSE]
[CARMINHA] COME, TYPHOON!
[OVATION]
[TYPHOON] I'M COMING, MY LOVE!
[APPLAUSE]
[OVATION]
[TYPHOON] MY LOVE! 12 YEARS AGO, MY PEOPLE...
[CARMINHA] [LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] I MARRIED CARMINHA AND GAVE HER A BULLSHIT RING
A LOT FOR HER, YOU UNDERSTAND?
[LAUGHTER]
BUT TODAY I WILL CORRECT MY MISTAKE,
BECAUSE I BOUGHT YOU A BRILLIANT RING
WITH A LOT OF CARAT, THERE, OH. PUT IT THERE, MY LOVE.
THIS IS PRACTICALLY A... A KENNEL.
[CARMINHA] [LAUGHTER]
[TYPHOON] [LAUGHING] IT'S BEAUTIFUL, ISN'T IT?
[TYPHOON] AND I WANT TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THE OPPORTUNITY TO...
[KISS SNAP]
[TYPHOON] I LOVE YOU TOO. [LAUGHTER]
I WANT TO ALSO TAKE THIS OPPORTUNITY TO CALL MY CHILDREN
HERE ON STAGE. ÁGATA, MY PRINCESS, COMES RUNNING.
[IVANA] GO, GO, PRETTY ONE.
[TYPHOON] JORGE!
[DÉBORA] NO, MY LOVE, YOU DON'T GO. STAY HERE, IT'S BETTER...
[JORGINHO] NO, NOW IS MY MOMENT.
[DÉBORA] NO, YOU WON'T, NO.
[JORGINHO] I WILL...
[DÉBORA] STOP, MY LOVE.
[JORGINHO] I WILL. I WILL BE HAPPY.
[OVATION]
[JORGINHO] OPA! I'M GOING ALL IN.
[TYPHOON] MY PRINCESS COMING UP HERE.
[JORGINHO] I'M GOING, I'M GOING.
[TYPHOON] BEAUTIFUL, GORGEOUS, SPECTACULAR.
[AGATA] CONGRATULATIONS, FATHER.
[TYPHOON] THANK YOU, MY ANGEL.
[OVATION]
[TYPHOON] COME HERE, SON. THIS WAY, LOOK.
[APPLAUSE]
[TYPHOON] SINCE...
THIS SON OF MINE HERE DID NOT SPEAK IN THE TESTIMONY,
THERE ON THE BIG SCREEN, YOU WILL BE FORCED TO SPEAK HERE LIVE!
[TALK]
[ÁGATA] I THINK JORGINHO IS DRUNK, MOM.
[CARMINHA] DRUNK?
[JORGINHO] [LAUGHTER] WHO CAME HERE
CELEBRATE THE WEDDING ANNIVERSARY OF...
FROM MY BELOVED FATHER AND CARMINHA.
AND IT'S TRUE, IT'S TRUE, I DIDN'T GIVE MY STATEMENT,
BUT, MAN, WHO KNOWS, YOU CAN DO IT LIVE, RIGHT, DAD?
[TYPHOON] THAT'S IT.
[JORGINHO] SO, I'M GOING TO START SAYING THAT...
I AM NOT PART OF THIS FAMILY, I AM NOT PART OF THIS FAMILY.
THIS WOMAN HERE TOOK ME OUT OF WHERE I LIVED,
I WAS LIVING IN THE DUMP, YOU SHOULD HAVE LEFT ME THERE. BECAUSE YOU...
YOU'RE NOT MY MOTHER, ARE YOU LISTENING?
[CARMINHA] GIVE ME THIS HERE! GIVE ME THIS HERE, BOY.
[JORGINHO] YOU'RE NOT MINE...
[CARMINHA] GIVE ME THIS!
[TYPHOON] LOOK AT YOUR MOTHER! BE CAREFUL WITH...
♪DRAMATIC MUSIC♪
[JORGINHO] DID YOU PUT ME IN THE WORLD?
[JORGINHO] TALK TO ME, LOOK INTO MY EYES AND SAY,
DID YOU PUT ME INTO THE WORLD?
♪TENSION MUSIC♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME TO BREAK EVERYTHING♪
♪LET'S DANCE WITH EVERYTHING♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪
♪HI, HI, HI, HI♪
♪COME DANCE WITH ME♪
♪HI, HI, HI♪